FOREVER!
DOG!
Gentle Warning
The following podcast
may contain soothing
melodies and shimmering
synths that transport you
beyond outer space on
the wings of a butterfly.
Today with musician Kevin Tully
we take a relaxing
journey through the background
music that gives theme parks
their atmosphere. It's
Aerial Loops on podcast
The Ride.
Welcome to podcast The Ride, a podcast which would be a perfect musical area loop for a theme park called Dorkland. I'm Scott Gardner, Genphi, my girl.
Welcome to Dorkland. To all who come to this loserish place.
Go fuck yourself.
Jason Sheridan.
No lies detected
on my end.
Great, great.
Dorkland is your land.
Here age
recalls, what the hell is all that shit?
He's phrasing it so weird.
Could we prove the
dorkiness by how well do we know
the opening?
Oh right, the plaque or whatever. Not the plaque, but the speech.
Age recalls.
It's a nonsense phrase.
I'm not going to be able to recall it.
Age recalls fond memories of the past.
That's how people talked in the old days.
Here's a question, was Walter
dork? He has all the trappings
of a real dork.
Maybe by the standards of the
fifties.
Being a man
with a job and a
parent who has any interests.
That's true.
That's something that he enjoys in his life.
That was the definition of dork.
Other than sleeping or coming.
Other than that,
you like things.
It's a problem.
Tons of scotch pouring.
Okay, liquor as well.
I do think he is
a dork. I don't know, you can have a lot
of interests. Coming in the door, slamming it.
Yelling behind.
Creating the air
when you come home from work.
Too angry to talk to.
So the kids know to keep their distance
and not go in that room.
Eating some unseasoned food
while you enjoy a cigarette.
An unfiltered cigarette.
Ashing and mashed potatoes.
These are all
the interests of a well rounded
fifties man.
I'm just trying to think of what was a
fifties dork. What do they look like?
Like a
poindexter, like George McFly.
So like just standard dork.
So Walt presented as traditionally
masculine, but he had secret
dork tendencies.
There may be an argument
to be made that he was the inventor
of the dork.
That's a good point.
Whether that means him or that he set up
so much dorkiness.
Which we are a part of that
tradition. He's a dork pioneer.
His interest in trains was just straight up masculine
at the time. Nothing weird about that.
Now
it's a little weird.
But at the time that was just standard for like
a man of a certain age.
Well if it got a bunch of
black goo
all over your face
and arms, then how could that ever be considered
dorky? If you were covered in soot after
dealing with your favorite hobby.
Good to go. Covered in soot
you can read
science fiction, like dime store
novels. But you had to be
covered in soot to not be
considered a dork. Oh, if the books
had a bunch of soot. Yeah, well in your
face. It's spreading the soot on
each face that you touch. It's simple at smearing
some grease paint.
On your face or your arms. But now
performatively it has to happen organically.
It cannot be a performative gesture.
Like you said, you can't smear it on yourself.
In the act of reading the books
you have to get covered in soot or some sort
of crap. Okay.
You don't agree with me? I'll fight you on this.
Alright. I'm going to argue.
I want to argue. What if it's performative
but you're enjoying black and white
scotch and like an unfilled
Chesterfield while you do it?
Okay, that's better. And if you're drinking
a glass of soot then you're
yes. Then you're really a proper
1950's man.
Let's cut to the chase here
a little bit. Referred to in the opening
joke. Today's episode
is about areal loops.
I'm so happy to say this
phrase. It's been said on the show
here and there. But to finally have
it be an
episode title. To be focused
on. To be fixated on.
This I feel like is long
overdue. Let me give the quick dictionary
definition at the top
just so we know what we're talking about. I think this is a
thing that a hardcore
theme park dork definitely is
aware of but for a lay person or a
slightly less invested person. Areal
loops are just basically, I mean there's
so much more than this. But the fundamental
I would say is that it's the background music
in a particular land or area
in a theme park. It is the
musical soundtrack
to a theme park zone
that gives it it's auditory flavor
that sets the genre of what kind of
place you're in. What kind of
feeling you should be feeling in
this zone of a theme park.
And we're gonna
focus in on this and talk about
some of our favorites. Talk about what makes them
great. And I'm so
happy that this is coming to us courtesy
of our guest who is a very
musically minded person.
PTR listeners first met him as the
avatar which helped us transport
Nick Weigert to the CityWalk Orlando
parking garage. But in real
life he is no mere blank
slate avatar just waiting
for Nick Weigert to fill him
why he leads a vast
creative life. Including as the
lead singer songwriter of a great band called Telethon
whose new album Suburban Electric
is available now. He also has
already performed a hell of a mic drop
right at the top of the show. He's made PTR
history because he is the first guest ever
to bring in his own version
of the theme song. You have
already heard this at the top of the show
so you have heard his work. Now you will hear
the man himself. Please welcome Kevin Tully.
Hello. It's great
to be here. What is happening?
I'm so happy to be here.
It's a pleasure
to have you particularly because
there's this phrase that is thrown around
friend of the show or friend
of the pod and you have certainly
become that and more.
It's been such a pleasure. Thank you.
For sure. I mean
from helping us out with a true
theme park podcast
pioneering move of
the Avatar program to
close out the saga but also just
like getting to know you just like
you know via
DMs and chats through the years
Sending trash to you via text
message. Well it's
all I want. It's all I want to happen
and I'm so glad we have
that cooking. It's wonderful to share
be able to share crap with people
and have select
people to share
select crap with. Yes.
No it's really important
and you've like I think you've found
you have this relationship
certainly I think with Mike and I both
I think you straddle a lot of
Mike and Scott
interests. That's true yes.
We the hosts of the show who sometimes
cannot find common ground in certain
areas you are able to
be you cover the common
you become the common ground
because you're able to you know
and friends because now we've you know we've gotten
to hang out in Orlando a couple of times which has been wonderful
but you were like you will
both wander the
liminal spaces at the
at the Swan and Dolphin the locked in time
admire the
never changing carpet of the Dolphin
Hotel but also
visit Jelly Rolls with Mike
and be enthusiastic at Jelly Rolls
with Mike. Yes and we should say you
were at Jelly Rolls with us one of the nights
that I went to Jelly Rolls for this recent trip
so yes you were doing a
lot you were doing both things. You will talk
to Scott about some sort of obscure
I don't know session player but then also you'll
spend a long time talking to me about
when will Stephen Page rejoin the
Bare Naked Ladies is it possible
are we going to have to deal with a
Stephen Page less Bare Naked Ladies
forever. I think we are sadly
and I think you're right I think we are sadly
I think we've come down to that
it seems like he's happy where he's at
I hope that's true
and Ed is a good natured pilot who
used to write music we like. And we talk about Ed Robertson
Ed in case you know Ed is the one who
raps on one week and Stephen was the one who
was playing and Stephen left the band many years ago
and Ed is still in the band with
everybody else. I feel like I always thought the drummer was an
Ed. Is the drummer an Ed? That's Tyler
Okay I've had him mixed up the entire
time. What's Ed's last name? Robertson
Ed Robertson. Okay
It's like a game show here. It's like I knew that name
but I think I always slotted doesn't it I mean it sounds like
a drummer name a little bit. Ed Robertson
yeah a little bit. Tyler Stewart is
the name of the drummer he's the
silly one I would say as often the
drummers are. Yes
Would you not say there are multiple silly ones
in the Bare Naked Ladies? Well
To some degree
I would say that the ones in the band
currently are silly and
the one who has left the band was
a little bit less silly but still a little silly
This is a big question I have asked then
I cut to the core with that question
You both did a
well like
This is painful to
real B&L heads
Like a group mind meld
We've discussed like are there people
that go see Bare Naked Ladies that don't even realize Steven's
not there and I think the answer is yes
The answer is all touring band this is
always the case I can speak from
Beach Boys fandom I think there's tons
I think maybe 70%
of the audience at a Beach Boy at a current
Beach Boys show don't know one
iota about they don't know who Brian
Wilson is they don't know that
he's not there they don't know the
drama that occur they just think
wow it's them. Who are all of
those nine men must be the all
of the guys who sang Surfer Girl
in 1962
with no drama or changeover
And what percentage of those
people that go to current Beach Boys shows
are like the pitchfork
type people who are like Pet Sounds is
the greatest album of all time and
it's like like hipsters who appreciate
the genius
I honestly think it might be
like a 1%
I think there's an in between percentage
there has to be to well I'm not in the
1% because I don't go
that's the most elite
I've never seen just pure
we have sorry we have an agreement
that I think if they're
still touring in a decade
as the Mike Love Beach Boys then you
will go see them I forgot that
I made I don't know when when when did I make that
was that last year okay so nine
years we have nine years to go
until he has to go and
see them this is like the high
school or college friends are like if not married
by 35
marry each other
a lot like that yeah
so yes
much nerdier and in pursuit of by then
almost entirely AI
a 95
year old man right oh man
at those shows all the audience is like
hey does anyone have a lipid
tour that I can bump
so yeah Kevin
yeah we we you like the
90s crap you like a lot of mainstream
90s crap absolutely
and that's where we bond in
especially yeah that's how we initially
bonded yeah so
so it's yeah it's good it's good
to have somebody to talk about
Adam Durwitz with and Stephen Jenkins
you keep saying Durwitz
my saying is wrong? Durwitz
yeah I knew that even I knew that but it's okay
I do not know wait how many you've never known
it wasn't Durwitz don't feel embarrassed
Jason?
I feel like you texted it to me and I let
it slide the other day ah in
text you think it's text Durwitz too
I'm actually I feel like that's one of those where
like I knew that was wrong at one
point and then I forgot because
I said it without even thinking so
or I just never know it
even though I watched the full Rick Beato interview with
him well I should know it
another name that we used to say wrong
and I stand by that Rick
Beato is a cool he's a musician he'd be
named Beato it would make sense and Robertson
sounds like a drummer's name Rick Beato
is the ultimate drummer's name Rick Beato is like
a Star Wars side characters
name like it would be in the cantina
and have an action
and to clarify a George
named Star Wars
character a new character would never
be named Rick Beato but George
would have named somebody that in 2005
no problem true
and you're right to your
joke Jason I think you need to start
it's only fair
that you start I think maybe
just practice it once asking a very leading
question of your co-host which is
Adam what?
this is your chance to have
this is your chance to have a buka
a buka to what?
Beppo
he got it
Mike what is it?
Durrits
now try it again in four months
without any prep or we'll see
if he resets
Beppo got it
Jason I need to find crap to share with you
now I have crap that I share
off mike you did share
something with him
you were asking if I'd seen Topsy Turvy
and I was like no I don't know if I've
seen any Mike Lee movies
but Topsy Turvy is
about Gilbert
and Sullivan
you were the first person I thought of when I
watched it
I like this timing because
there is a
pirates music
like a reimagined
Pirates of Penzance
musical on Broadway
and you know David Hyde Pierce
is playing the modern major general
is he?
I love David Hyde Pierce
I'll tie that into some Nerd to My Have
which is that like that's crazy
that he'd be doing that because he
sang that song during his SNL monologue
in 1995
with musical guest live
that's my guess
in a certain era I can typically name
the musical guest
I didn't know that in the front of my mind
but I knew it in my bones
if you had to guess
or if you'd been a writer at the time and you had to write
a monologue for David Hyde Pierce that may be
where you would have gone
now I'm going to be upset if it's not
David Hyde Pierce and live
I think so
yeah because I feel like
it's no the Mulaney pointed out
Patrick Stewart's Salt and Pepper
but it's
it's always
good when you have the like
the more of the esteemed stage
actor saying ladies and gentlemen
live I do remember
that it is like very very well
delivered any feelings
about live either of you
you know what's the single
what's the live single
Fire Alone or
Lightning Crashes
I like those fine I never got into it
I'd be willing
to but I don't have too much
too many thoughts
I listen to Throwing Copper
the album that has both of those songs like a lot
in about
2014 I don't know
why I was like
throwing the album art of that
album is exceedingly
ugly it's like really ugly
no this I gotta see
it's like a throwing oh my god
yes that's a great
it looks like kind of a like a
like the
art of a
actor that would be on a Brown Derby
type restaurant it looks like somebody was
trying to do that for Marlon Brando
and then it went horribly awry
it looks like AI art
it really does it really looks like weird AI
this time yeah yeah
produced by Jerry Harrison of Talking Heads
it's a good album it's the precursor
to like a lot like I think the sound
of Throwing Copper became
something really terrible
that we all like
you know like butt rock type
sure sure I think that
live was the precursor to that
a little bit but that that live
album actually holds up pretty
well transcends that where like your
your creeds you might say
kind of like started playing
in the gutter of this
perhaps diverging from the path
the righteous path of
butt rock and it's yeah so it's not live's fault
live did not live if
maybe only accidentally they created
butt rock yeah that guy had an interesting haircut
too but I think he's bald now
I thought yeah I thought he just had no hair
perhaps like a pony like a
bald with maybe like a ponytail behind
I might be thinking of somebody else oh my god
wow that's a rare one
how do you do that
science shouldn't allow it well that's good though
Gilbert and Sullivan is a tie
well I feel like in terms of music
I feel like it's either gotta be
it's like a
confident female rap that Jane listens
to and therefore Jason
so it's either Ice Spice or it's like
Hello My Baby Hello My Ragtime Gal
it's a song Michigan J
Frog would have sung
that's the Jason music well and I'm sitting
over here and I was trying to figure out
like wait did David
Hyde Pierce sing Gilbert and Sullivan
the simpsons and I'm like no
Sideshow Bob in the Cape Fear
episode sings some
quick hits of the HMAS
pinafore and then
David Hyde Pierce is
Sideshow Mel
Sideshow Mel is
the guy who's always around
Sideshow Cecil
Sideshow Cecil because Frazier
would have been humming at that point
did Gilbert and maybe this is
a spoiler alert for the movie did Gilbert and Sullivan
ever have a Robertson Page
style breakup there's a little
bit of that in the film but do you
just mean a breakup
well I mean not specifically to like a
drug arrest that led to some problems
and then the band sort of broke up after having
a children's album a Playhouse Disney cruise
gone awry
is that true
wait no so it is
applicable hang on what's the story
here we got a lot to get through but let's do a condensed
version of the story
I don't think Gilbert and Sullivan had that
kind of breakup they definitely had TIFs
and if I'm forgetting a major plot point in the movie
I apologize I've watched a lot of Mike Lee
movies the past two months so
there's an arrest
then they make the children's album
I think they made it before that but then they're
supposed to go on like a tour and that kind of
gets derailed because it's kind of weird
that one of them got arrested blah blah blah
also don't feel like Stephen wanted to make that
children's album and
that's the whole thing then they do
do their bare naked ladies cruise
that they had done for a year or two before
that point
and this does feel related to Gilbert and Sullivan
in that big ships are involved
that's true much like the HMS Pinoff
I believe the last song they
ever played together outside of the
Canadian Hall of Fame induction is
Call and Answer
which is a really it's a video I
watch every few months the final
performance which is a really
nice song and then I
think really the nail in the coffin is a lawsuit
over the Big Bang Theory theme
which Stephen feels he didn't
get the right amount of money for that
he is on the track
I believe Ed says he wrote it himself
once that show becomes the biggest
show of the decade yeah you probably start thinking
that money no matter what you did on it
you need to get your residuals from the Big Bang
Theory right yes if there are any to get
God knows I don't blame him
which I did I saw
Big Bang Theory
not Big Bang Theory
Baronade Ladies with my dad and brother
in Atlantic City in like 2013
2014 I yelled at you for not knowing
Stephen was not there you were
very that was when you made that
KG joke you meant the guy
you're staring at that was the first
thing he said was like Stephen's not there
but the crowd obviously
first off my brother and I
were the youngest people in the audience by
many years and this was a very
seated concert this
was not people standing up
but they like real
quick transition from one song
to the next and did the Big Bang
Theory theme and the crowd
went nuts yeah of course yeah so
anyway they're playing I have
much like you have not seen the Ed Robertson
Baronade Ladies yeah you get it
all right all in 10 years there's a chance
I will see it next month
though at the Greek Theater
Fastball or Guster
opening for that one both of them I think
both?
goodness me
you're going to have to get back out here
really excited
that line up really excited my mother
Mike is
reclaiming the phrase get him
to the Greek to be about him
going to see the Ed Robertson
Baronade Ladies
and get them
him and his mom
that's sweet
in a reasonable amount of time
minus the extremely cursed
stars of the film
of the actual movie I shouldn't say
cursed that implies that they got
hit by a curse that caused what's
happening to them I think it was more
their decision making than a
curse but who knows I
don't know what happened I don't know what magic
amulets they're into
by curse you mean the power of Christ
oh you did bring us amulets
that's right you brought us
you're probably going to have some amulet talk today
I feel like some of these
composers definitely wear some big
amulets either own them or
are interested in them or inspired by
the idea of them but
I don't think possess any of the
toxic qualities of
musicians Diddy or Aldous Snow
we all
know as the star of
get him to the Greek
let's start heading into the
music loops direction and I'm
so glad you suggested this
Kevin
you know you obviously
being a musician yourself as evidence
to thank you for that
you played us this before we started recording
that is a brand new this is a new
dimension to coming on the show putting
your own stamp on it and I love
that theme it's amazing what two
hours to kill at your Burbank
Airbnb will do
for your productivity that's
a magical piece for being two
hours happy to do it speaks to your
talents but we were
I feel like we were talking about a lot of things
and we landed here and it did seem
like like the thing to do
maybe just a tiny bit more I mean I
think it's not like the headiest
concept but I do like that we're doing
kind of like an overview of area loops
before because what this does now is
free us up to maybe do an entire
episode about this loop oh yeah
or we do full we do a commentary
this might work for commentary
we could just play the music and talk
over it as opposed to a commentary
something where you need a video but basically
you know it's the background
music to a you know a land
or the entire
park or even an entrance plaza
or a hotel
or even a shuttle or a
bus it's just you know it's the background
music that plays in a theme park area
it's I feel like typically
they're around an hour
long and they just loop all day the
rest of the day although not always as
we've seen with recent
theme park fair
but it's really become this big area I feel
like in the YouTube era
because there are channels that allow you to
you know to check these out and archive
them there's hundreds and hundreds of these on
YouTube and we can we'll talk about them and
play some of them
but was there any particular
reason or philosophy why why have all the
topics to talk to us about why this
and not the reasons for the Bear
Naked Ladies demise?
Well it is
something that I feel
the area loops I believe are sort of
inside me at a well
at a deep level
it's my
blood and loins
no like ever since
I was a very
small boy like
nerding out on the internet
about Disney World
like these have loomed
really large and soundtracked
you know
much of my life
like and it used to be very hard to get
them
and now we're living in a golden
age of
YouTube availability
for these things. It's so insane
the importance that used to be placed
on a soundtrack
album that Disney would put out like
oh my god they did a 25th anniversary
of Disney World album
which means I can finally listen to
this track this track
whatever you know this Epcot
music the music from
you know Big Thunder
The Line whatever it is
and you were just waiting on those
morsels and I remember being a kid
thinking like if only there was a way now that we can
burn CDs why isn't
there like a way you can just go burn a CD
in the parks of any of the music
that I would want and now it's like
this is like more than
available to us for free
do you remember the kiosks where you
could burn CDs? Okay
as I was saying it I was thinking
am I not pulling this from whole cloth but rather
faintly recalling that there was
a thing of this nature. They were kiosks
whoa. Where?
I didn't know this. You know how they have
like the art of Disney kiosks in various
stores where you can like pick
a painting
and it will print for
you in any size. Is it Disneyana
in Disneyland?
When you first go in on the right. Yeah
yeah and that's where they have like statues and stuff
but then they also have a kiosk where you can basically like
order a print. Posters on demand.
Yep exactly but they had
that I don't know exactly where they were but
they were kiosks
in various stores just
like that where you could hand select
tracks and the funny
thing is I
impossibly have not impossibly
very possible through the power of
BitTorrent but I have every
file that was ever available
on a folder
and there's some obscure stuff on there.
Really? Stuff that is like beyond
what these YouTubers might find
and post? 100% it's like not and that
stuff's not really on there. Like
the stuff that we would want
probably is like a lot of it is not on there
but if you want like a
clip of
you know Ben Franklin and
the American Venture like
being like I assure you these
glasses are not rose colored like
you can get that sound bite
on a CD. Of course I do.
It's the least hamfisted
jamming of a fact into dialogue
I've ever heard. Send that to
Jason Kevin that's what you're in
with him is. I'll send you the file. The folder.
I knew about the kiosk
a few
I learned about them a few years ago I never
saw them. I do
remember pulling stuff
on
my tunes in like local
college dorm networks
and I would like
flip out if there was theme park
stuff but I remember being
Would you find theme park music in the
dorms? Yeah every well cause you
could see everyone's
audio
collections. Did you
not like just go straight to that
try to find the name go straight to their door
and if a woman asked to marry
them. Okay there
was I was at
a friend's dorm once
and it was just a bunch of us hanging
out and we were we were all fiddling
with that and looking at it cause not everyone
knew like there was a new version of it out
and there was one with
like tons of theme park stuff
and I was like trying to explain
to her I was like can you download
this stuff and burn it to CDs
for me? And the reaction was pretty
much no.
Oh so rather the opposite
this became a wedge between you
and another as much of our theme park
fandom all was before meeting each other
before the vast wave of
theme park fandom that has grown
over the year now that we all together
live in dork land. I think this
is a particularly like
topic for the real theme park
heads to like
I don't really get
excited about hearing
it's a small world or something
like the songs from the
park. Do you know what I mean?
I don't mind them but I don't listen
to those almost every
you know couple times a week.
It's more
and not without giving away
some of what we want to talk about it is more
like okay there was this
track with just this odd
bubbly like
some bubbly synth
that was kind of like
a little bit cheesy and embarrassing but
like really did it for me when I was a kid
and it was probably like
track four of ten in the
queue of horizons or whatever.
That sort of thing. That's always
what we're after.
And some of the YouTube
loops
people have had to reconstruct
stuff or then some of the
stuff you're listening to and you're like
I think this is source audio
how did they get this?
That's a big question I have.
Where did these all come from?
How is there so much of this on YouTube?
You gotta stick a microphone
in a bush or go into like the
bathroom and
You think that's what happened?
No I mean I know
that the speakers in the bush and
the speakers in the bathroom are like great
great ways to
mainline the
loops.
The last time we were in Orlando
I was like okay there's
original audio
in the port of entry restrooms
by Seuss Landing.
And I went in there to
use the bathroom and
I just heard what I thought
was an argument.
And I came out and I looked around
and no one was in there and I realized
like this is source
this is
original audio of
people arguing
but I didn't want to be a creep just
recording with my phone
like in a bathroom.
What was the argument about?
Wouldn't it have been like a
very charactery type of argument?
It was charactery and I thought
Like you will not be
voyaging today? What are you doing you crazy woman?
It is, it was
something like that and I was like
what is going on out there?
The seas are much too rough today.
That's why I shall use my flying machine
you see? Whether or not you believe it is
possible. Jason's like oh this couple's really having
a hard time getting along today. It started
innocuous and I thought
it was two people arguing and then I came out
and no one was in there and I didn't
want to just, I didn't know how long
it was but I
have not been able to find, listener
if you know what I'm talking about. The islands
of adventure port of entry
specifically the Seuss Landing side
confisco grill
and Seuss Landing I don't know if it's
the residents of port of entry or the
imaginary
cooks at confisco grill
arguing. Oh could be.
It could be a
soundtrack that is character
cooks from a restaurant
and that's something they made and pumped into
the bathroom. Is confisco a guy?
Well I assume confisco is
the little statue, the deformed
man that's outside of
confisco grill. I always assume that
was confisco himself. I think so
and then you get a lot, you
this is you are a perfect guest for the show
the fact that you were referring to the little statue
of confisco. He has an oblong head. Something that has
stumped me, Jason is all
and again this is what you guys text about is
the ins and outs, every statue
port of entry. Well there's lots of good statues
there's the J. Jonah, Jameson
statue in the extended queue
for Spider-Man which I think they really
use these days. Dr. Doom's
throne, right?
Yes, his empty throne.
I can't, what you have described is so obscure
I cannot find a photo of it. Look up
confisco grill entrance.
We gotta find this oblong
head man. Entrance. A lot
of the
confisco grill pictures outside
of it were, used to be that
giant Seagram's mural that is
gone now. Wait I see it
now, okay. There is a guy, it's like
a, alright he's like bending in an odd
way. Can I see? His, I
think. Can you turn that toward me? Well it's
one of a zillion photos on a big old
something called TheStylishFoodie.com
Yeah, that
looks like, that looks like the guy. Does he not
have an oblong head? This guy?
Is he holding up a menu?
Yeah, and he has a
nose that I don't care for.
And does he get along with his wife?
That's my question. Does he yell at
his wife a lot? Yeah. Cause maybe
that's what you were hearing in the bathroom. He's got too
sweet of a smile, he can't be the fighter.
Those are always the worst. Oh that's
true. A smile, right?
Big phonies. The same, yeah yeah.
Okay, but let's start
let's start digging in
a little bit. And this is, yeah, I know that
this is a big area for you and I get, and I,
it's seemingly an influence on you
as a musician. I imagine
like, do you listen to these things
when you're like, just working
out and about trying to be inspired?
Yeah, I
do. I mean, especially with
so like, for the band
stuff, Telethon, like that's
more power pop, I find inspiration
listening to
power pop records. Sure. But
for a long time, the area loops were good
because they didn't remind me of anything
that I would ever be able to create. They're
like weird, they don't have the same
sensibilities melodically
as I like think in.
So for people who haven't heard your band, it's not
particularly the sound, it's not
the sound isn't reminiscent of
a banjo instrumental of the Davy
Crockett song. No, or like new
age music, like our ambient type
music, like
the music
I make is much more, I don't
know, it's more structured and
we don't find it
comfortable to stay in one musical
place for like a long time and like
be meditative or whatever, like we don't do
that at all, we're moving from place to
place to place, so listening to new age
music, as you might find on
these area loops,
not all of them, but many
of them, like was always kind of nice
for me to listen
to music that doesn't remind me of anything I'd
make. Now, I have
dabbled a little bit in making more
instrumental new age music recently.
As you did in the show, yes. Yeah, yeah.
And there's like a project I sort of
have cooking up that may never get finished, but
yeah, I'm kind of trying to do that
with recreated synths from the
80s and stuff, but
I don't want to spill
the secrets of your unfinished project, but you have
described this as like that you're trying to do
music for an imaginary Epcot
pavilion. That's right, yeah, I've been
privately, quietly
working on that since
Thanksgiving
last year, and
I don't know, again, I don't know if it will ever get finished,
but you heard it here first, yeah,
I'm kind of trying to make like a sweet
spot, like 19 minute
movement of instrumental
synth music, and I looked up like the
synths that all the people on
some loops we'll probably be talking about soon
were using, and that
they used on those albums, and I downloaded
like the official recreations of them,
and I've been just sort of messing around.
So like that thing I created for
this, that was in the
tone palette of those
recreated
synths. An actual old school, because that
was extremely, as we'll get into, and we
bonded over this style, but it's very like
Epcot of that era, Tomorrowland
of that era, and it's
one of the, we've discussed kind of the like
chicken or the egg
of it all, like do we love
this kind of music
because we grew up going to theme
parks, or
is it like an inverse
we, like we love that kind
of music, and then it's like, it just deepens our theme
park appreciation that that kind of music
was around, it gives us like a new wave of
theme park fandom, or is it really
like, the, you heard this
song when you were eight years old,
and so it's drilled, and it affected your
music taste forever
in a way that's permanent. You never really know,
you never fully know. You can't know.
It's certainly part of it. Yeah, yeah. It's gotta
be part of it. It's gotta be. And I for sure
have like responded to pieces
of music because I'm like, that
feels like something that would have played at Epcot.
Yeah, yes, of course.
Yeah, yeah. It happens.
Yeah, I think, I think probably the
average person that goes to these places don't
realize how much that is
I mean, they don't notice a
lot of it, just like how much it's
actually adding to the mood of it.
Just because, I mean, some of the
stuff I'm gonna play probably is more like
a real, like a traditional song
that's three minutes or whatever, but still
some of it, very background music-ish.
And if it wasn't playing, or if
it was a different song, it would really change.
Like we were at Universal
a couple days ago, and instead of like
the big soaring Universal theme as you walk in,
they're playing like three Billy Joel songs.
It does change the vibe. That drives me
nuts. Billy Joel specifically or just
rock and pop songs
at the park? I think music with words
in general at theme park
like as background music in theme parks kind of
bugs me. There's a part,
there's a section of Universal Studios
Florida that play, I know that
one of the songs on it is Pinch Me
by the Barenaked Ladies. And although I like
that song, I'm like, what is this doing
for the place making of the
park? It bothers me. And it's distracting.
And I think the best
theme park area loops and background
music is
contributing to the theme, but it is not
distracting. Yeah. That is a really
good point. Yeah, yeah. If it's
attracting your attention too much, or the
regular person's attention too much,
then it's not just, you know, it should be
similar to just like the details
on the awnings.
Like the aging
of an old building or the paint of a new building.
I was kind of going back
and forth on that
because I looked up
just in case there was any crossover,
I picked some alternates.
So I was looking up Hollywood Studios
music. And it's a lot of
instrumentals when you first enter,
but the loop I found
for specifically Sunset
Boulevard, which is the path,
the road leading to
Tower of Terror, is like
all, like, old
song standard, like
Andrew Sisters and stuff, standards.
I know they play Mersey Doats
on that loop, like Mersey Doats
and Dozy Doats. Sure I am, Dozy Davy.
He's spinning that thing, that thing
constantly. Yeah, number
seven Spotify rep, yeah. But I can't remember
if they have, so you heard words though.
Yeah. Well, that's
we were joking about, Begin the Begin
earlier. Oh, right. And I
forget which, it's a song that's been
sung, performed by a
million people, to
even, I forget whether
it was Julio Iglesias or Enrique
Iglesias, that version, more
more recently than
World War II, I mean.
The broad
strokes, the definition of recent.
By the way,
just the phrase, we were laughing about
Begin the Beguine.
That's something that Frazier and Niles would do.
Yeah, not to be too on the nose, but
I was talking about
what a fit of laughter we got into that day.
Begin the Beguine and Gilbert
Sullivan beforehand.
Well this is, I think what makes this
a very good topic
for us, for Podcast The Right
also, is how much it appeals to everybody's
specific niches
and interests, because like
within the three of us, the hosts, there's very
like, extremely
divergent musical taste,
but there is a place for all of us
within the world
of theme park area music.
Absolutely.
So, I guess I'll go ahead
here, I just have a couple things, I have
a little bit of a platter, a sample
or a platter of things.
We've all picked
one to focus on, one
that's always spoken to us.
One has turned into three.
So the premise was to do
something, then Mike broke the rules.
I had one again before, so
it's all out of control already.
This is going to become a Steven and Ed thing
real fast.
How long did the Bannock Ladies last together
as a band? 15 years? 20 years?
Probably.
We've got a couple more years to go.
So, yeah,
so some are like,
some of these things I have here are like
what we're describing in the background, but then one
that I really like is more of a loop of
like rock and roll,
I'll say that, with lyrics and whatever,
but it really is a place for all of us,
whether you like rock and roll music
or you like rock and roll,
you have a place
in the Disney parks. Yours, though,
have lyrics, but make sense
in the placement of like,
a nod to mid
20th century.
I think this is really up to the individual.
Do you want
songs with lyrics? Do you want
popular songs? Is it distracting to your
audience to listen to popular songs?
I feel like, and then sometimes
I feel like the majority
of these are instrumental,
but that doesn't mean they're always specifically composed
for the area, although some are,
and this is a big thing that's kind of trumpeted
when a new area opens, like the heat
is on, new, you know, because
in Galaxy's Edge you got new
area music by John fucking
Williams, and then in Epic
Universe the music is a huge
deal, I mean, so much music was made for
that. I have thoughts about that.
Good stuff.
Okay, okay.
Let's hear a little bit of Mike, and then let's,
because you've, like, well, we've been,
and now you've been, so yeah,
we should talk about, you know, the present
and future of area loop music
shown throughout the universe. I have thoughts, yep.
Great, great. We'll talk about it.
But Mike, where are you taking us?
What area are we looping to?
Toontown. I know what we're
listening to.
Wow, we've got a
cool, we've got a refreshed instrumental
eye-to-eye goofy movie, eye-to-eye.
I haven't heard this. Is this just
playing generally in Toontown? Yes. Okay.
Wow. So yeah, it's just,
there's a loungy eye-to-eye.
You can keep playing. You gotta get
into the chorus. Let's play and talk.
Sure, let's play and talk.
Wait for, wait for
the chorus here.
This is nice.
What, like, pop-wise does this remind
me of? That's what I was trying to
figure out, because this is one of my
favorites, too, and it is an example of a new
area loop that I think is
really phenomenal. Yes.
Yeah, we are not, and you particularly are
not, like, only the old ones are
good. I think that
there is an area I gravitate towards,
but I'm open to, I want new
ones to be good, and I think this Toontown
one, I mean, I noticed it last year when I
went into Toontown to ride
Runaway Railway, and
I instantly was like, this is a
new loop I've never heard before, and I found it on
YouTube, and I listen to it all the time.
It's so breezy,
but I don't know what genre it is.
I said loungy, but
it's kind of fully, like, lounge,
I don't know, but it is, like,
laid back to it. It's like a hard tip of my tongue that is
not coming, but, like, if you put vocals
on that. It's very breezy,
very happy, and they
picked good songs, like Chippendale,
Rescue Rangers is on there, Eye to Eye.
There's Mickey Mouse Club, and then there's
a couple from the Mickey Mouse Clubhouse,
which are, they might be
Giants songs. Hot Dog,
and the Mickey Mouse Clubhouse theme.
Which many parents know, but I don't.
Yes, I know it now.
The show's been on in the house lately, but I didn't know there
might be Giants.
Well, because they composed the theme
song to The Daily Show, right?
I wish that was on
Did they?
Or did they do a version of it?
I don't know.
That's because I thought, for a long time,
I thought they did Big Bang Theory.
Oh my god, Jason, you never said that to me.
I know, I know.
I would have smacked you in the face.
That's some common, like,
goofy music crossover,
Barenaked Ladies, TMBG.
TMBG, I think was The Daily Show and Malcolm in the Middle.
Right? Yes.
They did Malcolm in the Middle, I know that.
They may have done a new version of it at some point.
It's by Bob Mould.
Oh, right.
I don't even want to attempt.
Is it Husker Dew or is it Hoosker Dew?
It's a Hoosker?
Hoosker Dew, I think.
Sugar, he's in the band Sugar, which is a really good band.
Wait, but TMBG
wasn't involved with The Daily Show at all?
Not the original, but I think they may have done a version.
And then, of course, the Timbaland
remix that accompanied the show
in the later 20 cents.
Right.
Something I noticed about this Toontown loop is like
I think there's
certain bands do this really well.
When you get to be a very virtuosic musician,
you start filling in the spaces around
the melodies with
spicing things up and adding
flair. And you can only do
that really when you're really feeling the groove.
And Steely Dan was great at doing this.
I think My Beloved Fish is really good
at doing this. And whoever is playing
on this Toontown loop, like every little
thing that your ears want to
hear ends up
happening or they end up plussing it up
and doing something exciting with it.
Sort of filling in all available
space. Do we have any idea who did it?
Oh, you do, okay.
Michael Rubino. The Toontown tuners.
Well, that's what I was going to ask. I researched
this. This is on Spotify
as they uploaded.
This is a rare area loop that's been uploaded
as an album to Spotify.
And by the Toontown
tuners. But the
composer of it, I looked this up, was Michael
Rubino. He was just a
hardworking film and TV
and video game composer.
But how
would you feel if you assembled this great
ensemble? It
seems like it's a small ensemble
of musicians.
And these are probably people that need jobs
and need work. And this is a really good thing to put
on our portfolio, but it's just credited
only as the Toontown tuners.
There's no names attached.
It's probably something he's all
too familiar with. Right. I'd assume
working in all of these different areas.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
I'm not saying that makes it right.
Covered credits, yeah, yeah.
If you're listening and you're a Toontown
tuner, great job. Because yeah, everything
instrumentally going on there is great.
Yes, and I mentioned this before on the show, and I
don't know if this is available.
But if you go back, and I spent a lot of
time in Toontown recently, I do believe
this music is part of a really
nice reinvigoration of
Toontown in addition to the new
ride that's there. Obviously, I also have a child
that likes to be there now, so I'm in Toontown
way more than I ever was.
But there's a cool thing that happens
is if you go into the back by the caves,
there's even like quieter
versions of all the songs playing
in Toontown. That's fascinating.
I'll check tomorrow. And explain,
oh yes, please do.
Give us the report. But like,
it's not just quieter
volume. It's a rearrange. That's
interesting. What does that mean? Like less
instruments? Lullaby? Kind of more
of a lullaby-ish thing.
So you can go, if you're sitting, because there's benches under
in the caves, it's a really nice
place to chill out, kids or no kids.
There'll be some kids running around back there, but like
it's completely out of the sun.
And there's like really like
quiet versions. So you walk from
wherever in the cave and walk out into
the main Toontown, and then you hear like this version
now playing. You keep saying cave.
What cave? It's like a
fake rocks.
Toontown has a cave now. In the back of
Toontown, there's a cave.
It's what used to be the
Chippendale slide. It's like all the way in
the corner. It's the full corner of
Disneyland. There's fake grass
back there. The kids love it.
There's fake rocks. And then there is like a bunch
of fake rocks that kind of, I mean it's not
a cave that you can crawl into it, but it's a bunch
of fake rocks. And then there's a bunch of benches
in the back there. And you can completely get out of the sun
and chill out for a second.
It's still loud, but
it's different arrangements of these songs.
And it's a very neat little thing.
That's beautiful. That's beautiful stuff.
And there have been area loops
that came out in the past couple years
that I have been less than happy
about, but there are a couple that have
been really good. And I'm encouraged
to see that one of the most recent additions to
Disneyland has a great loop like this.
If you had to say
something that you don't like, and
you don't have to put a piece
of music on blast if you don't want to,
but could you describe,
because it doesn't seem like there's a lot of
areas in which these
can go wrong, but clearly they do.
What is in here? What
do we think makes a bad area loop?
Besides it just being like a bunch of
hits from 18
years ago. Although Mike might be into that
though too.
We're walking through Magic Mountain and then like,
oh, Bruno Mars.
13 year old Bruno Mars song.
Eve 6. Late period
Eve 6.
18 is longer than that.
Can you conjure any specifics
of what makes a disappointing area loop?
So I
think, and I don't
mean to put this on blast, but
world discovery,
Epcot,
all of the stuff that used to be future world,
they made this big deal about this
composer named I think
Pinar Toprak.
I don't know how to pronounce it.
But she composed this
new loop for that area.
And I went day
one to hear it. And I
was so excited. I was like, you got big
shoes to fill, Pinar.
Which we'll probably talk about later.
But as I got there,
it's very
beautiful. The music is very
very beautiful and pleasant to listen to.
But there's no
it took me a while
and I finally found a melody that I can kind of
cling to, but I couldn't sing it to you right now.
And that drives me a little bit
crazy because there's a recurring melody
in this like Epcot, this new Epcot
loop. And
when you're hearing it over and over again, you're like, oh yes,
that's the melody
is this soaring, beautiful, very
no complaints about it. But
like I can, it's not memorable.
And I think that there are
I think that a singable
I think about a lot about singable
solos and like singable
singable instrumentals
like you should be able to
remember the melody and be
able to sing it. Yes. As an
aficionado of 70s, 80s jazz, which we
touched on here. I can't remember
what the name is or it'll come up in a mix
and I don't even remember who the artist is.
But if I can
like do the basic melody that
at least is the starting point, that's something.
If it's just pure noodle,
then like it's probably not going to stick with you. It's kind of true of
film scores too.
Is that at the very
entrance of Epcot?
It plays all throughout
what used to be Future World as far as I
can tell. Like where Walt's sitting on the
stoop. Yeah. I feel like people
were kind of mixed
on that when it debuted.
Yeah. I feel like
and maybe they were like
pulling it back or like they put in
classic stuff or mixed it up
or... Every time I've been there
recently, it's been playing.
And I've gotten used to it. It just
it's generically beautiful.
Whereas I think that the music
that was there before had some
serious character.
Yes. Instantly memorable.
I think that'll come up for both of us.
Where I might admit, this is a little
goofy. What you're
listening to here is a little bit
like your first... Yeah, yeah.
Not that kind of goofy, but
it's a related kind of goofy.
But the like I might go
like it's like
cheesy, right? But then it like you
do remember it. It's like not
afraid to be cheesy, which I always
admire. Right. Instead of just sounding like
every inspirational
section, like
inspirational film score
for every movie that's come out. Like
I don't need that in my area loops.
They use... Disney's been using
they've been compiling these ones
that are compilations of film score songs.
The American President song? I do like
that. That's a good one.
I like it too.
I just wonder if
that's what you meant. But yeah, that's a little
bit I think where it started because people love that
Soarin' Loop, which is not on
my list. I like it. It's pleasant. But
I think they took that and ran with it. And I think they started
only using music that they have
license to because they use the same
damn Saving Mr. Bank's track
in Sook.
And it is nice to
listen to, but it's not...
Right. When they were willing to
pay for the music from a movie they don't
own, it ends up
feeling like Disney, even though
it's not owned by Disney. It's worth paying
for.
Mike, do you want to play more to not
get out of your zone too much?
We've realized this episode's going to be
three to ten hours long.
I was going to shout out
Frontierland, but
we know what it's like. I was going to play a little
Buffalo Gals for Jason, but
let's not do it.
He's fucking champing
at the bit.
You're not going to play it.
And this
is from Cars Land.
No, this is from Frontierland.
We know Buffalo Gals in Cars Land?
It's the dusty
west. It would make sense there.
But I just...
There are a lot of songs played
in Frontierland. We met Davy
Crockett and all these different things.
But it really...I don't know.
As I've said, I like Hillbilly Nonsense the older
I get. And part of it's from
Wilco, but part of a lot of it is from
going to Disney. Any theme park,
you know, Knott's Berry Farm,
you need an old west town.
That is sort of part of it.
And little small things we've gone
to over the years.
Do you understand why there's a straight line between
Wilco and the music
that Mike increasingly listens to, which is
like, oh, dangle, dangle, banjo!
I'm gonna have a hold on that!
Bob Wills and his Texas Playboys.
Yeah, I think there's some
early Wilco tracks and then
I think, is it
the most recent Wilco album?
Cruel Country you're talking about?
Is it the second to last?
That's the one with the song about a skunk
that gets stuck in a barrel?
I've never
googled something faster.
I wish there was one like that.
They started as an alt country band.
I would say they still are there.
AM.
AM is the big alt country.
More, yeah.
Appearing there, though, maybe has a little more
because it is like Forget the Flowers and stuff.
That's true. A little more, yeah.
It's a little more acoustic country like what you just
played. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's a little country of B&L as well.
That's right. So I get a little of it in there.
They experimented.
But then going into like Frontierland and all
these different places over the years, you hear
all this in the background.
Critter Country had a really good loop.
The Splash Mountain Q. I remember I used to
listen to that a lot.
I don't listen to it anymore.
That's good. Those are the rules.
Except for sometimes
when I...
That's when you do that
Russell Brand voice again.
Then you can admit that.
It's like bluegrass
standards.
In some cases, I think,
does Frontierland have any...
It's all times of the era, I think.
They don't have any like...
You don't get eye-to-eye bluegrass
version. No, I don't believe so.
That would be pretty good and that's probably
coming. Well, Frontierland's
going away, I assume, in the next
10 years, too. So we'll see.
Or in the...
Whatever in Disney World, there's going to
be no river there. I assume the
Hall of Presidents' days are numbered in the
next... But that's not Frontierland.
I guess that's not. But I feel like all of that
is going to just turn into IP land.
They paved paradise and they put up
a parking lot.
I think the idea of
Frontierland has been on the table for going
away, in general.
Do you think they don't at least leave up the
four stores in Country Bear Jamboree?
Maybe. I mean, maybe they...
Country Bears is just a little
section there. I don't know. I don't know what it
looks like in Florida, especially, because of what
Cars does to that whole area.
I must say, I am excited about that.
And the music of Cars Land is
good and maybe... And it's not
dissimilar to this, as well. Cars Land
in California.
Well, do you have some Cars Land that you wanted to?
I do, but not
the stuff I'm talking about. I'm talking
about Halloween Cars Land Overland.
Oh, right. I forgot.
I love
California Adventure at Halloween.
The purple lights, I say it
every other episode, the purple lights
by the Carthay is really great, but Cars
Land itself, during Halloween,
is my favorite. And they have a
full... We did
an episode last year about
different Halloween songs.
So they do play Monster Mash, they play
Love Potion No. 9, but they play stuff that I had
not heard until I went to
Cars Land.
So they have, like... This is a genre
that you wish that there were,
you know, there was a year's
worth of music that is songs about
ghosts and zombies. That's correct.
I do wish that.
But they've got other
Bobby Boris Pickett songs, like Scully
Gully.
Just slightly less good versions
of the Monster Mash.
That's all I want.
Well, and slightly less good versions of the song
Hully Gully. Well, sure, yes.
Wait a minute.
So it's Scully with a K.
I think so, yeah.
The song Hully Gully, I only sort of know.
It's that, but about skulls.
So there's that.
There's Buck Owens doing Monster's
Holiday.
Didn't we listen to Monster's Holiday?
Not this
version. This is Buck Owens doing it.
Oh, hell yeah.
And I don't think
it's the same song. It's just
another song called Monster's Holiday.
Taking it easy.
It is similar to it.
Get more
into this. It's good.
It's better than Scully Gully.
Monster's Holiday.
Different Monster's Holiday.
This is just fun.
Fun music to
look at your friends, Tomator and
Lightning McQueen and their Halloween
costumes. Yes. Have you been
during Halloween? I have, but I don't
remember there being a special loop.
Really? Yeah, well
I should say I've been when
Haunted Mansion Holiday is going, but that could
be like when I go tomorrow.
Oh, that could be too early.
Halloween in May.
So maybe I haven't seen this, but this is
great. But I think
what is important with loops when it comes to
like, I'll call this a pop song,
a rock song, is if you can
get stuff that people aren't that familiar
with, it can then make you still feel
like, oh, I'm in a different place. Obviously
it sounds like stuff I've heard before.
But I think that's part of
some of the loops. If you can find like obscure
stuff. Yeah, and things where you feel like
you can only hear it in this place. As with
characters we love because you only meet them in this certain ride.
It might pull you out of it
if it's music you associate too much with.
Yes. So then you know it's not in a park.
So I like that about it because there's a full
hour long loop and most of the stuff
I don't think is common Halloween
stuff. But it evokes
the imagery of Halloween
costumed cars.
Yes. With eyes. And it's similar
to the music they play during
the day. Tires that are turned into
moaning faces of the dam. Yes.
I do.
That's worth an episode.
This haunt cast season.
Halloween.
Is it called Halloween? Yeah,
I believe so. And then some of them are dressed, the cars
are dressed as Pixar characters as well.
But the lights in there
are really fun. Like that is a
nice hang during Halloween.
The cars are dressed as Pixar
characters? At the very least there's posters
where they're dressed like Woody and Buzz.
Yes. Or is it like
car parodies of Hocus Pocus
or something? I know I've taken photos
of these and I don't remember what they are.
There might be a Christmas too.
Is it like
old Doc starring
in a parody of the Santa Claus?
What are they? I want the
Cheech Marin car
to be dressed as like Frankenstein.
I don't want him dressed as Wally.
Well Luigi and Guido could
easily do the Monster
Saint guys. That's fun.
Someone's a vampire
every year? Mater's usually
the vampire. He's purple and he's
got the cape and stuff and the fangs.
It'd be cute if Mater and Lightning Queen
dressed up as each other.
Sure. I think that's
Texas. After everything they've
been through? After the twists and turns of that
friendship? Yeah, that'd be the ultimate sign
that they get along. Yeah, they actually are
the cars. Here are the cars.
This is from a couple years ago. Maybe they haven't done this in recent years.
But like here's some cars
dressed as Woody and Buzz. So the cars
know...
Well yeah, because this is established in the
credits of Cars 1 because they all go
to see drive-in movies that are
car versions of Toy Story, Bugs Life
and one of the other
ones, Monsters Inc. I don't know. And then the
truck that's voiced by John Ratzenberger
points out that they reuse the same
voice actors all the time. That's fun.
You can't complain about that.
I like that truck. Yeah.
It's a good truck. Got a toy of that truck in the house.
So never mind when that comes out.
I have a couple, I think, of the cars
when they sold the Cars toys
where they were all Star Wars characters.
Oh yeah. And I think Luigi
and Guido might be R2D2
and say 3PO?
If they're not, they'd really drop the ball.
Yeah. I mean
unless they're dressed like Jar Jar
and Boss Nas. That's the
other big Star Wars duo.
That would be really good. I have that stitch that's
General Grievous from the old days.
Is that true? Yeah, yeah.
I have a stitch toy. Does he have all the arms?
Because he has multiple arms. Yeah.
He has four lightsabers.
That's on the highest show.
That's on the, like
that's a daddy toy. Yeah.
It's in a box somewhere. If Bobby
Boris Pickett was a car,
what kind of car, what do you picture?
Oh, oh.
Like if a car was singing that beautiful song
we just heard. Gully Gully?
I don't know old cars
well enough. I know, it's really a bad idea.
I mean is it obvious to say a
hearse? But a classic old hearse.
Probably a hearse, yeah.
A Studebaker?
The rest of the year, a Packard,
the rest of the year is a very long, very wide
car. That's why I know
about old cars, long and wide.
This is why we gotta get Jay Leno on the show
to teach us more about old cars.
But as always, recording in the
Burbank area, he may crash into the walls
at any time.
You can find those two, Frontierland
and the Cars Land Halloween
playlist on Spotify, but then they have
them on YouTube. We should just link to all these
and throw them in the show. Our little special ones.
Is there more that you want to play?
No, we should move on. There's just so much
to get to. But those are just
great little shout outs.
I'm gonna have that Buck Owens in my head for sure.
We have passed
the auxed Kevin.
Kevin, very excited to dig into
it. It must have been tough.
You picked this episode topic and then how do you
narrow down a favorite
within hundreds? It was painful
for sure to do that.
With some back and forth because I thought you said one
and then the answer changed too. Yeah.
I said one. What I said was the Wonders of
Life loop. Which is
not ultimately what I picked, but
for anybody wanting to get
wanting a primer of like
new age music from about
1990, 1991
ish, Wonders of Life is really
great. It's got this great
San Diego group
called Check Field on there.
That's just a great mix of like sort of
earthy sounds with jazz.
There on that we've got
Ray Lynch who is this sort of
strange computer music
synth wizard
sort of guy and he made very, very fun
slightly haunting
computery music. Like it's all on there.
He did something called Celestial Soda Pop.
Celestial Soda Pop. Right. Which
I kept thinking about when I was in Celestial
Park drinking their special soda pop. Of course.
Oh wow. He invented the
idea of Celestial Soda Pop. I guess so.
Yeah so Wonders of Life
is a really great loop and like I've gotten
really obsessed with it and sort of
took all of the artists on that and
started wandering down the rabbit holes.
And that's how my
playlist that I've shared with you Scott
Liminal Oasis started is that I just started
taking the artists on the Wonders of Life
loop and started going down rabbit holes
of albums and finding more
music that sounds like that until I have
hundreds of hours of this. Which what a way
that's in terms of that like do we like
this cause of theme parser? Do we like it on its own?
That's a great way to figure it out is to like
okay so something about this is taking me
back to Epcot Center in the mid 90s
or whatever but like that there's more
of that it's that vibe but it wasn't
specifically played there. Right. And you're describing
a playlist. Are you willing to let the
listeners in into the world of Liminal Oasis?
Of course. I consider this one of the crowning
achievements of my life.
Well I mean and understandably because the stats
are so good. I think I can pull
it up on spot. This is a
this is a hundred
and sixty six hours. Good God.
Wow. Yeah basically.
Liminal Oasis with a bunch
of like odd symbols on both sides.
It's great art. A great like
electric prism in the
cosmos. This is
a wonderful playlist that you've made and
as the playlist that I will play
I feel like you kind of like it sort of
holds your hand from the like
maybe barely more accessible
worlds of smooth
70s 80s jazz. Yeah. Into
the confusing intimidating
world of new age music.
It's not intimidating Scott.
It was for me. I think
I in my head I'm like no
adults in the 2020s
should be listening to 1990s
new age music. This is a
way till this is a one way ticket to
being unrelatable to your fellow man.
And I assumed I think a degree
of cheesy or cheesiness
that maybe as I've started to like
wade into the waters I'll go you know
well that's not so cheesy. Oh that's
not so cheesy at all. This I like.
This I kind of like. I think embracing the fact
that a lot of this music is cheesy
and you wouldn't necessarily want
I don't know the
girl you have a crush on in high school to hear
you listening to it if you were like on the school bus
or whatever. Yes. No it's the music
you dive into with somebody you're
deep into a marriage with who you
trust. Who has no way out.
Who's trapped.
Or in our case musically where Aaron
and I I think have like a you know
mutually assured destruction
like we both just go we push each
other deeper and deeper into
the land of cheese to where like
we don't consider it any of it. Any of it
cheesy anymore. It's not good
first make out music but it's good
like settled make out music.
I thought you were going to say second make out music.
Oh well you know
if you're really high on the hog you know.
Look it's not as good as Buffalo Gals
but it's pretty good.
Chattanooga choo choo usually.
That gets them cooking.
Do you want to come over?
I got some great tunes
ready to go. Shuffle off to Buffalo
is next that's right.
If you want to come over and have a good laugh about
begin the beguine.
When I was in fifth grade I had a crush
on this girl and we went on a school
field trip and I specifically brought
the mighty mighty boss tones.
Let's face it CD so that she could listen
to it and she would maybe think
oh this is a type of music I've never heard before.
How does she like royal oil?
She didn't care
for it very much but on that same trip
the one and only time I ever won anything from
the crane game I won it for her.
A little vampire
but then she didn't like the mighty mighty boss tones
CD. Anyway so she's out.
Hit the bricks. And let's face it I don't
let's face it that's the name of the album.
I didn't mean to do that but let's face it
she probably wouldn't like the wonders of life loop either.
Well it's important to know early then.
You have a vast
collection of new age
cassette tapes. Yeah good memory.
And that all stemmed from like one Christmas
Eve I was in my childhood bedroom
and I was like kind of
trying to get sleepy. I was listening to some
area loops but then I got really hopped up
thinking about all the artists
and albums that comprise like
these area loops and I was like I gotta
like start saving those on Spotify
but none of them were on Spotify.
There are some but a lot of them
if you want to hear the full thing
you need you can't.
Some of them aren't even on YouTube
so I just went on eBay and I started buying
cassettes on Christmas Eve
and within like
an hour
I think I had spent like $200
on like 90's new age cassettes.
Oh my god.
That really speaks to the obscurity
of it. That it has not only not made
the Spotify transition but that
cassette becomes the primary
way to experience this music.
You can get them on CD. But you wanted
it. I wanted it and I don't do vinyl. I didn't do
any physical media really for music
until these cassettes and I still
really only have like new age and smooth jazz
cassettes.
It's good for physical media because of
the photo art of some of these people.
I think you get a kick
out of looking at the images of most
of these artists.
All this to say the Wonders of Life
loop is great and if you want a primer on
good music like that just start digging
into these artists.
To that end I refresh my memory about
it and getting comfortable with new
age stuff. I was just listening to it not
looking at artists and there was one that was like
this one's really doing it for me.
This is hidden.
Who we got here? Who is this?
Look it up. Yanni.
I was just
digging a Yanni track without even
realizing it.
That's a number called Looking Glass by Yanni.
If you think Yanni
looks crazy, if listeners
even remember Yanni, a staple of
TBS music, one of the most
beautifully haired, beautifully
mustachioed men,
beautifully puffy shirted men ever to live,
I feel like
you get deeper into this genre and Yanni
just looks like a normal guy on the street.
He is kind of a hunk but Yanni
looks cool compared to
somebody that I'm about to talk to
with. So Wonders of Life was not my
pick but the Innoventions
loop was.
And then we're talking
when Innoventions opens in 94,
this is the music when Innoventions is
new on the scene, when Epcot is
entering a new era of futurism.
That's right.
I'll give you a hit of it because there's multiple
different movements and maybe we can
maybe we can
find, yeah here's a track list
so it sort of starts off
with this track.
There's a whole story with this and I
kind of learned it.
We gotta get the main melody here.
So good. This is David Arkenstone
with a track called Papillon
on the Wings of the Butterfly.
This is, if you had like
Chet GPT, please
create the name of
a new age music artist and the kind of
song title that they would do.
And now create an image of that
artist and it is exactly David
Arkenstone. I love
this track so much. I wonder
if listeners of a certain era, like
does it take you
to original Innoventions, to what
we've lost?
It starts to get a little more
interesting.
Yes, and this is, so this is
an interesting loop because this is
not an original piece of music
made by a Disney Imagineer.
But the composer's name is
Russell Brower at Disney
Imagineering and he took
a bunch of songs apparently to
the committee of Imagineers
and one of them was
David Arkenstone's Papillon on the Wings of the Butterfly
and he had them pick
which song
they liked best for the tone of
the Innoventions area. So he would know
which way to go with his own music?
That's right and so
as a springboard
Papillon on the Wings of the Butterfly
B-Gat
Future World theme. Let's hope this is
where this loop goes.
Here we go.
This is...
I am ready
to learn.
I'm ready to learn about the internet.
I'm ready to not meet
Cinderella today. I'm here
to get my mind expanded.
Yeah, you're here to meet Vector Man.
Here to meet
Sega Genesis classic
Vector. Toejam and Earl
Toejam and Earl.
Walk around Toejam and Earl.
Oh man, that'd be something.
There was walk around
Crash Bandicoot at Universal
from last year.
He hung out in the courtyard.
When I talk about singable
melodies that you remember
this is one of the most
this is a perfect
melody. You don't hear
this stuff that much
these days. But
it's just an interesting collection of notes.
I wish I knew more about music
theory but really I just think it's like
it conveys the optimism
of future world
and invention and
innovation together.
It would work in a museum too.
It's stirring.
It reaches out to
kids. Instead of
this is stuffy and boring
even the best piece of classical music
might make you feel like
this is work I have to do today. But this
is kind of like
it's building you.
It's like making you anticipate
what's coming today.
Correct me if I'm wrong because this
may be a stupid thing as I express it.
It's so era specific
too that it has
the vibe of something that is like
inspiring and you're about to go
exploring. You're about to go on an adventure
as well. But because it is
tied to such a specific era
it just can't
help but be like
so stimulating for men of a certain
age.
Do you find it stimulating, Michael?
Yeah, absolutely.
It just feels so specific
due to an era.
It reminds me of
it could also be the introduction
to a VHS that you would watch
in science class.
It's not that I remember this from being a kid
but I just feel like it makes me feel like
being a kid.
For whatever thing it is
whether it be a video game, whether it be a VHS
and I feel like this
is not just millennial
nostalgia. I feel like this
could pop off on TikTok.
Yeah!
You could sample it, you could slow it down
and you could do a lot with this.
Let's do that really quick.
Oh boy.
Let's hear what it sounds like.
I remember in like 2021
22 as Disney
phased
reopening stuff and finally
starting going on their Epcot reopening
and there was a post
either on the
Imagineer account on Instagram
or Daddy Tomorrow's account
and it was talking about
different glass
for like the shop
reflecting rainbow or lights
and I was like
this is what we're getting instead of
we're losing the
inventions music but we're getting
different
oh it's
in the
range of it's over we're back
that was a real it's over
definitely and yeah
this also
played in mouse gear
oh right
store mouse gear in that area
but Innoventions and Mouse Gear I think
opened at the same time
I don't know what was playing
in this place but all I know is
I hear this and I can
go straight to the old electric umbrella
I'm in electric
umbrella as I listen to this
I never spent too much time
there I think I popped in
before it was gone I got to see it
before it flickered away
I don't remember what the food was like
but I know that the phrase electric
umbrella fills me with optimism
this in general this all just makes
this is like the 21st century
is coming it's going to be
beautiful and wonderful and magical
not a whole bunch of dog shit
that gets worse and worse
well Scott unfortunately the future turned out
to be a lot of
bland minimalist bullshit
that's already out of style
outside of generic apartments
with white walls and great floors
which I say as someone who
lives in an apartment with white
walls and great floors
no but doesn't this take you like this is
in the future in a mirror
right now it's only an Epcot Center
but soon everywhere I turn
there will be electric umbrellas
whatever that means
people holding them in stores
as shade out in the world
the world will be electric umbrellas
each more purple than the last
I slowed it down by the way
oh you didn't even know
it worked so well
wait let's listen
now I hear it slow down
took Quaaludes
live remixes
this is great thank you for this
I don't really like it this way
I like it better normal
there was a moment probably many years ago
at this point where I felt like
there's a lot of like video game mixes
too like any sort of like ambient loop
thing I do like that a lot now but you can get
like really like 8 bit mixes
of whatever red hot chili there's like
the sound prof
what do you call them sound
sound font thank you of Donkey Kong
Country but it's Californication
I do like that
it's like the weird
that's been done for the Beach Boys Love You
oh I believe that
possibly the last Beach Boys album
so there's all these different kinds of loops and stuff
and then whenever it was they started
so much video game music started being posted
I always loved all the Mario
music and all the Nintendo music but then
you would get these loops of them and you'd
start realizing oh this isn't just a fun
little piece of music that I liked
these are like really genius
level things that you can sometimes
just because of the old school
sound of it the 8 bit sound of it
you're like you don't necessarily notice how
cool it is
it didn't have to be whatever the music
and NBA Jam didn't have to be
like so great and memorable
but you feel like people
caring all across the board
in these video games in the parks
it felt like you know like a little
content opportunity opened up and
people filled it with love and with
cool keyboard sounds
now you get like orchestra
performances of Nintendo
stuff and then you go holy
shit Super Mario World music is
amazing those in particular
these songs are I never even
I always like these and these are so hummable but
I would love to hear that song
in different styles too
I was just thinking about this
recently well I was thinking
about this episode like if somebody
did a like if Russell
Brower himself
I don't know hosted or what do you call
conducted a the orchestra
playing here I assume I assume
this is actually an orchestra not
just synth it sounds pretty real
with a little bit of synth in there too
but I could be wrong but if he
did like something at
say the Dr. Phillips Center in
Orlando Florida if he had a
live show where he just played
the interventions loop
I would probably
I would probably get emotional it like feels
impossible now but the fact also
but then like ten years ago you if you
if you'd been told there's going to be
a like massive cult
fandom of the track
aquatic ambiance from Donkey Kong
Country like this will be played
emotionally at festivals and people
will be close to this like this is
why we have to do we have to like spread
this fandom and get it out like like
no Disney there's even more layers
of cult fandom within your upper
then you even do you have to serve this now
you have to do an orchestral Russell Brower
concert yeah apparently he
wasn't even going to have music for this
area because a executive
I listen to an interview about this but the
executive gave him a little guff about it
was like that's a that's a thoroughfare
nobody's going to stop there they don't need music
they can just go to the fountain if they want music
but he advocated for the
grandparents and the parents who
are waiting for their children to meet them at a
central location he said you don't want them
to sit in silence this needs
music yeah
oh it's like inclusive it's
great and now everywhere you go
at a Disney park I don't think you would be
able to find like a silent section
yeah and that wasn't always the case
I don't think yeah yeah
interesting um you know it's a big area with all this
too where the hell is all this music coming
from you know sometimes you can see the speakers
but sometimes you really
can't in a lot of cases you
can't Kevin we were in Orlando
we had a great evening at Wilderness Lodge
where I had never been you showed me
all the all the great nooks and crannies
and at one point when we
were on our way what is the the train building
where is that like the DVC
where all of Walt's train stuff
is the Carol Wood
room the Carol
Wood room we were on like a little like
covered bridge essentially to the
Carol Wood room and then noting
how loud all of the like the
the cricket chirping was and then
we went wait a minute yeah is this manufactured
and from where
and then we looked up and there have been speakers
so hidden we didn't even they were above
us the whole time and that's how I feel
in a lot of these places like where
is the music coming that's
like an incredible underrated part of
I'd say particularly Disney parks
but you know but all parks yeah maybe
that's an episode where we like go through Disneyland
and try to find all the speakers
speaker hunts
sometimes you just find like because
I know you sent videos of just things like
you like this piece of music and then it's just playing
off of like a little pod in a planter
and that's fine you can do that
there's a charm to that too
sometimes a barely visible speakers
fun but an invisible speaker
what a magic trick yeah that's
really cool and I get something sounding good
from a source you cannot see
that's wild we did
determine that those crickets were in fact
being pumped in yeah yes
but we completely but I mean we
noted it I guess eventually
but it was realistic enough that we had the question
Wilderness Lodge has a great loop by the way
I didn't highlight it here because it's sort of just
generic soaring
inspiring nature
National Parks, John Muir
Spirit of America but I yeah
I don't think any of what we're talking about
is hotels
and there's a lot of
some of them really are like
you know Resort gets a title
like Saratoga Springs and you're like
how do you score that what is the music of
Saratoga Springs these people they always figure
out as it turns out the Saratoga Springs
loop I think is mostly just sort of
like the type of music
I think you have dubbed or maybe your wife has
dubbed crap jazz crap jazz
yes yeah yeah
re-orchestrations of camp
town races like jazzy
you need to be in charge of this
of that sound track
it's more just like weather channel music
which of course I like but it's not
it's not for everyone I know the line
between like because it's something I will play
I don't consider crap jazz there's
there is music there's definitely
instrumental music in the Disney parks that we
called crap jazz but we that is a
loving term on our part actually
I think maybe we declared this is a little
cheesy it's a little bit like it's when things
stop sounding as good maybe in like 2000
or so yeah you don't have like inherently
cool production techniques as
with 80s 90s stuff
but then the more time you spend
in DCA wine area
you're like I kind of love the crap jazz
I'm very fond of the crap jazz
I know I like it too I don't consider crap an insult
anymore I like all of it
doesn't matter I have that great Californian
hotel oh I love
any piece of music yeah yeah yeah yeah absolutely
what else you got
do you got other stuff from that or do you
I have just a snippet of something else but I will end the
interventions loop talk by saying this is my goat
100% greatest of all
time for me Russell Brow
who went on to do a lot of World of Warcraft
so did David Arkenstone
wow wow
so Disney this initial
playground for composers
who have gone on to do things that are like
you know a little bit more mainstream
yeah and Arkenstone wasn't involved with Disney
Arkenstone was just a guy that
Russell Brower liked the music of
and then the Imagineers were like
no we like that one keep that
beginning in there right around it
no please we like Papillon
I just want to say the title here
no wait we really like Papillon on the wings of the butterfly
off the album in the wake of the wind
which I have it comes with a map
whoa
a fictional land Jason I
don't know I really don't know
Lord of Entry shit
that album cover if we're
thinking of the same one look it up that's
an aesthetic that I would call a really specific
early 90's micro aesthetic which is
Columbus core this is
when we were going Columbus
crazy for the 500th
anniversary of
1492 when there were
multiple Columbus films I think one
with a Vangelis score yeah
who factors into there's some Vangelis in some
of these some of these things
but yeah he was like Jason
this album gives you a little bit more
Columbus magic if that's what you're
after I feel like
because we got rid of Columbus for a while and I feel
like there was some horrible White House thing
today it was like Columbus is back yeah
I feel like I saw that literally today that's not
what I'm saying I don't agree you're saying
that I'm just saying it's funny I think it's more today
I think when I say Columbus core
I actually think more of
Port of Entry or so like oh sure
imagine setting sail like
imagine like a good person
who's taken a bunch of ships across
the world like not a pirate but
perhaps a merchant yes merchant
yes they're off to find nice
spices this is a cover for
one of my beloved Ninja Turtles adventures
comics is
in stone
1492 on Donatello's back
Columbus
mania really why is that happening
I don't remember
I just remember the cover after
you said that going like Columbus isn't that well this is
January 1993
oh 1992 was
five hundred okay yes
yes so there's they were like
somewhere in storm near the Caribbean
Sea that's what the
place to find the turtles
did I interrupt though
no all I was going to say is like
if I was making
I every once in a while make a list of like my
favorite albums of all time and
loops are not
loop is not album but
if it was if you consider the interventions
loop an album I think
it would be up
there in my top ten in your
personal world all you need to do is the magic
of a CD burning kiosk
oh yeah and then it becomes an album
every loop can be album
with CD burn you actually
have a rank like would it be like between seven
like would you have a number in your head where
it would be or just your thinking would be in the ten
one no I don't know
I mean like I guess an easier way
to phrase is like if I had ten desert
island albums yeah to
you know what I mean to take with me I think this
would be I would probably take a
there would be a Beatles album on there but this would kick
a lot of Beatles albums off of there
like I wouldn't be like sorry
it might bump a few what's the best one
it bumps yeah maybe that yeah like
I kind of I remember Sergeant Pepper well enough that's fine
yeah I don't know
but Sergeant Pepper's gotta go
yeah and it would serve as a
reminder of great
memories in the parks while I was on my desert
island well sure hey 45 minutes
to an hour though you're pushing that CD
how much audio that CD
that's true yeah no no no a burnable
CD has 70 minutes I
know because I believe that's the number
or something around there and I know this
because I burn my dad a CD
of instrumental surf music
for his birthday for Christmas and
for Father's Day he makes me a track
list that he writes out on a legal pad
and he gives me a fun idea of a
surf cover and title that it should
have and then I go ripping tracks
on YouTube and I have to get out
an old laptop that I only keep because
it has the ability to burn CDs
and I make him a surf I just did it
the other day for his for his birthday
I have like a $15 external
like USB-C
the old external wow wow
I had to burn a DVD of my
I had to rip a DVD
of my friend's
sister's bat mitzvah
from like 1998 or something
the other day that's a real mystery ripping
a DVD that's a like
that's like Apollo 13 like we need to
make all this shit fit into this
handbrake remember handbrake
forever wow
VLC is that the program?
VLC failed me
VLC can play an old DVD
sometimes though it can rip things
I think I could have ripped it with VLC
but I had to download handbrake
well and then you have to go like does it need to be
playable or is it a data disc
because a data disc can hold a lot
oh that's like 800 megs I think
yeah yeah you gotta choose
is it the 70 minutes or the 800
megs anyway it was touch and go
maybe my super drive ate the DVD at one point
anyway I'm glad that we're just on
YouTube now like we don't need to
so people these these pioneers who've done
all this work for us and posted it God bless you
if you've ever posted one of these loops
and something to
all listeners out there as you say
Desert Island Discs and number one maybe it
goes to that saying please in comments
or social media or wherever you interact with
the show let us know your favorite
theme park area loop out there
so we can highlight it in future
episodes as we
you know do this explore this area
more yeah this might need a part two
maybe so maybe so one last thing
international spotlight de Efteling in the Netherlands
oh yeah one of the only
parks that I've been to that
isn't Disney or Universal that has really
great music this is
off of this is the loop for
their castle trackless
dark ride Symbolica which
the characters go Symbolica
that is an incredible looking ride follows the magical journeys
of the magical jester Pardosh
and this is the sound of it
I think we did an episode and said that name completely
not that way I guarantee
this name is
Pardwitz
it really
gets cooking
this is an hour long
this reminds me of Mario Odyssey
yeah
isn't that nice
but it kind of goes through
variations on that theme
throughout and it's wow
that's something for like
purely made for a theme park that's beautiful
I've been clamoring to get back to Efteling
because it's a very strange park with
kind of strange music oh wow yeah
I'd love to go in general alright well Kevin
I'm staying in a similar neck of the woods
to you which makes sense because I feel like
our first contact I don't know if it was
if you talked to me first or
you just emailed the podcast
that's a good question I don't know either
it could have been that
but I
I know that the first you and I talked
was that you know that I had floated
every once in a while
I will bring up the kind of very
relaxing 70s 80s smooth jazz
that I'm very passionate about that
makes me a more relaxed person
day to day as I often say
I don't need to smoke cigarettes because I listen
to music like this and it really
brings me down a notch especially
when a project is
insane or whatever but you know
I'll drop a Bob James or
a Dave Gruessen or a Lee Rittenhour
and you reached out
and I think sensing a
kindred musical spirit
and said do you know that there's
this playlist of all of the music
that would play at the contemporary
in the lobby in
the early 90s that's right I
emailed I remember I emailed it
that might have been like two general podcasts
the ride at Gmail an email that we
sometimes check I'm sorry
I know this was this was in a time
where we might check it a little more thoroughly
but yours cut through
because like why yes
yes I do and I took to that playlist
so quickly and that is not what
I'm talking about this that's
not what I chose although very well could
have been but that like
I I
appreciated that you were like okay
if he's like you must you must have been like I
don't hear it people reference this kind of music
in the wild ever right
I need to contact this person and make sure
he knows that there is a way to
feel at all times like you're in the lobby
of the contemporary that is a great
loop that has that has some
serious smooth stuff on yes
the ripping tins on it
oh my god ripping ripping tins
is that was really like you know I thought
that I didn't fuck with 90s
jazz and then the ripping
tins changed everything the ripping
tins are a group who have
all of their album covers
are this like have a
cat daddy
on them with like a big crazy
he's like sort of like a you know he's
like a joe camel who isn't
like you know
there isn't the toxic association
camel but he does
have the he is like a cool jazz
guy and he's got a fedora in sunglasses
definitely looks like a night owl
jazz cat
messy cat yeah not a
gross cat like a leisure suit larry cat
or yeah no he's
he's wonderful and you're not you told me not only about
like you made me aware of
more ripping of the the disney ripping
tins association but also there's a music
video where the ripping tins cat comes
to life oh yeah yep
that's an incredible piece for a tourist
in paradise they're probably their
closest thing they have to a single and
the cat I think is the voice of the part that's like
ba ba ba baby baby
that's one you can hum
da da da da da da
da da da it really is
if listener if you don't understand what this is
and why I like it I mean imagine
like I think the closest way I could
translate it is like do you
like the tailspin theme
and do you want a ton of instrumental music
that's like the tailspin theme so true
light tropical relaxation
early nineties five this cat
is a little lascivious yeah nowadays
it's a it's a long long smile
kind of a penis thing
here oh wow he's opening for the hard
oh god it's mike seeing his penises
again I mean this is there's no doubt about it
this is his arm and his finger
you know what I'm saying that's not their first album
look at a couple more variations on
the ripping tins cat some of
them don't know what I'm looking at there is
kind of a penis in the ripping tins cat
this is what mike does he ruins everything
by seeing his subliminal penises everywhere
by seeing the truth
I see the truth is what's happening here
is that this cat is a penis thing but you know what
this car is a big dick
this cat's driving a big dick car
no it's a long yellow limo
that's weekend in monaco that's good stuff
that's a killer that's yeah yeah
see for me mike I'm about the music
not about the subliminal penises
that in that case aren't on the cover
that's not a big long penis mike
I think that one is his yellow car
it's just a cool yellow car
but it's like kind of bent it's kind of like
limp it's like a little where's the penis
and curves ahead where he's skiing down a hill
is it the purple ski
is it because it's purple like a penis
isn't really
this one I don't know I don't know
sorry we're fresh from a big penises in everything
fight that maybe the listener hasn't
heard yet stay tuned to the second gate
you'll hear it soon enough
penis everywhere
that's my philosophy
alright I'm getting a little heated I gotta cool down
with some smooth jazz
so anyway that's what you reached out about that
shout out Kim Pencil
love all of Kim Pencil's shimmery piano
music that was always
available like Kim Pencil really
really blew my mind
P-E-N-S-Y-L
yes confusingly even though his albums
they're like a pencil pun in the album
pencil sketches
pencil sketches but it's spelled like his real name
P-E-N-S-Y-L
this is you know I like all this stuff too
I was listening to a lot of ambient music
kind of around the time
we were all like
listening to a lot of Japanese
city pop
also spotty on spotify
like there's
no almost none you gotta go to youtube
some stuff is on apple music
but some stuff yeah
but
ambient music I really
like having it on and having it on
in the background can't fall
asleep to it
I don't know it just starts to
have the reverse effect
of relaxing I don't know if
it's changes in movements
but sometimes it stresses
me out well listen what I'm
at some point in my
loop I'm going to play a
piece of music that is
definitely that I became even more familiar
with due to Kevin's Playlist Liminal Oasis
and what I'm going to play is a guaranteed
sleep aid
relaxer the B piece of
music of any I've ever
found that is a path
to the end of
an anxious night like I've never
found something that is more the key
and if boy if I could help anybody
with sleep anxiety out there if I
if this piece has the magic
that it has for me I would love
to be able to pass this along which I need to get
the link for that liminal oasis
playlist because too many people are
abusing the word liminal on spotify
and even searching
under playlists it's just
impossible I felt a little bad
using the word liminal
because I feel like I see it
used incorrectly or
overused but I hope that when people
listen to my playlist they deem it
worthy of the word no I'm sure you've done
the work on I'm sure you know it but
it fits are you
are you saying you're finding
count like counterfeit liminal
playlists a million playlists
with the word liminal in it okay
but it sounds like a cool
word but it doesn't actually like
Claire whereas I think you are this is
you are describing all music that could play
in a place that is somewhere between
being open and closed yes yeah
there's a lot of dead mall playlists
style playlists yeah
but you gotta you know look there's a lot of that
just sounds too modern or something like
I don't think they're really hitting the nail on the head with
some of that like it being it's not
because ball music isn't actually like
weird and scary like I like
vaporwave but that's not what actually plays
at a mall like Rippington's are what plays
at a mall this kind of music is what
plays at the mall I'm gonna start getting into this
this is
what I have chosen a close cousin
to interventions Tomorrowland
1989 to 2003
this is the music
from Magic Kingdom Tomorrowland
now I have a question about this
which is like is this really what was still
playing in the Buck Rogers
94 era it doesn't kind of doesn't seem
right to me it might be mislabeled well
I have some stuff like that
but also
the one website
that does a lot of
retro WDW
they have video from very early
Tomorrowland 94 like
it's not everything's open yet
and they're playing like that
music that plays
when the looney tunes go to a
factory oh really that's that
dun dun da da da da
da oh interesting and so
I don't know if that was just placeholder or what
on the people mover I don't want that
but I have no memory of that
no thank you I want the pure
relaxation of what I'm
gonna start playing here
so and this is I've referred to
this on the show before
this is not the actual name but I saw
YouTube comment refer to it as this
and I can never unhear it it's what
it is in my heart to me wherever
it played this might have been I think some
of this might have been in the Tokyo
Tomorrowland in this era as well
but what I will always know it as
is the bubble shuffle loop
and that is due to the first
track bubble shuffle by
Larry Carlton
here it comes
oh that little pad
it's like is it space
music I don't know maybe
not but I
like what it's doing to me
this is really the good stuff
did Larry Carlton play the solo
on Steely Dan's Kid Charlemagne
that is correct so Larry
yeah Larry Carlton I finally I have a show
sanctions excuse to talk about
Steely Dan Steely Dan solo he's one of
the great I mean all the greatest
guitarists of the era you know
tried to cut it with Dan and
not everybody could but he was one of the
best yeah he's
Kid Charlemagne he's
Don't Take Me Alive he's
Third World Man I think he's on
Josie many of
the greats but this is from a solo
album this is from a solo album
I think from 1989
called On Solid Ground
and
here's what's crazy about that yeah I think
it's from 89 and what we're
hearing is about as chill
as you could imagine
would you believe that midway
through the making of this album was a
heinous act of violence
that almost threatened Larry Carlton's
guitar playing career forever no
I didn't know this it doesn't square with what we're
listening to at all apparently he was literally
halfway through the album and he was gonna
pull an all-nighter and like get three more
tracks out get this thing
out into the public for their relaxation
purposes he goes outside
because he hears a weird sound like
what's going on in the neighborhood and
he's just randomly shot
just like a teenager who's maybe
trying to commit a robbery there or elsewhere
just like
startles him and he shoots
him try to square that with
this incredible solo as
all Larry Carlton solos are
hot yeah
like and literally and just it's crazy that
it was this album I never heard this about
this man but then
the album becomes half of it was
in the can but then it becomes
his like path
to recuperation and to like
yes I can play guitar again
because he halfway
through the album he wondered if he
like it affected him exactly in the
nerves where maybe he will never
play guitar again and he described
it as like he became a baby he had
to like learn how to even
hold the guitar and then within
six months because he's a
legend of all time he
not only figured it out he got maybe better
than he was before he
re-recorded some of the tracks because he thought
they didn't have the juice and now he's playing
like with the post-shooting aggression
he has stuff to like work out
feelings to work out about the horrible
thing that he went through
and then he gets this album
done proves that he is on solid
ground still musically
and lifestyle wise
and then he
does a benefit concert to
help other like
victims of random acts of violence
like let's raise money for people
where there is no specific like you don't know who
the assailant is or why or why it happened
he did a big concert raised a ton of money
got his pals Michael McDonald and
Joni Mitchell to come play because
he's also the guitar on Help Me
one of the biggest Joni Mitch so this is the
true legend this guy then he goes
and like does you know
ton more benefits for that raises a ton of
like this guy raised hundreds of thousands
of dollars for people
who were randomly attacked
and then his music sounds
this good and relaxing how about that
broadcast news and newspapers were
very obsessed with
quote random acts of violence
I feel like in the 90s
well he proves that it wasn't a fake
it was an actual
concern it happened to
we were almost robbed of
this piece of I don't know if this track
Bubble Shuffle was
done pre-shooting or post-shooting
but if it was post and if
this random guy almost robbed the world
of Bubble Shuffle and my favorite
Disney music loop
my god
no amount of jail could
be enough infinite life sentences
for that but
if that did happen you would at least
so Bubble Shuffle I agree is the
fulcrum of this Tomorrowland
loop right it is
it is a center piece
what a title incredible title this is what I would
very creatively call
a playlist
area loop where it's really just a playlist
of uh this is true
it is not it's not
composed I mean similar to
Wonders of Life I would say like like yeah
there is not always like a it's a little
bit more of like a little curated mix
yes and I
whoever was on
this task of curating
area loop playlists in
the late 80s
early 90s was
kicking ass at it
and they clearly just had a
I would love to know the full process was
it an Imagineer
I heard a small thing
from Imagineer
Eddie Soto
he's very on line yeah yeah he gives us
a lot of factoids yeah selecting
the music for Frontierland
and Main Street I found a
snippet about that
but I don't
know if is he the mastermind behind
the Wonders of Life and Tomorrowland
or was it like up to like who's
in charge of the land or what
or do they hire
like a music supervisor like
a movie would like somebody to pick the tracks
who's like because you need some you
know to find some of these that you know to find
Inside the Sky
by Steve Hahn you know
you need it's gotta be somebody
who knows like a hundred
thousand albums you're not just gonna chance
into these tracks I think some of
this stuff and Kevin I do have
to tell you when you said does so
and so play on the Steely Dan record
we should probably put a chapter marker there
because like half the audience gonna be
like pumping their fist and half
are gonna be like oh I'm gonna come back
later I'm gonna put on something
or who is this half
show yourselves name yourselves
but what I was gonna say
was like yes some of this stuff
statistically
some of this stuff has
to have been made by someone
going oh shit we needed that
yesterday yeah
who can we call who's a ringer
who can turn this around in
48 hours that's true
yeah no it might be yeah it could
be a rush job it could be somebody who was barely
paid or not at all I didn't
I don't know if I was like
15 or like 21 before
I realized you could make music
and not care about it is a
concept like music to me
felt like it was so important and it must
just be pouring from like the deepest
recesses of your mind
so the idea that like oh yeah people are on
maybe it was the Ben Fold song
One Down is that what it's called
about finishing his contract out
and finishing the song when I realized oh
this is a job
for some people now hang on we are not
there is I don't want
to hear it said I'm not saying that Larry Carlton
doesn't care I think I think you're describing
selecting the playlist well yeah
selecting the I found
I've mentioned this before
but there's a podcast
episode the unofficial Universal
Orlando podcast
the music of Marvel superhero
island with composer
Howard Drossin
and he is
like pretty up front
about this from 2016
and he's very up front
you're going to say that he's never gone to
Marvel superhero island right yes
you've told us we've heard this one before
you can't believe this
well he I just
less that he could have gone but more
that the anecdote of like I have
couple teenagers would they like it
and it's like yes there's a giant roller
coaster but just when he's
like yeah I think I have the mini the
original mini discs around
here somewhere with that music
this sticks in your groin
this is what I'm saying where you're
allowed him on hallowed ground you're 12 years
old and you're just like this must be
this man's passion project who
composed all this music he cares
so much about spider-man well but then
they sold the souvenir
CD with track by track
all the original music
I hate to tell you he didn't give a shit about Marvel
superhero island it was a gig
he jerked it off basically
this is Jason learning
for the first time that anyone doesn't give
a shit about Marvel superhero island I was
hoping you'd bring this part up
about the main what's his name say his name
Howard Drozin
hey Howard fuck you not caring
about Marvel at all
you warped this innocent young brain
I'm trying to give him his flowers
he doesn't deserve it he didn't put the passion
into that music that's what I think
people are booing because a steely Dan
guitarist was mentioned and then we're praising
Howard Drozin despite him
jizzing all over the most sacred
property in land
jizzing in a bad way
not to create life
that's what I'm saying
the only reason to jizz
do we like the Marvel
super sorry to interrupt the Tomorrowland
yes I do yes I like it
breaks his computer while saying it
yes that is the perfect music
but we do like it
I like it
in the context of Marvel superhero island
but I don't know that I like it
outside of that context yeah it's very
intense it's hard rock
yeah the hardest rock
but I don't know that it's
I don't know that it's like something I listen to otherwise
I don't know
Jason demanded that it be his wedding
march
brings the bluetooth speaker
it was the call to adventure
because why what greater
adventure is there than that of
matrimony
alright I'm going to
play a little bit more of this I don't have
to do a ton but I do just want to get a quick
hit of night fire dance
Andreas Wallenweider
wow you had it
that you know the artist
German heart declare
down to the moon
this is what I'm talking about these synth voicings
we're like not afraid to be a little cheesy
little mark mother's bow
yes a little penis playoffs
because they love this is the
it's a dangerous time synth wise
it's late 80's where people realize they can sample
a voice and then do
wah wah wah wah I am a voice
who is a keyboard
but there's a lot of love
Todd regerman a whole album that way which is wonderful
this whole album
is very fun
down to the moon yeah
kind of all sounds like this
if you like this always sounds like
lowrider to me
which probably was intentional
I love you also just
this genre of music names itself
perfectly the album down to the moon
the songs moon dance
steam forest
silver wheel steam forest
hush patients at bamboo forest
hush patients
this is pre ai
like nowadays chat gbt
would probably tell you all these
think of these names for you
this I feel like I gotta make it
to the weird little solo that comes
is it this
there's some change in this too
love this
wah wah wah I'm in the future
this is a wonderful future
that really feels video game
ish to me
it would score a level that like
is just like you're in a forest
but then something like glitches
there's like that
the very strange synth sound
what's the I can't think of anything today
on a midi keyboard where you push
the wheel up and down
the pitch bend thank you
it feels like that and it feels like you would score
a video game level where you're in a forest but then
some weird like color shoots
out of the ground or the screen glitches
or like there's something odd about this
forest hey mike I'm gonna give you a little
credit here I don't think anyone's gonna give you a tough
time for not remembering
what the wheel the tiny
wheel on a midi keyboard is called
Jason hates music stuff that's what we're finding
right now people are booing about stealing
people are booing about the pitch bend
what is this hate
I hate music I hate pitch bends
Jason has good taste in music
I appreciate what he was gonna say
but I bet there are people
that are going it's a god damn pitch wheel
it's easy
you were trying to make me feel better
but now I feel worse
there's a lot of people throwing their phones
at the wall like how do you not know
pitch bend
I think from what I've heard you might have the hippest
music taste of the host
I'm sorry
Jane has the
hippest music taste
Jane has the hippest
Jane can detect stuff
and knows all the songwriters
you don't have to give that to me
because I have no concerns about being hip
I gave it up a while ago
I learned the name Max Martin
last year
Max Martin was a hit maker of our time
well I knew the hits of our time
but I didn't know all the team behind it
are you into what's his name Benson Boone
is that his name the guy in the jumpsuit that sings
is he the back flipping guy
yeah
is it hip to be into Benson Boone
or is that just the most popular music
I prefer Bunsen Honeydew
I can get on with that
I'm not going to argue with that
Selena Gomez's fiance is
Benny Blanco
he's not Benson Boone
of his name I've been making for weeks
that's right no two different guys
well let me do another one of those
and say that the track that I now must play
this is not by
recent guest Paul Scheer
it is by Paul Spear
and David Lans
this is from the album Natural States
the track is Behind the Waterfall
this is what I referred to
as a go to sleep aid
this almost feels too
personal at this point to play
for you all and on the podcast
but we've discussed Behind the Waterfall
we've been Behind the Waterfall many times
the backside of water
wow it ties together
I don't think they're related
here we go
Scott your eyelids
they look like they're drooping
oh here comes Rem
sleep shakes
if we could all catch a quick two minutes
yeah that's fine we should be allowed
we do long episodes let's all just
close your eyes everyone
a little exercise my nose is a little stuffed up
so if I try to breathe through I'm sorry
it's the allergies
in California that I get
you gotta try Flonase
I heard about this Flonase
thing and I do think I should try it
don't I swear if you talk about CVS
kind of bullshit over my favorite track
it's probably where you get it though
if you can get a first catch up for
Flonase in Zartek it's cheaper than
UTC oh really
this song
really does have healing powers though
it's helping me ignore everything
that's being said right now Jason do you think
you could just get me that prescription
I don't want to feel like going into a doctor
this is me at night going like
I can't sleep I don't know what am I doing
I'm on a podcast where there's tangents about
CVS and people say things like
stinky urethra and that'll be
20 minutes of the episode
every week but you know what it's okay because
if I can calm down if I can calm down
oh and now a new
instrument is playing
I think this is a very tasteful
the call of the elk
I don't know it sounds like
you imagine
you imagine an elk walked up
that's the elk's voice
I said look I see
I see things when I hear music
what can I tell you
anything is valid anything that you feel in this natural
this is from the omnipresent
it's a new age
record label Nerada
and I was going to say
I think maybe whoever was curating these loops
maybe wasn't just going off
the whole world of music maybe they
knew Nerada and their imprint
Nerada Mystique
and also Windham Hill
or Nerada Equinox
which is what this is from
they had a Nerada Insider
and Nerada Milwaukee based
label
I assume this was like that their headquarters
were at the top of the Himalayas
Nerada is
was in Wisconsin
and I only
know this because on the cassettes for these
albums a lot of which I have the address is
on there and it's on like I think North Farwell
Street in Milwaukee where
is now a pizza
restaurant called Pizza Shuttle
wow all the world's new age
music came from the pizza shuttle
and I've been to pizza shuttle
many times
they have pinball machines there
what kind of pie are we talking about
I don't remember that
I can't remember
I'll let it
wrap up there
I highly recommend that
where in the park would you find that
that's still tomorrow
and that track was also
in Wonders of Life
that was shared between what was potentially yours
some of these did repeat
here and there there's not that many repeats
but I feel like they
picked the tracks the best tracks
to repeat behind the waterfall being in
multiple places do you think the
guy who knew Nerada
do you think he just spread
it like stretched it like
divvied it out really
like really stretched out his
billable hours
he didn't tell them right away about
the label Nerada I'll have to search far
and wide for music that fits these themes
I'll have to travel to lands
far and near
I imagine it will take me three months
with a musical sherpa
another three month contract
I believe is due
well they chose beautifully
I do have to thank for your playlist
here's what I'll do I'll go to your
playlist I'll start with that
that's the base and then I'll just let it
randomize take me somewhere else
in this liminal oasis and it really
and my like there's been bad sleep
anxiety for sure for the last five years or so this thing
this always does it I will say
I don't think it's I'm glad you're
having luck with it for sleep because it wasn't designed
for sleep necessarily
suddenly there will be like
some samba comes in
but I don't
hold that against you because it's not made for
sleep but a lot of it does work a lot of it
definitely does liminal sleep oasis would be
a good branch maybe I could start my
own Nerada mystique oh yeah
imprint of my of my playlist
you should be the new and oh and we should
say I mean that was the that was the inspiration
for your opening track
which I knew as soon as I heard it like
oh my god he this this
this motherfucker just David
Lansd our theme song
and I couldn't be more honored you know
you nerated us and I
I thank you for that happy happy
to do it there's a really good live video
of David Lansd and Paul Spear playing
that song oh and
I was surprised to see that I think
Paul Spear
cause David Lansd plays piano and he's playing
a synth I think it's like a DX
7 synth then I think Spear
is playing an acoustic electric
guitar
which is interesting and it's making a very nice
sound and they both
look I think they're wearing baggy sleeves
and probably some like crystals and then there's
a dude that
not David Lansd or Paul Spear there's a dude
just going
like hog wild on some bongos
so you gotta have that
the Rippingsons has one of the great
like pony tailed
gourd shakers
the guy with the big you gotta have a big
gourd with a net on it
and the beginning of the video is like
you know desert sands tour
or something
sold out show in Mexico
city and it's like this giant
like seemingly like amphitheater
arena and it really looks like
it's sold out so this must have been
semi big maybe it was a festival
or something but people were out there
for Lansd and Spear playing behind the waterfall
a lot
I am glad that is the case
are these guys still around?
David Lansd is
definitely I don't know if
he still makes music
that's such a good idea Mike
I don't know
are they more appropriate for
the garden rocks or eat to the beat
I don't know which event
or for just have them play live next to Walt
have them sit down next to
the sitting Walt cause that's where their music
belongs
you don't rock out the way you do to
you know Smash Mouth
with New Singer
that's what Eat to the Beat is for
they replaced poor Steve so god damn
fast
like they had a guy in mind
he like passed away and it was like
Smash Mouth is on the road
they were able to audition them very fast
cause the audition was just like
sing the word some
they needed all that
somebody just go some
they had a hallway
of people all tuning up
some some some
wait I don't got it let me try again
next
Smash Mouth is good
anyway this is the kind of thing
you text each other
yeah you guys hang out at the Astro Lans
you're waiting for this
Epcot should
start having its own Astro Lounge
there is a bar coming
around Spaceship Earth
what better to call it
it's a literal Astro Lounge
play the Innoventions loop in the Spaceship Earth
Bar and Lounge
why not either you could have some random piece of music
or you could have something that people would appreciate
that's old school that takes you there and in my case
puts you to sleep
alright well I've got the aux cord now
I'm going to stay in the Tomorrowland
Neck of the Woods
and I will eventually get to some
new agey stuff for another loop
but let's jump into something
very
goofy
you said earlier goofy and a little jaunty
yes
I've put this on as a relaxer before
this is a real
we've all we all know this I think
if we're the theme park people
yeah so this is a loop
I would date this
to the later
90s Kevin you mentioned
there is some
Randy Newman
like remix Toy Story Randy Newman
and I've got some of the remixed
songs
queued up
but more for the theme
park kind of remix
but some of this
stuff I'm not sure if it's like well I don't know
if that's Rocket to the Moon
because I was not alive
for that right
or I guess I was alive for that one
I was alive for Mars
Mission to Mars but not
Rocket to the Moon but some of this
stuff just sounds like
kind of fun retro-y
sci-fi
spacey so
what park we think here this is
Disney World this is the grand
that's Miracle for Molecules
playing right there
Miracles for Molecules
from Inner Space
yeah that's the song yeah
I don't know that song well enough to know that
from wait
from Adventures Through Inner Space
Miracles from Molecules
just a little
reference
so this is the thing they do now a little bit is like
reincorporate you know
Great Big Beautiful Tomorrow
from Retired Attractions that's fun
which if you have to
if that's how we get new original
music or you know
newly arranged music
in the parks yeah it has to be IP
or like like
the Toontown or the Tomorrowland one
you're sharing like I'm fine with that well they made all
this cool music for Tomorrowland
2055 that leaked somehow
that maybe was recorded off of a bathroom
speaker but like a never built
redo for Disneyland
this is so
for some reason like just the music
leaked and it's a bunch of like very
stirring orchestral covers of
songs from Tomorrowland past
they started playing
they played it in a
they tested the music in a Tomorrowland bathroom
for some reason
this is going to be the score for the whole land
and they decided let's play it in the bathroom and that's the only
remnant of this never built
Tomorrowland version and somebody happened to be
taking a shit with an induction
recording microphone and yeah in
1994 yeah
uploading that to the internet just brought the tape recorder
to the shitter with him like oh thank god
because you mentioned it here is
the ramp up
to great big beautiful
tomorrow oh this is good stuff I know
the ramp up this is where you get like psyched
so peppy it is peppy
it's just it gives me the
imagery in my mind of shooting stars
and the astro
like the little
it feels like the little things go sailing
we got some of those
in our intro little
things that feel like shooting
stars inspiration for your
as I was dissecting that by the way
listening to just making sure
I knew for my
variation on it I was admiring
your handiwork there
I don't even know I'd have to go back and look
at what that is
the other one
now is the time right
yeah the best time of your life
second carousel
of progress theme yes
and then a great big
beautiful tomorrow comes back
but this was
for a brand new
like buy the appliances now
song
yeah this is a great loop
and as far as I know they still play
some of this in tomorrowland
you can hear a lot of it
on the people mover
yeah is there
strange things from
the toy story soundtrack on there
or am I thinking of something I've heard that somewhere
yeah I've heard it somewhere maybe it's not on this
I've heard it in disneyland that is on
here yeah yeah does this same music
show up in disneyland tomorrowland
it feels right
so here's one more
theme park
oh wow
this is if you had wings
but it's really spacey
really
really emotional
yeah and this bears some sonic
similarities to the new age
music of the other loops
but it's just a little bit more
goofy wacky
the sci-fi is more
jazz I mean in a way the
smooth jazz as tomorrowland music
makes no sense but I
I like the kind of future
they're imagining a chill
future which increasingly we're not in
and I feel like that was a listen
to more jazz I feel like that was a pitch bend
don't tell this guy about
those little pitch bends he doesn't like
I was trying to do something nice
I was calling out a pitch bend
it's not mine I was just trying to say
this is just a fun loop
yeah yeah it's really fun
I mean it's a lot of circuits it sounds like circuits
beep boop music
a robot would listen to when the robots
go on the ride but it's not like
outekr or some sort of like
crazy beep boop music it's not harsh
yeah yeah it's
beep boop music for the children
for kids for kids yeah now this is the other
one and we're getting more
new agey oh
my god this is my
sleep this is my sleep music
this is well
this is like a 36
minute loop and it says
the youtube
video was named islands of adventure
entrance loop ocean
trader market
ocean trader market you can find on
the official islands of adventure album
it's like just under
3 minutes but this one has
a lot more
flourishes
I feel like this should be like
bell in beauty and the beast
or like little town
it does kind of sound like that
Jason should be doing the lyrics
Jason should be singing about like he's in the morning
and he's getting Cinnabon
here I am
lighting up my long cigarette
yeah this is
cigarette smoking music isn't it
the bubble order is taking too long
some of the music not just
this but some of the other music today
reminded me of the term
from the 80s
and 90s I don't know
when people coin the term
changes a little
but global village
coffee house have you encountered
this oh I love the aesthetic
you're showing me here yeah well it's very
how do you I mean it's sort of like it's kind
of in the borders bookstore zone
that's the kind of art that would be on a coffee
cup Atlantic dance hall
as I showed you oh right
what you described as yearbook
art yeah like yearbook core but that's
maybe a little bit different than
global village coffee global village
coffee shop yeah global village
coffee shop or global coffee
shop this was a thing
that as I was googling it earlier
in the episode people were
talking about it catching on on
TikTok so yeah there
has been some revisiting
this is the steel drums
part of this arrangement
this is
this is when you're waiting for your Cinnabon
well no this is this is before
you enter the park
so this is not port of entry this
is before you before even
I think maybe you can hear bits of
it in port of entry but
around the tickets and those
coverings and the lighthouse
they have and it's just very
chill it just so chill it
goes with the chill port of entry is
very chill chill and but mysterious
it is mysterious you don't
know what adventures you're about to embark on
and maybe you were about to say something about
this Jason but do you know about the dynamic
nature of this track
where
the different pans
what about that yeah so
as you pass through port of entry
from the way I understand it there's
so that ding ding ding
ding ding they
have multiple instruments doing
multiple tracks of that and as you go from
area to area like you
you pass by where the
person is giving music lessons
in the port of entry and you can hear
the version of that that
has like whatever instrument she's
playing or teaching and you can hear her
ukulele maybe
the pirates with ukulele yeah
but there's probably is like a ukulele thing
but like it different
speakers in the land play the same
song but different
like isolated tracks
of it so it all creates this living
soundtrack that you walk
through and you hear different parts as you
go to different places yes which is really
cool geez that's pretty genius
here's another like bit
of this arrangement
kicks in in just a
second the clapping
the clapping goes
on for so long
so I think the clapping
is one of those isolated
tracks like there's probably that where
you walk by a certain part and you
the clapping is very loud because it's coming
from that specific speaker
and it's probably thematic clapping I don't know
I'll have to check
yeah so this is broken
up I mean well
that's another island of adventure
track something like you were like mixing it in
there well as Kevin
has told us it's very
easy to mix like yeah
port of entry and the entrance area
like stuff goes in
and out a lot I think there was also
something I forget what the
full definition was but
islands of adventure the first park
with like some sort
of dynamic audio like the speakers
are all over oh
really
and I think every
land had original music
too so if you look at the islands of adventure
official soundtrack on Spotify
or Apple music
they break down the like
call to entry slash main
theme confisco grill ocean
trader market skipper island
tours those are all the port of entry
individual tracks
right and these were these were on a
CD and the composer if I recall is William
Kidd but I don't know really anything
else about William Kidd
teenagers been to the port
of entry yeah does he have respect
for Marvel and all of its great heroes
yeah William Kidd is not
uh Dorson
Dorson Droson
Dorson Henry what was the name
Henry Droson
seems right but who knows
I don't know we should not remember
his name after what he did
that ocean trader market
loop if my wife hears that
she knows I'm taking a nap
that's my nap in music
really wow
that ne ne ne
she's like oh he's laying
down for a nap I don't nap that much
is not in right now
is everyone doing music to go to sleep
here in this room I don't usually
it needs it's like
it's like honestly that that
behind the waterfall that's like I've hit an emergency
oh really that's it's 2am
and I gotta be up for something early I gotta
bring out the big guns and that's when I go to that
cause usually hopefully if I'm alright just
a podcast is doing it for me maybe a
.75 podcast
but uh yeah I'm actually not
typically a music person you should have blasted that
that first night we were in Orlando cause I feel like
we couldn't get to sleep that was terrible for both
yeah I know I was
fucking on a high from the first night of
Jelly Rolls and I knew it was an exciting day
the next day pre epic?
an exciting day the next day knowing
that you'd be at Jelly Rolls again
yes I was very excited for the end
of the next day but yeah it was hard getting to sleep
Jason are you a music guy at the night now?
uh no I
usually put on podcasts to go to sleep
same for a good night's
sleep I do old
Disney podcasts that have old news
in them
from the so not relevant
oh yes you've said you've downloaded a bunch of
from like 2009
wow it's kind of a thing
but what podcast do you do?
I will put it on and then
eventually I'll do like 15
or 30 minutes sleep timer
cause then in the morning I actually
went here
so I don't have to backtrack to when I
remember well this is the key
I think the key is it's got to be a podcast
that you don't actually care about listening to
and I don't
I don't want to make a rule for it cause I know people
probably listen to this show to fall asleep and
I wouldn't take it as an insult
that's a compliment
I might wake up laughing
yours is going to be
so uproarious you're going to be
woken up how many laughs per minute
on this show? 9?
well they did a study and yeah
it's 9 laughs per minute
and that's a weak minute
that's if we aren't really cooking
I have started laughing and turned it into
a snort so as not to wake the
dog or my wife
you've routed your own laugh into a snort
I've routed my own laugh to try to
not disturb the house
doesn't the snort make the dog think that a big boar is coming in?
no
don't be silly Scott
of course he doesn't think that
he's a dog who can reason
he would never
my go to is
because it's usually
the voices are
restrained
it's like an NPR style
well your
Kickstarter sucks their voices
are pretty level
there's a podcast called Western Kabuki
about internet
stuff and then
a married couple
from Australia
comedians Demi Lardner and
Tom Walker that podcast
is a very funny non sequitur
title Big Soft Titty
dot PNG
but that is nothing to do with the
content of it it's just very funny
they're on Twitch a lot too
I just heard that person on the guys
podcast I think
yes they both been on guys they're very funny
it might have been for the fart guys episode
Demi is on the fart guys I forget which
one Tom is on
but that's too see that's too
interesting of a podcast to listen to for me
sleeping I have to listen to like
inside the magic before inside the magic
was a terrible website
that has
Ricky era
so you know Ricky
Ricky Briganti
yeah I have his full
library of which are now
completely removed from the internet
his podcast from 2005
to 2014 I have
every episode and I just pick a random
number and I listen to that to fall
asleep that sounds to life
that's a real cousin of having the like the database
the
torrented collection
right all of the CD kiosk
music right but this is just one
words like you can figure out you know
you're hearing news of
it would always start with the news of
the week and it would sometimes
be like you
know there's a new version of
test track coming or something more
monumental Expedition Everest but then sometimes it's like
it's like Bolt's
DVD is going to come out
and it has
it has these special features
and we've interviewed this person about
the Bolt DVD Disney
this week it's heavy anticipation
for their upcoming sure to be biggest
blockbuster of the summer the Lone Ranger
America has Lone Ranger fever
and we're here to capitalize on it
Tonto Mania
Savior of Frontierland
Lone Ranger
what else you got Jason
oh that was it those were my two
hey wonderful
thanks for the clapping
let's all clap for that
again now pan it now go to the other side
of the mic great great great oh that's very
dynamic binaural audio
it's perfect it's perfect
there are podcasts
of people walking
around the theme parks and recording
with binaural mics
and that
I've used to fall asleep if they're
just riding the monorail oh
yeah I used to do that too
like I had this recording of Ellen's
Energy Adventure this was when I was very young
you don't have to add a qualifier
to that there isn't there's always
a good age to fall asleep
something about this particular
one just seems like kind of sicko mode
and so yeah I was like 13 or 14
but I had this like just the entire
45 minute Ellen's Energy
Adventure attraction audio
and I would fall asleep to that
or the American Adventure
you were channeling the spirit
of overheated dads for
both of those that's right
and I did sleep in both of those
attractions maybe that's why but you didn't get
overheated in a different way by
sexy sexy Bill Nye
a la somebody's blushing bride
over here
Jason's arch nemesis
Bill Nye
my elementary school
fond member is
replaced by
your fun music videos are not fun
to be anymore Beakman was better than
you oh my
fourth grade science teacher was so
anti-Beakman really?
yes she hated Beakman she
loved Bill Nye but she would
occasionally begrudgingly put
on Beakman because Beakman was
too wild with science
I think he was probably she found him
annoying strange camera angles
unrealistic hair what about that mouse
guy that was a sidekick
oh I don't care for him
was it a rat? oh well mouse was similar
I liked him yeah
we should we should wind it down we've been going for a long
time but this has been a wonderful
exploration I feel I am
were there any runner ups for anyone
was there anything that you wanted to
do a little bit I mean one that
was like very formative for
me was the everything that plays
before Captain EO
waiting for it to start I think
I had a big influence on my music taste
in general like still like
scares me to bit like it really
takes me there that's on YouTube
and just like you know kind of like
variations on one little like
you know what one little
synth theme and just kind of like
ambienting out the same musical
neck of the woods but then with you know with little
weird scary stabs of
little sparkly synth things
yeah still scares me like
I was three yeah no I that's
that stuff is good when they
talk about like the arts arts and crafts movement
in California
like there's a little tram loop with all
also with like oh that's right that would have been the name
for inspired by the arts and crafts
movement but that does like
that kind of takes me there I know yeah
for whatever reason that phrase and I think that maybe
there isn't even music under it but now I start thinking
of just DCA
aesthetic and the music when I think of that
phrase hear that honey it was inspired by the arts
and crafts movement early California
I think I say that we got
to check it out there arts and crafts
I am on the email
newsletter of the museum of
arts and crafts which I believe
is in Florida
the museum of the arts and crafts movement
so the movement was
not just California
there was a movement happening everywhere I think it was kind of
wasn't in California at all Disney's lying
that voiceover is lying
I bet there were arts and crafts movements
in a lot of states
probably just Florida
yeah and they're stealing it
anything else you consider
anything else you want to shout out
we don't have a lot of time we shouldn't go on
and on but epic universe
so what I will say about
epic universe is that
the music I heard there was all
really good
I think like the Burke music
loop is potentially
just music from the
scores of the movies but they're very
well selected it's not just playing it's not playing
some pop song that was at the end of how
to train your dragon which I assume there was one
it's like very atmospheric
that's what party rock anthem was from I believe
party rock anthem
love theme from how to train your dragon
and like of course the Danny Elfman
stuff is really atmospheric and cool
when you're in the land but the celestial
park music to me
really
really rules it's pretty good
apparently maybe 14 hours
of it that's what I heard I remember
Jim Hill I think he maybe said 60
and I got excited but
no I think maybe I miss a lot of
hours it is as 16
as 60 I think maybe
he was not wrong there whether to bother
people we I know it universal
going like do you have
access to these fort is there
any box that's coming with these 14
to 60 hours I wouldn't be surprised
massive crate lands in
the vinyl of dark
universe already
sold out so obviously there's
they're thinking in that way I think
celestial park as far as I could tell
every restaurant had
a loop meteor astro
pub had a loop
pizza moon
has a loop and
star light
no stardust racers has a really
like moody
score that plays next to it
and a little bit
of dynamic like
island of adventure growing dynamic place
dynamic with like
as you walk from place to place the song
changes I think there might
be a little bit of that too but I'll
go back soon I've been supposedly
people who worked on port of entry also
worked on celestial park
that explains why I
feel of peace I love celestial
park and I thank you
guys yeah I know
I was gonna say you were trying to sell
us on it because we did not fall in
the state that we saw we did not necessarily
I always try I always try to invite
anyone who listens to the show
when they do the show to rip
into us before they
start and that's the closest it's
happened gentle way to do it no no
I want well I I'm trying to like you want
well you like to get fucked up so yeah you want people
to unleash the beast I'm saying I
believe in your capacity to love
celestial park someday
you're coming at us with positive like
educational Epcot energy like we can find
a way yeah we can explore
the cosmos there's so many good angles
online of and I don't hate celestial
park but there's so many good angles that
I didn't experience yeah I
think when you both go back I think
you will see it in a new light
I think I
have you seen the video
where someone took the old camcorder
to epic universe
and it's soundtracked with like
an instrumental
killers when
when we were young
came out 20 years ago
oh wow
so I
I think I was laughing
at the idea that that is going
to make it a moving experience
I felt emotional
yeah here in that that tune
and the old footage yeah
it worked it worked on me
okay so we are now
we're just saying epic universe we're like
heading into an area where area
loops are more important than
ever this might be like the
greatest chapter of area loop we've ever
experienced I think it
I think that
it shows promise and it shows that they're
thinking about it still which is all I ask
for Disney I think is still
thinking about it in certain places
they've gone a little more boring they aren't willing
to do their weird little Ray
Lynch's and their blips and bloops yeah I don't know
if the Ray Lynch era is ever coming
back but
I mean if they're making new music
I support it
but none of this like saving Mr
Banks crap like just
don't just throw stuff you have the rights to
from like Nat Geo documentaries and
call it an area loop
think about it because it's
important and it gives people a lot
to think about and a lot to talk about
which was so nice to do here
for a while with you great
great idea for an app thank you for bringing it
to us and just so great to have you
on the show properly
not via the
avatar system so happy to say
Kevin Tully Survive podcast the ride
nice let's exit through the
gift shop anything you'd like to plug
yeah Telethon
the band all of our music
is available for free telethonband.bandcamp.com
we have a new album
Suburban Electric came out
early March and
tour at least a small tour
happening in July great great
yes well
yeah check all that out I really like the record
and it has been great
hanging and getting to know you over
the last couple of years from a
from but a contemporary
related email to
a lot of good hangs and a great episode
here so thanks buddy
yes happy to do it anytime
it's yeah
it's been a hoot hey wonderful wonderful as
for us sorry Kevin would you come back
and do an episode just on that cat that
pervert cat the Rippentons cat
the Rippentons cat yeah
I would love maybe that's that could be
my birthday shot we would have to like
find primary source material of
like who illustrated it we need to like
talk to the person who created the Rippentons cat
yeah yeah it's not far
from that I like I don't know it's
there's sort of some like Wolfgang
puckiness to it yeah
I think it ties in this and just
there's like an airbrush thing about it I think
is very interesting it's a little
t-shirt
you would buy to save the rainforest
and a little of that global
coffee shop I think it's very
related to global coffee shop
the save the rain fart that was the
same artist who drew a lot of the Joe
Camel stuff don't forget oh that's right
oh I forgot that title yeah yeah yes
no it's definitely it's it's camel core
it's rainforest core and did you not
inspire a tattoo of this
what was the story with the
tattoo oh telethon bassist
Alex he got
tattoos to represent every
member of telethon
and mine is a Rippentons
cat when he when asked how
do what how do I sum you up via
tattoo you said this cat
yeah wow yeah
I wanted him to do the one from
the Rippentons album for exclamation
point where the Rippentons cat is swinging a golf
club because I play golf
but he didn't want to get like golf
a golf
insignia on his
on his leg that's
fair so you got scary cat great
scary cat golfing I don't know
yeah it's whichever one has a
it's like a joker motif like a
card it's
really really an ugly version I think
the Rippentons cat can be cute but
that is not a version that is when you look up
Rippentons cat you will see many
terrifying horrible pieces of
art and if you're Mike you'll see many
penises
suggestions of penises
as for us for three
bonus episodes every month check out podcast the ride the second
gate or get one more bonus episode on our VAP
tier club three you'll find all of that
at patreon.com slash podcast the ride
maybe we should make some effort to put these playlists
in the show notes Kevin's playlist
liminal oasis which you
know alright sixty hours epic universe
sure but if you want a hundred sixty
six hours
that really transport you it's really gotten
away from me I don't know
no curate don't cut it
down don't lose a thing
forever
dog this has been a forever
dog production executive
produced by Mike Carlson Jason
Sheridan Scott Gardner
Brett Boehm Joe
Silio and Alex Ramsey
for more original podcasts
please visit forever dog podcasts
dot com and subscribe to
our shows on apple podcasts
spotify or wherever you get
your podcasts keep up with the latest
forever dog news by following
us on twitter and instagram
at forever dog team
and liking our page on facebook