Well, we know who needs to start this one.
Yep, you got it.
How can the fuck guess the round is 78?
On this episode I threw toilet paper everywhere, yay!
There he is.
See, we couldn't just be done, maybe.
This might be the first done in 20 seconds.
30 seconds.
Wow, they could do that.
Yeah, that's an option.
Boy, that'd be interesting, but also then the anger would start too.
Yeah, it would be interesting.
Yeah, but some people would think it was a pretty rebellious cool rogue move.
There would be think pieces about it for sure, about how brave it was and bold.
But then some people, some more traditional listeners might say, well, I would have liked a full episode.
I'd pay money for this.
They might say that.
But sometimes it's the notes they're not playing.
Sometimes it's them getting in their cars and going home as soon as the intros happen.
It's the mischievous thing you could expect from a character like Stitch.
Oh, you're right.
That's true too.
The scampishness.
Yeah, I mean, you truly did say it all right there.
But I guess to stretch it out a little bit, this week Lilo and Stitch returns to the big screen.
The live action Lilo and Stitch is out at the end of this week.
And as we know, when one of these Disney live action movies comes out, it's pandemonium in the streets.
You feel the excitement more and more with each passing one that comes out.
It is funny you say that, but because of obviously many not well-received live action remakes.
It's like, actually, Mephisto is doing very well.
Actually, that is the first week we're not right.
And it's actually stuck around.
So what you said was lies.
But it will be interesting because I feel like the trailer for this one came out.
And a bunch of people were like, you know what?
This one looks good.
For whatever reason, I saw a lot of people say that.
I've not seen the film.
It's funny because this one felt different in reception.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, and maybe, and I'm rooting for it.
I don't know this.
I don't think any of us know the director, Dean Fleischer Kemp.
But I think we've got friends of friends.
So that's a comedy.
That's a cool comedy person.
So you've got to be rooting for someone of that nature.
Sure.
So then this comedy person has a hit with a Disney live action,
and then it starts to trickle down to the lowest rung of comedy director out there
to get the call from the Mouse House.
All I know is trickle down always works.
It always works in America.
Yeah.
My hurts morning in America.
You want to talk about the same time period?
It's breakfast time in America.
Down below him, the dog below the table waiting for his scripts.
Could you have a little?
What's the Fox and the Hound debut?
What's left?
Great Mouse Detective Streaming Service?
At least let me do a cold read for this sidekick.
I think I'm getting the...
Well, you know what I think I could do?
Hunchback 2.
That's the one I'm passionate about.
Right, right, right.
Hunchback 2 much more than Hunchback 1,
mainly just for this one shot of him ringing a bell that I like,
this looped animation.
So I would build the whole pitch around that,
and I'm sure that'll be fine.
I think making Hunchback of Notre Dame for release in 2030
should be fine and not problematic,
not loaded with landmine after landmine.
I choked a little bit, and not for real.
I shoot choked, as wrestlers would say.
I did hear...
I don't think you...
I think the title, The Guy of Notre Dame, new title.
Yeah.
Notre Dame's finest.
Interesting guy.
Nice man who lives at Notre Dame.
I did hear Barry Jenkins was using his Oscar win and Mufasa money
or credibility to elevate a lot of smaller filmmakers
that he produced movies and stuff.
So I like that.
I respect that, getting your bag and rising tide lifts all ships.
So Scott's going to get his bag, and then all the other tides will rise.
The smaller tides will even rise now because he gets his bag.
Sure.
But again, there is trickle down in size of bags.
Yeah.
The bags do get smaller and smaller, but it is still a bag.
That's Disney's...
Can you deny that it is a bag?
Because you're looking at it?
How do you define a bag?
That is one.
You'll get Dean's scraps, and then your scraps from this streaming deal
is that you'll give Jason a gift card for one month of free Disney Plus.
So that's how it'll trickle down to Jason.
They keep going up and up, and if you don't want ads, you're in trouble.
Right.
It's free, but it's not ad-free.
Okay, that's fine.
Sorry.
I know there's new foot-breeze animations.
My movie, Guy of Notre Dame, lost so much money.
Maybe that's the commercial that finally convinced me to try Fabric Softener.
So anyways, it being Stitch Mania, as the listeners are aware of,
Stitch Mania seems like a good time to talk about this,
which has come up here and there through the year.
I think it must have been touched on when we talked about the Castle cake
a long time ago when the cake was turned into a castle.
Well, that's what happened at the end when it went back to Castle.
The cake was turned into a castle.
I was right, and that was right to say that.
A bag is a bag.
No, but if you look at the history of unusual things
that have happened to Cinderella Castle in Walt Disney World,
the history is two things, and this is the second.
Here we are.
What happened was, on November 16, 2004,
to celebrate the opening of what would soon be heralded
as the new worst ride in Disney World,
Stitch's Great Escape was opening.
Stitch has a new, sure-to-be permanent home
that won't become fodder for the Disney excavator vloggers out there
to run around in in ten years' time.
Look, there was a new Stitch ride.
How do we promote it?
What if Stitch goes wild in the Magic Kingdom?
And the biggest way that this was conveyed
was that you walked into the park that day
and the castle was covered in toilet paper.
This actually happened, if you don't know that this happened.
He also tagged the castle.
Oh, you're right.
One big component,
which if you want to say what it was,
if you want to say it in your own voice,
if you want to say it in somebody else's voice.
I wrote Stitch is king.
It's pre-paid.
Sorry, Christ, today is Stitch is king.
New yay album forthcoming, Stitch is king.
Yeah, a big sign says Stitch is king on it,
and that happened for one day only.
They went to all of this effort for one day
pseudo-transformation of Cinderella Castle,
and it has lived in infamy ever since.
I like it.
I think it's funny.
I also like it.
Yeah.
I like it, and I think they should do more things like this.
It's going to be a clean sweep here.
I also like it.
I think the listeners probably too, I would guess.
But you're not Kate Castle fan?
Yeah, that was where I landed.
You were more middle.
I was not.
Jason and I are big Kate Castle boys.
Oh, I love it.
I love the Kate Castle.
I recall.
Yes, I think people come for their one-year vacation,
their annual vacation, maybe every couple years they come.
People want to see the castle the way they remember it.
I don't care.
I want that thing to look different every time I go into the parks.
Yeah.
I would like a new overlay every week.
And I know that's coming from a place of privilege for somebody who gets to go a lot.
But I don't care.
I want it.
I do find it, because that's not an angle that I particularly had about the castle cake.
I had just other objections to the castle cake.
This notion that this is my one time, and I get to see the castle,
and instead I am confronted with this.
I am at one of the most magical spot in the world,
and I can't have a nice picture in front of it because it is cake
or because it has toilet paper all over it.
Flip your thinking.
You're there on the most special.
Of course.
You're there at a time where something very unusual has happened.
Most boring people just went and took a picture of the castle like anybody could.
You were there in rarefied air.
You got to see something that maybe people might not even believe ever happened
decades after the fact.
You're special, and you don't even realize it.
You're the privileged one.
You don't even know.
Even this is a day like that's really special.
Castle Kate stuck around for a little while.
Yeah, that was a long time.
This stuck around, but the people who would disagree with me
are the ones who spent thousands and thousands of dollars
for that grand Floridian wedding pavilion with a perfect view of the castle.
That is kind of why this lives in infamy
because it's like people were getting married that day.
Is that true?
Did anyone register being upset about that?
Yeah, is that an anecdote you saw online?
This is what I've always heard about it.
Well, the reason they haven't done something like this since
is because the wedding pavilion is right there
and it's got a perfect view of the castle.
Right, from the distance.
Now, if it was a Stitch super fan getting married,
they'd probably be thrilled.
Though you can't see Stitch from that far away.
You'd just see toilet paper.
Just see his handiwork.
You would, and there is a little bit of a leap here
because here's one question I had coming into this.
Is this something that Stitch would do?
I mean, it certainly seems in character,
but this isn't something that happens in the movie, is it?
I can answer that one word, yes.
Is there toilet paper stuff?
Oh, he ran away again.
Oh, so he can't answer it.
Can you answer on his behalf?
Yeah, he said yes.
I think he's just a little bit of a rascal.
This guy's asking literally because I've seen the movie and I can't remember.
Does he toilet paper someone's house?
I don't think so.
I think he just makes a mess.
Yes, he's messy.
He goes through the pots and pans and all that, but I don't think he...
There's a lot of results of pictures of it.
There's a pin with him with toilet paper,
and there's Stitch toilet paper holders.
Maybe he gets into the toilet paper in the movie?
Similar, I think, because he behaves kind of like a dog
and they pass him off as a dog once or twice.
And if you have a wily dog and they fuck with your toilet paper.
I see.
I think, Mike, I differ from you.
I like when they fuck with the castle.
I like this. I like castle cake.
What do you differ with me?
You just say he likes all.
Well, yeah, but I don't like when they add ornamentations,
like too much gold accents or anniversary pieces.
But that's almost more subtle stuff.
That seems wild to me.
I don't even notice that shit.
They change the colors.
I think that castle...
I'm a stickler for this.
I think the castle should be very gray
with touches of blue on the turrets.
And what happens that you don't like?
They keep painting it different colors
and adding more gold and stuff.
Do you know what castle year is your prime year
for castle enjoyment?
I think it's probably the 70s through the 90s.
And do you think it was the same color consistently?
I think it was, yeah,
because I think that gray was meant to pop
with the Florida blue.
So you would be upset if one summer it was like,
it's hot color summer, 90s throwback, hot colors.
Oh, if they go all out, yes,
but if it's the anniversary of Hong Kong Disney
and every park is celebrating.
You're saying they would do a subtle paint job
in that instance?
They would do a subtle paint job
or they would add a gold medallion or stuff.
So you don't like subtle changes to the castle.
Gray or I want it wild.
So what I'm describing is like neon pink, hot purple.
Love it, love it.
You would love that.
I would love that.
That is interesting to me
because I sometimes clock the little changes,
like it's like more gold or whatever,
but that doesn't usually bother me.
I like that actually.
I like the subtle changes too.
So you're right, we do differ there.
My other outtake is,
I kind of liked Stitch's Great Escape.
It had a lot of elements of Alien Counter.
They saved Skippy, they saved the tomb
and it gets dark and the shoulder is strange move.
It might be a victim of that first ride being so beloved.
Yeah, obviously they wanted to tamp down the scariness,
but another thing is just practically
in terms of getting people off the board in Tomorrowland,
it would eat people, pre-show people, ride show.
This is not a good reason to like a ride.
People go to it.
People go to it so they don't go on the people,
but there's not a line for the people.
This ride was great.
People went inside it,
which prevented them from going on things I wanted to do.
This is the thing.
You'd say the same thing about like,
Disney World set up a closet
and people went in there accidentally,
which prevented them from going in the big thunder line.
This is what like little Lantesta enjoyed
about going to theme parks is that it would be like,
well, this is a people eater.
Look how fast the line goes at the hot dog cart or whatever.
That's the different like sort of math brain that,
and Jason obviously enjoyed that as well.
Monsters Inc. Laugh Floor is fun
and it also holds a lot of people.
There you go.
Gets them off the board.
So it's a whole thing.
There's no Astro Orbiter or...
This is a phrase I've never heard.
Get them off the board means that now they aren't like,
milling about.
They're not milling about.
They're not eating in the restaurants
or going on other attractions.
Attractions, yeah, yeah.
And it keeps them out of like, you know,
Tron as a giant line or Spaceman as a giant line.
It is a thing that teenagers love the most.
Crowd management.
This is, I just don't,
the reasons we have said why Stitch's Grit Escape was good,
eats people, retains some elements of previous attraction,
but not all.
Previous attraction, which...
I mean, that wasn't the most glowing review
I've ever heard of a ride.
But let's put on top of it,
you get a chili dog burp in the face.
Now that too.
I did not experience this attraction,
so I guess I can't judge.
It sounds very unpleasant to me.
But that said, I like some other,
because Stitch shows up and bothers the tiki birds
in the Japan tiki room,
which on paper seems like an annoying thing,
but I liked it quite a bit.
I saw it, yeah.
You know, Stitch hijinks in other things,
I would say I don't mind overall.
And I like these particular Stitch hijinks.
I guess, let me, here's a couple other aspects of this,
because it wasn't just the toilet paper unexplained,
although probably if you weren't paying close attention,
it kind of was that.
And you thought, what happened?
Did a plane do an accidental dump of refuse
in an aerial equivalent of a Dave Matthews
banning boat situation?
Did Dave Matthews' plane fly over Disney World,
which is not legal.
And we are just lucky.
Yeah, yeah, well, it made a mistake,
mistake one, flying over Disney World.
I like that it was also Dave Matthews.
Right.
All right, lesson learned from the bus fiasco.
You don't know when they went over a bridge in Chicago,
correct?
And they dumped a septic tank
all over a tourist boat that was open air.
Now there's a plaque in that spot commemorating
when it happened.
So yes, Dave Matthews' plane flies over Disney World.
We went to Chicago a few years ago.
We didn't go see the plaque.
We did.
We didn't see the plaque, no.
There may not have been a plaque at that time.
It may not have been there?
Yes, the plaque may be a newer, I don't know,
full history of the plaque.
I think it was an architecture boat,
was it an architecture boat tour, which I've taken?
Just a nice little tour around the lake.
That's what it is, too.
Maybe it's not that one.
No type of cruise would this be good for
or would deserve it.
Maybe it's not the same tour.
There's no such thing as that.
But it's funny that as opposed to like a booze cruise,
if it was like, oh yes, wonderful architecture
all across the city.
There is, yeah, there is.
There's the building from the Wilco cover.
There it is.
A remarkable piece of architecture.
What's that?
Oh!
I forget what tour it is.
I should look it up, which tour.
I think it is a tour.
I don't think it was like a party boat.
I'm pretty sure it was like,
because the architecture tour,
you just have all little chairs on the top deck
and you sit and there's a guide
that tells you about the buildings.
That's it.
Then you get a bunch of poop on you.
Now before I begin the next part of the tour,
I've been talking for a long time,
so if you don't mind,
I'm just going to clear my throat
and look up at the sky as I do it.
Okay.
So anyways, the full picture here,
when you entered the park that day,
wait, I might forget,
was there something in the front?
They didn't do anything to like the,
like in front of the railroad station or anything.
I'm not sure.
Okay, here's what I do know,
is that when you walked in,
you might see a big sign that says,
that's a wanted poster,
and it said,
Experiment 626, AKA Stitch,
wanted for creating mischief, mayhem, and pandemonium.
Be on the lookout.
A naughty blue menace known as Stitch has escaped.
Wait, it's been a while since you said the phrase,
naughty, naughty.
That feels like it needs a Stitchening.
Naughty, naughty.
Oh, he came back.
He was real excited to come back home.
Stitch.
Oh no, where'd he go?
Oh no, he's got to get into the bathrooms
at Forever Long now.
Uh-oh.
Oh, there's a whole shelf of toilet paper in there.
Oh no.
Oh, that's the thing that he does, as we know,
is he goes into the toilet paper and spreads it around.
Okay, Stitch has escaped in the Magic Kingdom Park
and was last seen in the vicinity of Cinderella Castle.
If you have any information leading to the capture
of this alien troublemaker,
report to the Galactic Federation Teleport Center
in Tomorrowland.
So kind of like a subtle, in-story way
to tell people that Stitch is on the loose
and that something is coming to Tomorrowland,
and I assume Galactic Federation Teleport Center
is the like alien encounter-esque, you know,
like whatever, the pad.
Roo, yeah, they don't say go to Stitch's great escape.
They keep it in story.
Okay, yeah.
I think that's cool.
And I really like the idea that you would go
to the Magic Kingdom that day,
and there's a story going on.
Yes.
Just today.
It's only for us.
And then you went down Main Street,
and there were wanted posters everywhere,
all along all of the lamp posts.
That's cool, too.
All leading you to the main show,
that being the castle.
I mean, why wouldn't they do stuff like this all the time?
I think that's great.
Yeah, well, specifically for opening rides,
or you mean just in general?
Hmm.
I mean, I guess, look, I'd like a little story going on
for whatever reason.
Whatever they need to plug.
My jealousy of Tokyo getting Quacky Duck City.
I mean, there's a story going on.
It's Donald's birthday.
We're celebrating it.
It's taking over everything.
The flower bed outside, Main Street.
It just isn't something they do Pixar fast,
and it's very generic,
and, you know, it'll be a Pixar parade,
but that's about it.
You're not getting, you're not changing the castle
into the ball, or the light,
with Luxo, the name of the light.
Oh, yes.
Right, right, right.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's not bad.
Hey, sure, yeah.
Into a giant lamp.
Yeah, turn the castle into a giant lamp.
One of the lists about this mentioned
when they turned Space of Earth
into a big Mike Wazowski head.
Oh, yeah, that's fun.
That's good.
That is good.
Project.
But was that just for a show?
That wasn't, like, a thing they did for a long time.
No, it was just a projection in a show.
That was part of something.
But I like it.
Yeah, I like that, too.
That's very cool.
Well, you know what it all is reminiscent of
is an idea that never happened,
that's something that Jim Hill
wrote an article about a long time ago,
something that was proposed that they wanted to do
that Disney, very inventive Disney promotions guy
Jack Lindquist came up with,
which is that when they wanted to put Muppet Vision 3D
into Lincoln Theater in Disneyland,
that they were going to do this whole thing
where there was a passing of the baton,
where the big six or whatever went on vacation,
and they hand the park over to the Muppets
for a certain stretch of time,
and that they would have committed to this
and that you would not have been able to meet Mickey
and Minnie, and the characters are not around,
and they actually commit to the story.
Cool, really cool.
This I think was, it must have been after
Muppet Vision opened and was successful in Florida,
so probably like 1991, something like that,
and it was going to be this, like,
at least summer-long promotion that where,
very much like this, there is a story going on.
You know that the Muppets have been handed
the keys to Disneyland.
When you drive in that day,
the sign doesn't say Disneyland.
A sheet has been put up over it, and it says Muppetland.
So great.
Characters are running around through rides
that they're not supposed to be in.
Animal is chasing the girls in Pirates.
So awesome.
Miss Piggy snuck into Small World and stuff,
or like there's a penguin around or whatever.
So awesome.
The biggest thing all culminating in,
that for the whole summer or whatever amount of time,
the Matterhorn was going to be Kermit Green.
Right.
Incredible.
This, how, like, we'd all always be talking about this.
Yeah, yeah.
That would have been a legendary thing.
And I guess some people, like,
but would it have made anybody,
I mean, like, I don't think the Matterhorn is the same.
I don't think anybody cares if the Matterhorn is green.
Why not?
Yeah, probably not.
I don't know, I guess.
There's a degree of Disney purist
that probably would hate anything like that,
but also that same Disney purist
that would think would like the Muppets.
But then, I don't know,
because they've tried to do a zillion things
to Blinken over the years,
and it's always like, no, no, no, torches.
Yeah, I don't know, because it depends how,
it depends how good everything was on some level, I guess,
because you could see the bad version of, like,
it looks green, it looks like shit,
it throws everything off,
which we'd still love, by the way.
Yes.
Doesn't matter if it's bad, whatever.
It doesn't matter if some of this stuff was bad,
because it would have been so, it would be interesting.
But, so I can understand where, again,
the people, like, come for their one time during the year,
but they should, I don't know, I'm torn on exactly,
because some people also, I feel like,
wouldn't have noticed that animals on the ride, on pirates.
There'd be people there that kind of come casually,
and they didn't know there was a big Muppet takeover,
and I guess maybe they were looking to meet Mickey,
and he's not there, and that would be upsetting.
It's like, he's Disney, now it feels like it's maybe more doable
if you do it at California Adventure,
and you can go meet Mickey at Disneyland.
Sure.
No problem, but if that is big,
like, you brought your kid that day.
Something like that, they should do whatever they want to car-
I can understand, if the castle is untouchable,
I guess I understand that, but anything else?
Don't we, I kind of like the,
or I think everybody didn't like, maybe,
the idea that when they turn the, with projection,
they turn the Tower of Terror into like a-
Christmas present.
It's not my favorite thing in the world.
What?
I love it.
I don't, well, the projection, I don't know,
it's a little too projectioned out lately.
I am too.
In general.
But that's the only way,
they're never getting paint cans out,
they're never gonna paint the whole Tower of Terror.
Yeah, I don't know, it depends,
but whatever the show was I was watching,
I didn't love it.
Or like a Christmas party.
It didn't seem like the right building.
I don't think I knew there was a show,
I thought they just did it.
Well, maybe, I might be mixing,
there's a show in Paris that they use that tower a lot,
there's an Avengers show there,
and I'm trying to remember if this is what I'm thinking of,
or if I'm thinking of the Hollywood Studios
when there was a big present.
Yeah.
A lot of this seems like the logical conclusion
of like, when Epcot opened,
it's like different kind of theme park,
there's one character,
there's only Figment and Dreamfinder,
like none of the usual characters,
and then like, okay, they're here,
but they're in space suits.
Okay, they're here, but they ride the bus,
and it's just so quickly chipped away over the years.
You know, the closest thing they could do now,
these days, is to do like a ticketed event,
like a Muppet takeover event.
Oh, yeah.
And then do the narrative in there,
because I don't think they've,
like all these ticketed events are pretty popular
out here at least.
Yeah.
Obviously, Mickey's Very Merry or whatever
is popular in Florida, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Or whatever, not so scary as popular.
The Jollywood Nights is not popular,
but still sells out,
even though people didn't like it the first year.
I don't know, whatever.
I think they're course correct.
But they figured it out, okay.
But ticketed events are fun,
we went to that 90s night five years ago,
seems like people like Star Wars night,
they like the Pride night,
but it does feel like you could do something
a little more, I hate to say experimental,
at Disneyland.
Yeah, yeah.
But that is, I guess what it is,
if it's like, yes, there's a narrative
that the Muppets literally have taken it over.
Yeah.
I guess it's tougher,
because like you can't,
you wouldn't want to like start taking robots out
for the day and putting them back on at night.
I think that's impossible to do.
I guess you could put a,
you could put like a sheet over animals
during the day.
You could put a statue,
you know, those kind of like the Incredicoaster
has the like non-moving statues.
Sure.
Cover it in a barrel during the day.
Yeah.
Curtain.
Make a barrel on it.
But like full, I've said this before,
like Disneyland alien invasion night
during like Halloween,
and the park is just pretty dark.
Cool.
And there's weird music and neon,
like very low neon light,
and there are like original aliens lurking everywhere.
Definitely.
And then like Space Mountain
would be maybe an actual overlay,
and then everything else would just be like,
oh, we turned the lights lower on pirates or something.
What do you think happens to Castle in this?
Like if we're going to...
In my alien scenario?
Yeah.
What do you think,
like let's say that you don't have their rules.
They've taken the,
the aliens have taken the Castle as their new base.
Wow.
Projection.
So a mix of projection.
Projection and make it seem like
a chunk of the Castle is missing.
Ooh.
That would be cool.
Go on fire like Independence Day.
But then also you could have it
like maybe that the alien ship
is like part like organic material.
Now it's growing as well.
So you got some like Giger,
HR Giger style,
weird like alien designs
that are kind of growing out of
the two sides of the Castle or to the top.
Oh, wow.
So like you really could go freaky with it.
Like they're like,
it's turning,
they're turning it into an organic.
Yes.
Item.
Like that it's,
they're like,
they're laying a lot of eggs.
They're getting the Castle pregnant
with their alien eggs.
Essentially.
Yeah.
So you,
I mean, that's,
you know,
that's,
that's if the gloves are off.
Yeah.
The gloves aren't off.
It's a little green.
Lighted a little green.
Not too much though.
Yeah.
Tint of green.
I, they,
again,
they wouldn't do that
because there'd be so many pictures
of a terrifying looking Castle.
Yeah.
And they just couldn't do it.
Sadly.
I've talked about this before.
What do they do with the Fox stuff?
And it's like full on aliens,
xenomorph Castle.
It's like black and smooth,
you know,
like kind of alien,
like one of the xenomorphs heads
or one of the ships.
Yeah.
It'd be awesome.
It's a giant head.
And then the mouth is swallowing you.
Yeah.
That would be awesome.
But.
If they wanted to soften it,
you know,
I keep hearing Mars,
they need moms.
So there was a bunch of aliens walking around,
but also a bunch of moms
that'll.
There'll be a bunch of moms.
Put you at ease.
Well, here's a little thought exercise
that I just started.
I'm like,
because what if this had worked at the time?
What if in 2004,
this is a hit
and it helped the ride
and we realized that we can promote
our new wares by taking our iconic Castle
or our other iconic landmarks
and doing stuff with them.
I'm just looking for like,
what else was Disney doing around this time?
Like in 2005,
what movies did they have?
And the one that I jumped to
is that they released the hit comedy,
The Pacifier.
And I think if you could have turned Spaceship Earth
into Vin Diesel's bald head.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
Hey, everybody.
It's me, The Pacifier.
Mike, the kids I'm supposed to watch are loose.
Have you seen them?
I feel like they might have gone to Italy.
Give me a shot if you see my kids.
If you just popped in and said that.
That's what I do, right?
That's me, The Pacifier.
He said,
give me a shot if you see my kids
every hour on the hour.
Oh, they could do it again.
They could do a reprise of it
when he released that single in like 2020.
Remember Vin Diesel's single?
I don't know.
Yeah, what was the name of it?
It was kind of catchy.
Didn't we talk about it?
We talked about it on the show.
I'm sure it must have come up on the show.
I would guarantee we did.
It wasn't the Jeremy Renner singles.
It wasn't his cover of House of the Rising Sun.
No.
Feel Like I Do.
Feel Like I Do, yeah.
By Vin Diesel, yeah.
Sure, you could have done that.
Yeah, you should have replaced
It's a Small World with it.
Let me just click to like 2006.
Oh yeah, what happened in 2006?
Oh, like Santa Claus 3.
Oh, turning it into the Evil Ice Fortress
of the villainous Jack Frost.
That's Martin Short.
That's Martin Sheen.
Martin Short.
Oh my God, I wish it was Martin Short.
Hey, Martin Short, you know,
they connect the ice castle
with his father-of-the-bride
wedding planner character
that the wedding pavilion is named after.
Yes, true.
Yes, Franxx.
Franxx.
That remains true to this day, I believe.
Great little Easter egg,
weird little Easter egg
that I sort of like.
I'm going to talk about that.
The thing that when I was younger,
I always loved about Parks is
when they would do like limited time
or very special things.
Yeah.
But now there's such,
they're so protective,
all the studios of their characters
and IP and everything.
But it might in like
a more disorganized,
less vertically integrated time,
some part of the company
might have no idea
that the other part of the company
is doing this.
That was the magic.
That rocks.
Is there something you could do
with the shaggy dog?
The Tim Allen shaggy dog.
The Tim Allen Robert Downey Jr. shaggy dog.
Oh.
Doesn't have to be castle,
can be any of them.
Well, what if the castle was furry?
Oh, that's good.
Oh man, that's very good.
Just like shag carpeting
kind of on the castle.
Because isn't the shaggy dog,
that's like a serum or something,
turns it into a shaggy dog.
Turns a man into a shaggy dog, yeah.
So somebody,
Dave Matthews Plane drove by,
released too much of the serum,
and the castle sprouted a bunch of fur.
Yuck.
I love it, it's very clean.
Oh, even if you could just,
like when Universal does Grinchmas,
and you can meet Max the dog,
and I think at one time I was in City Walk,
and someone was walking like four Max's to their car,
like whoever took them to watch the end of the night.
Like, I love meeting Max,
and petting Max, and saying hi to him.
If you could meet a giant sheep dog,
if you could meet the shaggy dog.
Well, that's true.
Did you meet the dogs when they were off the clock though?
Yeah, I think so.
So you stopped and met the Max's.
I feel like I saw them.
So you didn't have to pay to meet Max.
No, they were just walking by,
it was just like four dogs on leash.
And you're sure those were Max's though?
I think they were Max's.
Because I don't want you like stealing Valor.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Could it have been another?
They're rescue dogs.
They're not on the clock.
They're not working right now.
They are not allowed to be cute unless they're getting paid.
You wait for somebody at a Comic Con
to leave the autograph table to ask them for a photo.
Because then they're away from the part where they charge.
Well, I forget.
I forget whether I told this story.
When we went to the media day for Super Nintendo World,
and there was a shuttle bus to take you back to parking
when I was waiting,
there's a security guy,
and the security dog was off the clock.
And it was being like slobbery great date.
It was so exciting.
He was so friendly, saying hi to everyone.
He saw me, and he jumped up so excited.
His head bonked my head.
And it felt like I had been punched in the face.
Wait, he was off the clock?
He was off the clock.
They said, oh yeah, you can say hi.
He's off the clock right now.
We're going home.
Why do I not remember this?
Well, you were gone.
I think we all left separately.
Oh, okay.
So this was later?
Were you still down in the lower lot, or was it up?
Yeah, I think you were walking.
You were doing Jurassic World before we left,
and I went out the...
Was this a drug sniffing dog?
I think it was a bomb sniffing dog.
It was like a security dog.
Well, it could have been.
It was going for your cheek,
because he knows you always got big old blunts rolled up in there.
Bomb sniffing dogs don't care about grass, okay?
But he was so friendly.
How do you know he was a bomb sniffing dog?
I feel like that's what the security guy said.
He feels like...
Look, I don't know.
I don't know what they have there.
Bomb sniffing dogs are going to go nuts in the Super Nintendo world.
The Bowser's Castle is full of them.
This dog knocked my ass over,
and everyone ran over and helped me out,
but the dog just didn't.
He was just smiling.
And you were like, no, no, no.
It's okay. I understand.
I understand.
Please just have him shot.
Oh, God.
Never.
I mean, please punch me with...
Please headbutt me again, Marmaduke.
Please, sir.
Jason doesn't want the dog shot,
but something tells me Stitch might...
What would the character of Stitch want to happen to the dog?
I don't like sharing attention.
He's a dead man.
There we go.
The character of Stitch allows Jason to vent through the darkness.
If you get too angry,
your extra arms are going to pop out and grab guns.
I'll take care of that job myself.
Is this one of these where I forgot about this,
or was I really not around?
You weren't there.
You went into the park.
Michael, you have never forgotten one thing
that has ever happened to Jason in his life.
Well, it's a lie.
It's a lie, I guess.
I wanted to go back.
No way you would forget.
I wanted to go back to City Walk to buy Megan t-shirts.
And I proved right.
Megan, too, come in a few months.
I proved right.
The bitch is back.
Your desire for a shirt proved that it merited a sequel.
She's ahead.
What did she say in the trailer?
Hold on to your vaginas?
Does she say so?
Yeah, Megan's sassy now.
So are we green lighting the sequel or not?
I don't know.
The movie did well,
but merch sales just aren't what we want them to be.
It feels like one more t-shirt might push us over the edge.
That large man or small,
that large child or small man just bought two XXL t-shirts.
You believe you were mistaken for a large child?
I am always so glad that that's the case.
Facial hair helps.
That's true.
You shouldn't, what, you there.
You shouldn't be, you shouldn't be lighting up that big old blood.
You are about nine years old.
Large, but nine years old.
Oh, he started doing the Megan TikTok.
He started doing the arms and the kick.
It'd be fun to see Stitch do that with all his arms.
Let's stay focused on, yes,
now that we've made it back to Jason doing the voice.
If you're a newer listener,
you might not know the runner that's been occurring for,
I'm going to guess, 13 years,
which is Jason doing a Stitch impression.
A really bad Stitch impression.
Well, you know what, though?
I think it has improved as time has gone on.
I think it's in a better place now than the first,
because what I recall was an early attempt at it.
There was this hacking maniacal,
oh, that beats family,
where you're like,
as if acid is dissolving your lungs as you're trying to speak.
Yeah, I'm hurting myself.
But I think it has improved.
And I'm just wondering what else there is to do with Stitch
while we're...
Okay, I mean, in terms of role-playing,
anything like...
First of all, let's just liften it.
Can I speak to Stitch?
Stitch, is he still here?
Of course. I'm always happy to talk.
Very good.
What do you remember about the day, November 16th, 2004?
Oh, boy.
Well, you know, the limiter was taken off.
I was just allowed to create.
I was just allowed to do my thing, man.
Anybody ever tell you you sound a little bit like Wolfman?
I mean, at the top of my game.
Oh, Wolfman?
Me and him go way back.
Yeah, baby.
You sound cool like you did.
You sound like a guy who'd be kind of in, like,
a road trip in posse with Burt Reynolds and Dom Delaouise.
Oh, man, they were the best.
Oh, you go back to those guys.
Oh, yeah, I used to go...
and go to a posse big boy with that other L.A. DJ.
What's his name?
That other L.A. DJ.
But after it happened, I mean, like, did you feel...
Was there any guilt? Was there any remorse?
Were you proud of what you had done to the castle?
I had a lot of fun.
Producers, operations,
they really should have looked it out for that wedding thing.
I sent a very large gift.
You know, physical media residuals used to be a big deal.
Oh, yeah, and you're in the time you were coming up, absolutely.
Yeah, I sent an ice card to the briding room.
Well, look at that.
So it doesn't matter if they TP the toilet paper.
You made it right.
And you didn't try to bite one of the bridesmaids?
No, I bit their tires, so...
Oh, man.
Four tires, four bites.
Well, you gotta bite something, so it's good you didn't attack a person,
but you got your prankster energy out.
Was there anything going on with security?
Did they give you any flack
or did you escape as quickly as you could?
No, they were cool, man.
I learned all their deans.
I always sent them chocolate at Christmas.
They were the hardest-working guys at theme park.
That's good.
You look out for the working man.
You're a union guy.
You look out for...
Yeah, I mean, I would say after...
I mean, they're one now.
I'm in equity.
That's great, that's great.
Obviously, when they started doing the TV show
and the directivity sequel, I got a producer credit.
Oh, that's good.
Of course, you didn't do it yourself, because why would you?
You got bigger fish to fry.
Well, they let me direct Leo in Stitch 3 back in action.
Every kind day, I just grinded that one out.
They just stole back in action.
I remember, that was barely animated, I feel like.
They just told the story of what happened in the first movie
just through still storybook images for 65 minutes.
Yeah, it was a lot of photographs of doodles.
It wasn't even animatics.
But we tried our best with what we had.
Any memory, because your movie got green-lit in this day.
2004 was still in Michael Eisner's regime.
Any memories of him?
Great guy, great guy.
That's what I like to hear.
I got really muddy in Burbank because of those rainy winters.
So he let me rinse off.
Famously, yes.
Yeah, for like three days, yeah.
He let me rinse.
I got real muddy.
Played around a lot.
He let me rinse off in his private shower or bathroom.
He let you use the shower.
I would wish he would let me rinse off once.
That was kind of my dream.
Yeah.
I want to rinse off.
I also took a bite of one of the seven dwarfs
from the Dean Disney building.
Oh, no.
Oh, geez.
Those are huge, too.
It probably didn't even make that much of a dent, at least.
I don't want to say they led me to it,
but there was a trail of chili dogs.
And I don't know.
We didn't talk about content much back then,
but I think they wanted it.
You know, it went in the vault.
It went in the vault.
They needed some new promotional pictures, so.
Would you recommend, if you were going to bite something
like a tire or a concrete dwarf, do you ever add chili to it
just to make it more palatable?
Oh, sometimes.
But, you know, it's kind of a work thing.
You know, you got a clock in and out.
You feel like sometimes you eat stuff
just because people expect it of you?
Like, you're not even always in the mood?
I mean, when I do sign it, like, do conventions and stuff,
you're not always at 100%.
But people came out, and they took their time
and earned their money, so you want to give them a good show.
This is great.
OK, well, he appreciates.
He puts his fans first, even if you aren't on the fence.
Yeah, trying to be a man of the people.
I mean, I remember when I was just starting out,
I had some hard times.
You know, you do a lot of odd jobs out here.
See, not everybody would have that perspective.
I mean, yeah.
Oh, yeah, it's really easy to lose yourself
in the entertainment industry.
I mean, I've heard those, the gargoyles in Hunchback,
they're fucking assholes.
And where do they get, you know,
you're way more popular than them.
Yeah, I don't know.
They never, they were kind of high-and-by guys,
you know, at the Christmas parties.
This is really, why aren't they, how do they possibly feel
like they earned 12?
I don't know.
That bothers me.
Well, you're, you know, yeah, you're straight and narrow.
Stitch, I heard that you were a PA on American Gladiators
when you came out here for the first time.
Oh, yeah.
One of the numerous remakes.
Oh, yeah, yeah, of course.
Not the original, but...
No.
He tried it again in the late 90s,
and then I got Lilo and Stitch.
Like, it was a real lucky thing.
You got to start somewhere.
You know, Sebastian Stan talked about,
he almost threw in the towel,
but then he got $65,000 in residuals
from a hot tub time machine.
He did just say that.
Yeah, I saw that article.
It was pretty cool.
He's a real straight shooter.
Mm-hmm.
He's good.
Yeah, tell them something.
Connected to the roots, just like you.
If you had to, if you were allowed to cause
a little bit of mischief or mayhem
at another big theme park landmark,
anything you had eyes on,
anything beyond the toilet paper on the castle?
Well, I think I could hide an epic universe
in pretty much any land,
like pretty much any portal.
Yeah, well, they don't have all the kinks figured out yet,
so yeah, you could just scurry away quite easily.
Yeah, I mean, that's kind of natural.
You open a new theme park and you open a new hotel.
You got to recharge the key.
You got to get new keys.
Sure, sure, yeah.
So, like, I don't know,
maybe overturn a bucket of chili
or two or six on top of the Kronos.
Oh, yeah.
I might just swap one of those.
I might just make myself a big circle,
replace Mario or whatever.
Oh, just punch one out,
and then you're hanging around upside down
doing circles and stuff.
Yeah, but just when they start to suspect
something is off, I'll replace it.
Wow.
You know, it's what they call fun gaslighting.
It's just having a little laugh.
They do call it that.
I have heard fun gaslighting as a term.
That's what I, whenever I do it,
that's how I like to think of it, you know.
Sure.
Well, you've never done it before.
Oh.
See, that was fun gaslighting.
You started a question.
Oh, that was an example of fun gaslighting.
Yeah, you started a question.
Wow, that was pretty good.
Yeah, yeah.
You proved by example.
Well, look, I mean, thank you for being here.
I didn't realize you'd end up being a guest for so long,
but this has been great.
I guess you survived podcasts,
the ride, the second,
Stitch, anything you'd like to plug?
I know you got a movie coming out this week,
but I don't know how much you even relate to the movie.
You know, I was kind of more of a supervising role
when producing Lilo and Stitch, you know.
Oh, this is animated Stitch.
This isn't the CGI Stitch.
Yeah, yeah, I like the CG guy.
Right, right, right.
But didn't you, like, did New Stitch meet with you,
like, when Billy Dee met Donald Glover?
Hung out of the, tongue out of the time.
I'm in a couple scenes, I am.
You know, that movie, sometimes Donald Glover,
sometimes 21 Savage in the New Lilo and Stitch,
sometimes it's Stitch, sometimes it's me.
Wow, well, that's fun gaslighting.
That's keeping people on their toes.
All right, well, yeah, check it out in theaters,
and thank you for being here.
I guess we'll summon Jason.
Hey, check it out, and go see it instead of the live action
how they train your dragon.
I don't get any residuals for that.
But I could say I am hidden in one shot,
because I was just kind of in the soundstage next door one day.
What, geez, just blending in with dragons.
What a scamp.
Hey, we love you.
Thanks for being here.
Thank you.
Wow, that came better than Jason, I think.
Oh, that was nice.
That was a little break for me.
Better than what?
Oh, no, I didn't see anything.
You fun gaslighting me?
No, no, I was just regular.
You've done that before.
No, regular gaslighting.
Oh, OK.
I have regular gaslighting.
I have one more.
Now, I know I just, well, Stitch was here for a little bit,
but you do an impression of Stitch,
which I think we all can agree is a remarkable impression.
Oh, sure.
But one thing, I feel like you've spoken before
of feeling insecure in your ability to do different voices,
and you once said that you didn't even want to try to do this voice
or that voice until you paid Griffin money to voice coach you.
That's right.
Well, I just advice from friends who are, you know,
a little more experienced.
They work out and eat the squirrel.
That's true, and I'm not going to stop you from handing cash to Griffin.
Scott Pilgrim is like a funny side character, Scott Pilgrim.
No, no, no, I know, and I encourage this.
I think you should feed as much money to Griffin as possible to get voice lessons.
But I think even without the expert Griffin training,
I think there is a way, what I would love to do is just to figure out
if we can like make a little, because this is a problem we all,
you know, we start doing one voice and realize we're just doing the same.
How many voices we do just fall right into Leno.
You know, this happens to us.
The whole thing is like trying to make a little space between voices.
So what I've, I have a list of a couple of characters
who sound a little bit similar to Stitch.
Oh, thanks.
And I'm curious to hear if you could kind of like create a little distance
and make, like, see if you can get them to be a little bit different from each other.
OK, let me have a sip of water.
Yes, yeah, you might need that because we're getting a little bit,
we're getting a little scratchy here.
Oh, man, you're really putting him through the wringer here today.
He's doing a bang up job, I would say.
I didn't say anything about the quality of the job.
I'm just saying that he's really being tested today.
No, no, no, a little podcast or obstacle course.
OK, so let's just calibrate to Stitch, maybe with a classic Ohana means family.
Ohana means family.
Good, great, improved.
We see how far it's come.
But then this is a little difficult.
How would you, could you pivot to Gollum?
Ooh.
My precious.
And I think that, I think if you went...
So a little close.
Yeah, yeah, well, somewhere in, like, I don't know if that's what Gollum sounds like.
Is it more like that?
Oh, maybe.
I'd have to listen to it.
I don't think he's as gruff, isn't he?
Is he more like...
Whispering.
My precious.
That felt good.
Well, you know what it felt like a little bit is...
Peter Lorre.
Peter Lorre, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, is he on your list?
He's not on the list.
No, he should have been.
He definitely should have been on the list.
Yeah.
It's a real, it's a family tree.
All these things are only two degrees apart.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
He's more like Rick.
Wait, that's true.
You have to put a little bit of, like, what nationalities?
Oh, I don't know, actually.
I just think Wren for men and Stimpy is what I think, too.
Oh, wait, okay.
We're also not on my list, but Wren.
Do you think you could do Wren?
Stimpy, you idiot, you could say.
Stimpy, you idiot.
Okay.
That's pretty good, yeah.
Yeah, that's not bad.
Pretty good.
Okay, well, I wonder, okay, then this might start, this might start hitting it into another
direction.
Baby animal from Muppet Babies.
Oh, boy.
Oh, gosh.
I don't even remember.
What does he say at the end?
He says, go bye-bye?
He says, go bye-bye at the end of the episodes.
Go bye-bye.
Now, that's pretty good.
That's not bad.
Actually, what that does is kind of prove that maybe.
Bye-bye.
Isn't it a little more like that?
It's a little more high-pitched because it's a baby.
Isn't it more girl?
All right, well, if you, because I thought that was pretty close, if he takes his time
with it a little more.
Yeah.
Muppet Babies.
He needs to get in the whole vibe of the song, I think.
Does he say a line in the opening song?
Does he?
I don't know.
I don't recall.
When your town looks good.
Just close your eyes and make believe.
Is that him or is that?
I don't know.
That's one of the other ones.
I don't recall.
When your town looks good.
Just close your eyes and make believe.
You'll be anywhere.
Is that him or is that?
I don't know.
That's one of the other ones I want to say.
No, close your eyes and make believe is Miss Piggy, I believe.
Some of them are a little, I mean, obviously Piggy is different, but some of them are a
little similar.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Some of them, I mean, probably some of them are done by the same people.
And now I don't remember if, I feel like maybe, I know Dave Collier was some, but I feel
like Howie Mandel might have been somebody in there.
But here's, this was a Howie Mandel.
Do you feel like you could do Gizmo from Gremlins?
Oh, Gizmo.
Yeah, what is Gizmo?
Does Gizmo talk that much?
I mean, I know he dances.
He doesn't really say words.
It's kind of more of a, it's sort of a like-
That's a Howie Mandel voice.
Just kind of a like-
Beep, beep, beep.
Oh, that's, yes.
I think he would go higher.
Beep, beep, beep.
Well, there we go.
I'm coaching him too much.
That's, no, no, no.
I think that's fair game.
And it's very kind of you to do it for free instead of the vast amount of money.
We know Griffin is going to-
He should pay.
He should pay me.
Greedy Griffin, we call him.
He owes me.
Jason owes me.
Well, I probably do owe you meals and drinks over the years, but I've tried to make up
for that.
You never paid me for that TV.
You're still watching.
All right.
Well, you said I could have.
You said it was going in the garbage.
Yeah, but re-between the lines.
I wanted $500 for that TV.
Oh, come on.
You're supposed to just hand me a wad of cash.
You wanted how much?
$500, all singles.
Well, I could have gotten a brand new one for that price.
No, I wanted-
Single, like unmarked, non-
Singles.
$500.
In a bag, re-between the lines.
Saying it was a gift was fun gaslighting, or perhaps not fun gaslighting.
Well, now that the outcome is no money for me, it wasn't fun.
I thought it was fun, but it wasn't.
If you had to stay in the high-pitched zone, do you think you could take it to Baby Dinosaur?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I watched so many hours of that.
Baby Sinclair?
Yeah, Baby Sinclair.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
Yeah.
I feel like I do Baby Sinclair pretty regularly around the house.
Around the house?
Around the house, yeah.
Of course he-
Not the mama.
That just seemed a lot like you.
I'm the baby, gotta love me, great big eyes, and I'm really kind of late.
This is just, what we're finding is that this is just Jason and that he just, like,
he sings that nod in character to Jane.
Of course he does.
Oh, Garfield, Jane.
I'm the hubby, gotta love me.
Right.
Yeah?
Yeah, but he says-
Why the Lord says so?
But he says, baby, you know.
He says, I'm the baby.
Oh, I know.
I fucking-
I'm the baby, baby hubby.
There's been that, oh my God, there's been that five-minute stretch of every episode
lately where we have to do, I'm the little baby hubby, the little baby hubby dino boy.
He's the baby hubby dino boy.
We all have our process to prepare, you know.
It always seems like it's fresh too, you know, of all the bits that have been running to
the ground on the show.
The little, I'm a little hubby dino boy.
Always feels good to me.
It always feels-
Well, it is fresh.
I only got married like a month ago.
Well, that's true.
That's a great, by the way, plot development for our characters on this show.
That I got married?
And I want to thank you for doing that.
Because that adds more dimension to your character as far as when you're following our lives,
which to some degree is a reality show.
Yeah.
I suppose so.
And we know some things.
We know that Jane is the blushing bride.
We know that he's a little hubby baby boy.
I love him.
Little stinky baby.
Stinky baby hubby boy.
If you are a listener who is charmed by Jason saying, I'm the little stinky hubby boy, can
you write an essay explaining why?
Or is it more of just a feeling you get?
Is it just really, you can't even-
Like you couldn't put it into words.
You couldn't put it into words.
It's just a warm feeling you get when he says, I'm a little stinky hubby boy.
Little dino stinky.
Hey, whatever your preferred platform, the comments of this post, Reddit, Discord, Facebook,
whatever makes you most comfortable.
Yeah.
Okay.
You can comment anywhere you want.
This is sincere.
Reach out to the audience.
Oh yeah.
I don't know.
I'm formatting.
You know, sometimes it's a pain in the ass when you post in those.
No way.
I'm setting up a Google Forms for this and that is the only acceptable place for answers
to this question.
1,000 words minimum.
I don't buy this.
It's a feeling thing.
Professors got over here.
Highway.
Explain it to me.
He got tenure and he got more strength.
Proper spacing.
Yeah.
Well, that was a good, thank you for, that was, I think that was an excellent, I think
what that proved is that you don't need Griffin.
You don't need the thousands of dollars going into Griffin's pocket.
I think you created some space between all of those voices and made some unique voices
there.
I thought it was fun and impressive.
Animation casting, I live in Burbank and I own any number of microphones, so.
Not any.
I own 700 microphones.
No, I meant more like three or four, I guess.
Not any number.
Sounds like a Condenser bike, a USB mic.
I own a very specific number of microphones.
I own not any number.
I own one number of microphones.
Three.
There's built-in ones on the phone and the iPad.
Phones don't count.
You're going to put it on your phone.
Well, you need a proof of concept.
It's good enough.
You know.
Through the phone.
I also want to say that there's a weird tie together in the Disney family of this
infamous date, November 16th, 2004, that this was also the birthdate of a now treasured
member of the Disney family, the actor Jack Champion.
We know Jack Champion.
Jack Champion is, of course, the actor who portrayed Spider in Avatar, The Way of Water,
and well, again, in Avatar.
The young man.
Fire and Ash.
Yes.
There's a little human boy who is raised maybe to the objections of Naturi by the Sully
family.
Ironically, a rare human in an otherworldly realm, kind of the inverse of Stitch, but
yet both of them create a lot of mischief.
Fish out of water.
On their respective planets.
Are you saying that they should do like an alien encounter with Spider in the tube?
Oh, yeah.
Wait, yeah.
Or Spider messes with the castle?
He's a human boy.
Because he can crawl up cliff walls just like Stitch.
Right.
That's one of his talents.
Yep.
Yeah.
Or he could get up there on a banshee.
And some Avatar takeover of Magic Kingdom.
It's filling into that.
Wow.
Spider showing up in a tube.
Well, I would say even the Tree of Life.
He can skitter all around the Tree of Life.
And what if in California Adventure it's Avatar night and you replace a Spider-Man with
Spider animatronic?
Oh, yeah.
Spider, comma, man.
Stuntronic.
Yeah.
Spider.
Stitch.
You know.
The words are similar.
Because the humans were trying to get him to side with them, but he wouldn't.
And as James Cameron has said, the fire people side with humans and the water people, they
come to conflict.
Oh, these fire people.
I'm scared of these fire people.
You know, what would be really funny about the Spider Stuntronic at California Adventure
is that if you were far enough away, it would look like a naked human man.
Yeah.
So it would look like a naked man was flying.
He's kind of a Mowgli, yeah.
And if you can't really tell that the loin cloth is, and if it's just flopping around,
it might just seem like, yeah, you might just think that's junk hanging out.
If you're on the Annual Passholder Terrace and you're just sipping some wine, you look
over there, you're like, isn't he hurling a naked man through the air every 25 minutes?
Must be a punishment.
It must be a teen who tried to get out of a ride.
I guess what they do now is hook him up to a rope device and flail him across the park.
They've got a real medieval torture situation.
Jesus, no matter how much we drink up here, let's behave.
Right.
Don't want to get flung around.
Malfunctions and the spider thing goes so far into the terrace, the naked man hits the
table.
Ah, it lands right on top of you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Flies in the wrong direction.
Right.
One of his dreadlocks got in my mouth.
Well, they used to do that drink sampler that was like flavors of the sea, plant, and earth.
There was something along those lines.
The secret menu item is a spider.
Is a nada and you think, oh, what's that?
What kind of drink is that?
You'll see.
It actually is a big stunt metronic being flung into your face.
And if you meet the close up meet and greet spider, he's stinky.
Well, that's for you.
Yeah.
That's what you like.
This is, we've had our fun.
I think, I don't know how much I can do a podcast where the word stinky is said every
single episode.
I think this might be an allergic reaction as we've discussed.
I think I might be stinkied out.
But is the audience, and again, submit to the Google Forms.
Tell me if you are stinkied out.
But for the podcast that writes little stinker, Jason Sheridan, to say stinky, I think they're
going to love it.
I think they're loving it.
I guess so.
I think it's unanimous.
If I had to pick, I'm picking stinker.
Me too.
Strangely, I have no problem with the word stinker.
But the word stinky, I just, I think it has time.
I don't know how much stinky talk I can keep having.
That's fine.
Look, I got a very sensitive smell.
Sometimes I'm very sensitive to stuff.
So maybe I think of stinky too much.
You're speaking your truth.
Yes, absolutely.
Always try to do that podcasting, baby.
Always try to do that.
Always try to do that when I'm podcasting, baby.
That I would like to say, an image of Jason with his catchphrase underneath, always trying
to do that podcasting, baby.
And I have a thumbs up and like three to four assorted microphones around me.
So many.
Oh, and if you look, the fine print on it says any number of.
Any number of.
One of these is kind of broken.
One hand doing thumbs up, the other part like partially doing the Megan dance.
Oh, yeah.
Yep.
Well, we could have thought of a great shirt there.
I think we really covered everything that there is to cover about this thing that happened
one day.
Did we?
That's sort of.
Well, I mean, there's not too much other than what you're looking at.
I missed really quick.
There was also a TV ad that.
Oh, I didn't see this.
Yes.
It was part of it.
So it was it was actually a nod to a broader campaign that's a kind of produced TV ad in
which here we get to see Cinderella and Prince Charming actually reacting to Stitch taking
over the castle.
He just that was him.
He just threw a big thrown out and it shattered on the ground throne.
There's human actors playing Cinderella.
It's like full feasts.
He threw.
Yeah, I guess Cinderella and Prince Charming were going to shout out a gigantic turkey
just themselves.
Took so much work with their travel agent, but they finally got a reservation at Cinderella's
royal table.
Cinderella would be having it.
Yeah.
God, I guess not.
Geez.
Ah, much better.
Stitch is taking over.
So strap yourselves in for Disney's most experience.
Check out Stitch's great escape.
New at the Magic Kingdom.
Wow.
My goodness.
That's not yours, is it?
That was he ate the glass slipper glass slipper.
This is I like this, though.
This is like because I think they today they know they would never.
For some well, boring reason, they would never.
He's flipping the script on your sacred cows.
You know, really?
Like, what do you think is this is too precious?
That's that's a stitch.
Cinderella is no elite to him.
They're all they're all just human beings to him and he doesn't understand human beings.
Doesn't bother him at all.
Yeah, he ate her shoe and then he's hanging out and kind of he like turns wherever they
live into like he put up a he put up a dirt board.
Wait a minute.
I like stitches.
I want to go to this place.
Stitch's wing of the castle.
That's got like a there's a dart board and a bunch of toilet paper and a little like
old TV like you'd want to have in your chill basement and then like a foosball table
and a poster that says surfers point.
This is actually I would have a coherent decorating for him being a little monster guy.
There's quite a lot of surfing in that in that first movie.
I'm just amazed that he like hung a poster and hung it straight.
You have to be like disciplined to.
But I guess as we you know, we talked to him a little while ago.
He is he was like surprisingly lucid.
I thought.
Yeah, he was really a good decorator.
And frankly, I'd rather be in his little nook than I'd be when I didn't be in the boring
regular old castle talking to him was like when you like Wiley Coyote would do that like
addressing the camera and all of a sudden he was very articulate and knew a lot about
or like when the gremlin talks like Tony Randall.
That's true, too.
Mm hmm.
I love brain gremlin.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
Can you do that?
Can you do Tony Randall?
I think so.
So one year for Christmas, Jane got me a little brain gremlin like decorative cell.
A little bit of that had some that had a little juice.
This is I think you just got to push it further.
I think I think I think you made some progress in the voice avenue here and I want to hear
him.
But let's just let's like new impressions every time.
Sure.
Try to challenge yourself.
I'll buy one of those.
People in the news.
What's his name?
Hegseth.
Hegseth impression.
I don't know if I've ever heard Hegseth.
I feel like all I know about him is the energy is always just like everything is it's going
fine.
Okay.
Everything is fine.
I don't want to hear another shit from people saying we're not doing good.
Everything's going good.
Okay.
Like that's the energy.
You know what?
And that's what I like.
Maybe that's an impression you should keep doing because that is an energy very similar
to you, Mike Carlson.
Yeah.
There's a little more energy than my normal.
That's what happens when you show up 45 minutes late to a thing because you had high jinks
on the way.
That's true.
Everything's fine.
It's fine.
Except generally like I left a doll at home.
I didn't accidentally text war plans to like a reporter.
Like the stakes hopefully are a little different.
Yeah.
You texted a picture of the doll when you got home and then you gave it to them a week
or two later.
Yeah.
I haven't just been sending classified information on like a dirty internet line as they call
it or a dirty internet connection.
Not secured.
Well, scorching hagsets coming.
But so look forward to that.
And that's why you got to keep it tuned here to the second gate.
You survived podcast the ride.
If you want to dig even deeper, join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three where you get
one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
It feels like we need one more hit.
Like, can you just say goodbye?
Is Tony Randall?
Oh, either.
Yes.
You know what?
A dealer's choice.
Yeah.
Tony Randall or Stitch.
Well, hi, it's me.
Stitch is already up at Universal for FanFest Nights.
He got a comp I had to pay.
But goodbye, everyone.
Thank you for listening today.
Is that Tony Randall?
It's a perfect Tony Randall.
Perfect Tony Randall.
Was that an audio recording of Tony Randall?
Yeah.