Club 3
Boy, we really gotta come together this month, us Club 3 voters.
We gotta come together and find a way to combat the aggressive male energy of Bugman, right?
We gotta find a topic that makes sure that Club 3 doesn't have any of that over-the-top, that loud, masculine energy.
How do we do that? What should we pick? I don't know. How about restaurants?
Restaurants would be the way to... Let's punish Bugman by voting for his favorite thing in the world.
What happened to our little podcast?
We're all trying to figure it out. Where are we?
I don't know. As is always important to say, no rules have ever changed. No scales have ever been pressed.
This is democracy, and what is happening is... It is, yeah.
Well, it has been, to some extent, beyond our control, but that ends today.
Today is the day, and there's been a little bit of a shift in policy, and we have come to a decision about the future of Bugman in the Club 3 poll.
And we will reveal that at the end of the episode, so that'll be a little tease.
We're doing an executive order, I guess, and we'll see what the order says.
It has come to this. The whole thing is, it's been wanting to let democracy play itself out, and to not step in, and to just make a brash decision.
But duty calls, I guess.
Sometimes democracy doesn't work, quite frankly.
It doesn't work, and that's why you need a bold, powerful leader, three of them, frankly, to take initiative.
If there were descriptors for the three of us, I think people would say bold and powerful.
If you had to describe Mike, Scott, and Jason, the good boys, bold, I would say, boys found their presences to be extremely bold.
Sometimes too bold, honestly.
They describe so many bold interactions in their lives.
Oh my God, bold at every turn is generally how I describe my interactions in life.
Bold with women, bold with strangers, bold with people they run into.
That's who we are. What can I say?
Sometimes they say, uh, and yeah, and nervous laugh to cover the boldness.
And I appreciate that they do that, just as kind of a way to relate to me, the non-bold common man.
Right, right, right.
I'm so bold that a lot of times cars have pulled over when I have been on the sidewalk.
It went, hey, do you know how to get to this road?
I guess I just have one of those faces.
Wait a minute.
Where like, hey.
I was curious where that was going.
I was like, is this going to be like a you mama so fat joke?
Right.
But with I'm so bold.
I'm either walking along or I'm on the street and people are like, hey, do you know how to get back to the freeway?
And it's like, yeah, just go three blocks over and two blocks up.
You're saying that's bold.
But it's especially bold because he told him the wrong way to go.
That's how bold this guy is.
You know what I thought it was going to be?
I thought it almost felt like you were about to start rapping, like you were in a shuffle.
Like, I'm so bold, I'm here to say.
I'm so bold.
I like my tuna mac cold.
I think I was more like I am diminutive and non-threatening.
Oh, I see.
So they're like, hey, do you know where BJ's is?
Do you know where BJ's is?
Are people coming up to you on the side of the road and looking for BJ's?
Usually it's just.
Not that kind of BJ.
No, no, not that.
Not the Scripps like restaurant or something.
The home of the Pizooki is what you're talking about.
Well, yeah, it holds something for us.
It doesn't necessarily hold that weight for everyone.
The home of the Pizooki?
Yeah.
You're saying.
What's wrong with the people for whom it doesn't hold weight?
What's wrong with them?
I'm assuming they just haven't had one yet.
Were they at one that was too well done?
That's why they're asking you on the street.
Sir, you look like someone who might know the location of a dessert that will blow my mind.
That will change my life forever.
Would you be so bold as to point me in the direction of such a place?
Talking about a solid restaurant that has never got me sick before a restaurant that has only ever got me sick.
Oh, interesting.
OK, yeah.
Well, we'll talk about our history there because here's what we've been voted into.
Thanks to Josh Reese Club 3 suggestion.
The semi recently mentioned restaurants Hooters must have some weird lore.
There are some commenters who chimed in to talk about other things that are part of the weird lore that we can and should and will talk about.
When did we talk about this?
What episode did we talk about this?
I think it was that we were figuring out what to put in the fake office final floor.
Oh, by Frank Luntz's office.
Yeah, it's the discussion that led us to Frank Luntz's Oval Office in his house.
And I threw out, well, what about all of the many great fake Oval Offices across this nation,
such as the one in the George W. Bush Presidential Library, which is a view out the window of the sign of a Twin Peaks,
which is one of the chains of restaurants that we will talk about now.
I saw a comment say that that location has unfortunately closed so you can no longer look upon the best of America from the fake window of the best president of America.
But besides that, the chain is definitely on the grow.
Another one we'll talk about is not on the grow.
I watched an interview with the CEO of Twin Peaks.
Why did I do it?
You wanted to see what a bold CEO and leader was like.
I was searching for something.
I'm like, OK, maybe this will be funny.
And I'm like, after hearing him talk about the core principles and the fact that the beer is 29 degrees cold, that's our innovation when it comes to Twin Peaks.
And I was just like, oh, no, I just wasted 40 minutes of my life.
Was it 40 minutes?
I mean, I was doing some other things as well.
So it wasn't like I was solely focused on this man in his interview.
Yeah.
First off, it's so often men behind the scenes of these places and they're always either very boring or very nasty.
Like, it's gross.
There's so much gross stuff.
But it's also if there is a flaw in this episode concept.
And by the way, I think there's plenty here.
I found a lot of fun stuff.
I think some of the issue could be you do go like, oh, it's good.
Well, these chains are so like crazy and lascivious and to make the good boys have to talk about.
And then in reality, for the most part, they're kind of like boring restaurants.
And the people who run them are definitely boring, especially in the year 2025.
Yes. They're certainly just like, what are we doing here?
And Twin Peaks seems like kind of the post 2010 refresh of the concept to sort of take it to a slightly more homogenized place.
Because while they have sexy, skimpy outfits on the girls, it is like not, I would say, at the forefront of what's up with the chain as opposed to Hooters,
which rose in the 80s and 90s where it was absolutely the forefront.
That was the point of it.
But now I think what's happened to Hooters is that it's gotten sort of homogenized as well, sort of chasing the homogenization of all chain restaurants,
which is I think led them sort of to nowhere, almost like to a loss of identity.
That is my take.
That is like something you would hear on one of the different restaurant YouTube channels I watched and the different restaurant podcasters that were very excited to talk to the various CEOs.
While what you described sounds boring, this also sounds like the kind of thing you or any of us would do for entertainment all the time.
Talk about sort of what has happened with like a different chain restaurant is what you're saying?
Yes. Yeah. That's true.
Jason was just talking about he's excited to crack into his book about the rise and fall of Kmart.
That's true.
I mean, this is very much in our wheelhouse.
My favorite relaxing YouTube channels to put on is called Company Man.
And he tracks the rise and fall, like the rising fortunes and falling fortunes of different brands, restaurants, telecom brands, stores.
Company Man did a Hooters, correct?
They did two.
And is the verdict, would it be called a rise and fall?
Are we not yet?
Yeah.
Are we only at the kind of at the precipice of the fall?
Oh, no.
It's to be determined.
They declared Chapter 11 bankruptcy, and I don't know that that's the one you come back from.
Well, the thing is, though, I mean, yeah, it doesn't look good, but there are 400 locations worldwide.
Now, if they all disappear, then that's something.
And Chapter 11 is never.
Yeah, it doesn't sound good.
And that's this year, correct?
Jason, I'm going to speak your language here.
Marvel was in Chapter 11 and they sold.
Oh, maybe it's one.
It can be a restructuring.
And perhaps then, like, Universal makes a Hooters land because they make a deal with Hooters.
We might all be in line to see all the films of the Hooters cinematic universe.
It's possible, yes.
Soon enough.
So anything's possible.
Well, supposedly, in the one video, they talk about the founders, which still ran like 20 Hooters locations.
I think they branded the original Hooters.
Well, you're talking about the Hooters Six.
Yeah, from Clearwater.
The Hooters Six, I had to learn about as well.
The Hooters Six, which sound like they did something bad.
And I guess to some people they did.
I guess if you think about it.
They started the restaurant Hooters.
They started a restaurant where a bunch of old guys are like, hey, honey, how are you?
So, like, I guess you could say they were villains.
But the Hooters Six is what they called themselves, I believe.
Yes.
Pre-crimes.
No crimes.
Well, one key and one case.
Actually, one was absolved of the crime, that's what all.
A lot of lawsuits in the history of Hooters.
But, yeah, I don't know about these.
These guys all look like bad guys in the old arcade game Lethal Enforcers.
Oh, Lethal Enforcers.
Now I know what you mean.
Because they were like human beings that posed.
They were human beings and they all had like big hair mullets who were like.
That's really funny.
Sunglasses and stuff.
That is what the Hooters Six reminded me of.
The Hooters Six.
Well, yeah, you learn about Hooters Six if you go to the restaurant.
I went to the restaurant.
We'll talk about that.
But let me, I'll close out the Hooters Six, the people to whom we really owe the episode.
The men, which you believe.
The heroes, yeah.
To whom we owe the episode.
Yes, they opened the first Hooters in Clearwater, Florida on April Fool's Day 1983 as an inside
joke because they were sure they would fail at the venture.
Even going so far as placing tombstones bearing the names of the previous tenants who failed
in that location outside the entrance of their new establishment.
Did you guys come across pictures of the first Hooters in Clearwater, Florida?
I believe so.
It is.
Yeah.
It's been refreshed over the years.
Now it's kind of like a modern to code building.
Right, right.
In the early photos, it looks like three steps onto the porch and you will be in the ground.
Like that thing is just going to crack apart.
It is a truly cursed looking spot.
It looks like somebody like just assembled, like out of like a hurricane, like knocked
a bunch of patio furniture almost off or pieces of houses off and then somebody reassembled
Hooters with all of that raw material.
Or that it was accidentally reassembled by the hurricane itself.
It took pieces from many different buildings and just threw them together into a new one.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, no, it looks like such garbage.
One of the guys said, I had every intention of being broke in six months, but somehow
they were profitable in four.
This came out of the gate so huge.
So it worked out beyond their wildest dreams.
Let's name the Hooters six.
All right.
I'm willing to name one of the Hooters six.
I'm coming forward.
I don't care about the repercussions.
I don't care.
I don't care if Dennis Johnson, a brick mason by trade, buries me and then covers me up
with bricks.
I'm willing to take that.
I want Dennis named.
I want to speak Jason's language real quick.
The Hooters six is a lot like Spider-Man's foes, the Sinister six.
Oh, yeah.
Why don't we like, all right, this next guy, he's a liquor salesman.
He started selling a little more than that.
He started selling a bit of his skin.
It's Gil DeGion Antonio.
This guy is a retired service station owner.
I know what kind of service he liked.
Uncle Billy Ranieri.
Is his name Uncle Billy?
He's Uncle Billy.
He's an Uncle Billy.
Not Uncle Baby Billy, but Uncle Billy.
He was called that because he was 30 years older than all the rest of the men.
I don't know how the Hooters six met.
I don't know.
I don't want to know.
Yeah, I don't want to know.
Ken Wimmer.
He was a partner in a painting business.
Further questions?
No.
All right, that'll close out.
Ken Wimmer.
Yeah.
I looked into all these guys.
I was like, oh, there's going to be something big.
And they're like, no, a painter.
OK.
No, pretty much.
But that's the thing.
It's important to say they are not criminals.
This is not, they just started a restaurant.
They just started a restaurant where ladies would get like catcalls.
OK.
Yeah.
That's all I'm saying.
Well, they would basically encourage the catcalling.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
With the corporate, with like the attitude of the plate.
Waiting tables is like kind of a place where that happens to be, like it's a harrowing
job anyway.
Sure.
Well, yes.
Of course, it was a different time when they weren't thinking of things like this, I assume.
Sure.
They were just some fun loving painters and whatever the other thing was.
Well, yeah, he was in a, Ken Wimmer was in a painting business with L.D. Stewart, a painting
contrast contractor.
He was a college football player alongside Dick Butkus.
I know Dick Butkus.
His own name, kind of a sexual double entendre.
One of the greatest double entendres of all time, Dick Butkus.
He's a real life.
His own name is a living Bart prank phone call.
That's true.
I mean, I can't think of, there's some people with great names and that is just still the
top, I feel like, Dick Butkus.
Wow.
Just the top name ever named?
Well, in the genre of-
I have no disagreements.
In the genre, I guess you're right.
I was going to qualify it by saying it was like a prank call name, but I guess in all
names, it's the best name.
I can't think of a name.
My name is one of the most boring names, quite frankly.
Yeah.
Michael Carlson.
I don't mean to just agree, but you've done yourself no service saying it right after
Dick Butkus, the best name of all time.
Michael Carlson.
My parents almost called me Miles, and I wish that was the case.
I was almost Peterson.
The first name?
Yes, the first name.
I guess the way with it.
Peterson.
Really?
And then because I was a little wiener kid who took a briefcase to kindergarten, like
a brown briefcase-
Oh, you should have been Peterson.
My parents always say they were glad that that didn't end up being the name because
they could picture me showing up to kindergarten.
Hello, I'm Peterson T. Gardner.
Oh, boy, that is so good.
Encountering the worst six years of my life to follow.
That is so good.
At least you got out of your system before high school.
That is so good, though.
I can't get over how like what a perfect-
No, after that, I was only admired as a bold, cool guy.
Right.
I meant the briefcase, but yeah.
The briefcase, yeah, yeah.
Maybe I'd bring it back, though, as a professional to show him.
Sure.
That's about become my new podcast pseudonym, or when I start a business like the Hooters
6.
Are you in SAG, Scott?
I am in SAG.
Oh, so you already chose your name?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, I could shift it.
Yeah, you could change it, yeah.
I think.
Yeah, yeah.
Or I could change my SAG name to Peterson.
Or if you know ... Well, here's the ... I've completed this movie that I shot, and I'm
very proud of it, and I like it a lot.
If many horrible things happen, if some distributor buys it and says, like, fill it with fart
sounds and record scratches, and then you see it released under the name Peterson T. Gertner,
then you will know that it has been re-edited, not to my liking.
Okay, well, we'll keep an eye out.
Peterson will be the tell.
Well, if it's bought by the current Hooters Corporation, Hooters presents.
I don't know if I want to reveal the name yet, but-
Oh, yeah.
Does Hooters have a streaming service?
I wouldn't be shocked.
I wouldn't be shocked either.
It seems like-
A lot of their other ventures have gone under.
Hooters TV.
A lot of their other ventures have failed, so I doubt that would last.
There was a time, and that's the stuff that I'm the most excited to talk about, and the
stuff where I would reassure any listeners who have any trepidation at this point.
If there was any fear of, like, oh, no, no, in the restaurants episode, the guys are suddenly,
they're going to get so gross, this will be the point where they finally let out what
they've been hiding the whole time, as if we weren't just going to go, ooh, an airline,
ooh, a video game, ooh, Hootie the Owl.
An attempt to get into the past casual market.
Ooh, a weird ghost kitchen brand.
Hey, we're ourselves, no matter where your place is.
The rise of chicken wing popularity across the country.
Hank Hill?
Huh?
Was that Hank Hill?
There was a little Hank Hill in there.
I know he lives in there.
It was a very exciting time in the 90s.
It's just place after place, chain restaurants all added hot wings, you know?
You're saying that when the hot wings craze swept America?
There was, like, Hooters, that was one of their things.
They tapped into, like, specializing in wings.
They were one of the first big franchises that had wings.
Where wings was kind of the main.
Right.
The focus.
They didn't create wings, but they maybe popularized wings to some degree.
This is some of what the Hooters 6 were after, was that they wanted an establishment that
was filled with the good old 50s and 60s rock and roll music they love that makes you feel
good.
Can't object to that one.
Can't object to that part of it.
Can't object to the wings part.
They wanted, like, finger foods.
They wanted just, you know, stuff for dudes.
And the fine people of Buffalo had just the thing ready for them.
They had an idea wild enough it might just take wing.
I think that Hooters, I've been, like, Hooters maybe four times in my life.
That's more than me.
I'm only at two.
I think that eating Hooters wings early before I'd ever really had wings put me off wings
for years.
Because I think I had it when I was, like, 20 or 19 or maybe even a little earlier, but
I was just like, oh, yeah, the food here is awful.
I guess wings aren't so good.
Yeah, that had been, well, yeah, we should talk, and we could come back to the Hooters
6, but we should talk a little about our Hooters experience.
So what was that?
When was that?
Where was that?
I was really trying to track, because I've told this story before, a creepy high school
teacher tried to get all the graduating seniors to go with him to Hooters.
Yes.
And we knew that was weird.
We knew we didn't want to do that.
And you have to, I think that every time that this story comes up, you should reveal
another letter of his name.
Just drop the first.
T.
Okay.
And that's not, we don't know first or last.
His first name is Tom.
Oh, we got the whole name.
Wow.
Got the first name.
Geez, I feel like there's a rubric.
I suddenly, I just, you revealed the prize on the full board on Wheel of Fortune.
Well, that's a lot you gave us, but will you give us first initial?
Of the last name?
Yeah.
Yeah, E.
Wow, Tommy.
I mean, there's no way you can't figure the, if you really wanted to be like a Googler.
They called him Tommy the pervert.
I don't think, I don't even, I don't even know if I had gone to Hooters at that point.
It was, look, it was not, we were not going to places to feel comfortable.
We weren't going to feel comfortable around women at Hooters when we were 18.
We weren't comfortable around most of the women that didn't work at Hooters when we were 18.
But I think at some point early in college, it might have been in college that we went there and the food was awful.
And then maybe I went 10 years later in L.A. somewhere.
I don't really have a good memory.
Now, I will reveal now on Podcast the Ride.
Oh, boy.
That.
You were Tommy the whole time.
I know.
No, no.
Fucking Tyler Durden situation.
But you tried to pick a boring pseudonym to try to get away from being Tommy.
I caught this.
I didn't even realize I did this.
I caught this a couple of weeks ago.
We were doing the American Gladiators episode and we were talking about our Orlando trip.
And I was on I Drive wandering and I was like, I'm going to go eat somewhere funny.
I'm just for the show, for content.
And I started walking all the way down I Drive.
And I at a certain point hit kind of a wall, not a real wall, but a wall of just like I've walked too far.
And where did I end up at Hooters?
Wow.
And I ate at this Hooters restaurant.
You just did it.
I just did it.
Was this before the vote had even occurred?
This is before the vote even occurred.
You went to this hellish spot before.
I don't even want to run a reveal to the listeners that I had gone.
The listeners are going to hear that I went to Hooters.
I'm thinking this is more about me than it is about.
This is the kind of thing that's in your brain, Michael.
That's what I'm saying.
They'll know that I went to a restaurant that everyone in the world goes to.
I'm explaining my neuroses.
Haunted the cheat too because they've tried to go like we need to be more family friendly.
We need to be sexier.
We need to appeal to the guys with massive mental complexes about being in this room.
Here's the situation though.
Also part of it was there was absolutely nothing interesting happened.
The food was not good.
No one was in there.
I was polite to everyone.
I ate a sandwich and I left.
Part of it also was like not really a story there.
I didn't realize there was a Bahama Breeze past a bunch of trees.
Oh no.
Of course.
I would have much rather gone to the Bahama Breeze.
The next time you see a bunch of trees know that behind it might be Bahama Breeze.
Well that could be in part of what Jason's rap earlier.
We could put that in the same thing.
I'm so bold when I see trees I start thinking Bahama Breeze.
Right. That's good.
That's great.
My man when we have some downtime I'm going to download this app called Yelp and it's going to change your life.
Now he was trying to explore without his phone.
He's trying to get off his phone.
Trying to unhook from the device.
Trying to just be in the world.
Be on iDrive.
Discover.
Although I guarantee you were on your phone that entire time for 70 different reasons.
Yeah.
Well there were alerts happening for deals.
Now I admit I have been to a Twin Peaks in Las Vegas.
And I've been to a Tilted Kilt in San Diego.
You're emboldened by this.
You said those much louder than you said the Hooters.
Well now I've said my piece and now I'm just explaining to you the situation.
Twin Peaks I think.
Can you hear the sound?
Click click click click click click click.
That's everyone canceling their Club 3 memberships.
I understand they are disappointed in me.
I climbed the rock wall though.
Have I said this on the show?
That I climbed the Twin Peaks rock wall in Las Vegas?
I didn't know they had a rock wall in Las Vegas.
They have a rock wall in Las Vegas.
I was dared by my friends.
We went in and I climbed and competed against.
I was probably in my early 30s.
I competed against I'm sure someone who was 21.
Obviously she works at the restaurant.
So she knows how to climb.
This is like American Gladiators.
You went up against the pro.
It was very much like American Gladiators.
I could not climb for shit.
I couldn't make it past five feet in the air.
There's a video somewhere.
I'm desperately trying to find it.
There's a video of me looking like the biggest loser of all time.
I'm wearing like kind of like a dress shirt too.
I don't know why we were wearing a dress shirt.
I don't know if we went to like a show.
I guess we were doing like Normie Vegas.
I am struggling.
It's the most loserish video you've ever seen in your life.
Find it.
I exist and I'm trying to find it.
I think it's there somewhere.
Maybe a friend of mine has it.
Mike, rock wall climbing is incredibly difficult.
There's gyms just for it like that.
I understand that.
I had never done that before.
But at the very least I should have been able to get a couple more feet up.
I literally look like I can't get off the ground.
It is so humiliating.
It makes me want to try a rock wall not to say I could beat you.
I really don't know.
I think the only time I did anything similar was in like a really cheapo arcade in the Indian Empire.
Which might not reflect how actual rock walls are.
But you found it is like even though like you're helped by certain aspects it's still really difficult.
It was still really difficult.
But then my friend did it who doesn't have any rock wall experience and made it very far.
So that is really what.
Is that Strong Guy?
Or is that?
Or is that one of us weak guy?
It certainly is one of us weak guy.
There's no doubt about that.
But one of us strong.
I guess both my friends were stronger than me.
One of them was much stronger I think.
They're like arms and glutes and hip.
They might have just had a more developed muscle in the parts that are really flexed.
That's nice of you to say.
We know exactly what it is.
Higher T than Mike.
There I said it. They have higher T than Mike.
That's what I'm trying to do.
But it was maybe outside of being like a kid when you feel like you're humiliated.
It was the closest I've had that in my adult years.
To just feeling like oh my god.
I have just been destroyed here.
Not that there was a whole group looking.
But it's a big restaurant.
It's above the Taco Bell Cantina.
Is this in the area that I think I refer to it as the shit stack?
It's every crazy chain.
It's one of the big intersections of Las Vegas Boulevard.
So it straddles two floors of the shit stack.
Yes.
I've done that.
I don't know if I've said this before on the show.
My friend asked me to be his best man at the Tilted Kilt in San Diego.
We were walking.
This is no longer there in San Diego.
You know Jason knows this certain friend got into a verbal fight with Jason.
While we were looking for food the whole time.
We were really hungry.
We were both really hungry.
Overheated.
And rammy.
But they didn't know each other very well and all of a sudden they started arguing.
A fight of people who didn't know each other.
I was like oh no what's happening?
They were fine.
It was fine.
We're good friends nowadays.
When we do Wisconsin Dells he's coming on finally.
My longest friend.
Or one of my longest friends.
We'll do Wisconsin Dells and then he'll probably humiliate me in other ways.
Saying other things.
But we were walking and we were walking in the same zone.
It was not the same year.
But we were walking so long to find.
Comic Con you know in the radius of the convention center.
Everything is like 30 minute wait or something.
45 minute wait trying to eat.
But when you get in the outskirts by the Tilted Kilt.
It's a lot better.
That's where it is slash was.
I think.
Was.
We've eaten there together.
Yes.
Before with about 15, 20 other people.
Oh we did.
There was a big group.
You're right so I ate there at least twice.
So Tilted Kilt has not made me sick.
Cooters has.
Both times I've eaten there.
Which coincidentally also with like 10 to 20 people.
Okay oh giant groups.
Giant groups.
And so they were very nice.
That was fun.
No because I immediately got a stomach ache.
I was eating like wings.
And a side salad.
The one time I had just gotten over something.
So I'm drinking club soda.
And I just felt awful.
I will say.
I mean I don't think it's a surprise.
But I'm going into like these restaurants.
I feel like then.
I'm like well I'm going to be very on my bet.
I'm going to be very nice to everybody.
I'm not going to make anything weird.
I do have a complex now.
Not just because of climbing a rock wall.
But I do have a complex where I'm just like.
You are a normal man.
You just say thank you very much.
And you look straight ahead.
You are eating your meal.
Like I do have some of this in my head.
I swear.
Yeah I'm kind of right there with you.
Gentlemen how are we doing today?
I am doing quite well.
I am doing polite and I am doing respectful.
How are you and how is your inner life?
Too many questions.
It's like the BBC clip.
We're just normal men.
We're just innocent men.
I'm coming off normal.
When I'm in there.
The more you think about being normal.
It's like when you are super high.
And you think a lot about how I have to convince people.
That I am not super high.
That's how you level out to being extremely normal.
I always picture that like.
I'm going to be perceived.
And you see an older man talking to a cashier.
And it's clear he's talking a minute or two longer.
Than that cashier is interested.
I always have a paranoia in my head.
I'm talking too long.
I mean that's not just at Hooters.
That's in general where I'm like oh shit.
Did I just talk two or three minutes longer than I should have?
Well you know what I have seen you do it.
It's like where have I seen it?
When you're on a podcast and you're talking about CVS.
And apps and peels.
Actually that's more like two hours too long.
That's a safe space though.
I don't know if I'm coming from my droning on about something.
That's a different scenario.
Yes but I'm the cashier you see.
I guess that is true.
You are the cashier in that scenario.
But it's content.
Oh is that so?
It's a whole different story.
So I've been to the Hooters.
There was one in Santa Monica.
I don't know if it's still there.
It is not.
So we had a senior week in college.
A bunch of us went to Syracuse.
About an hour from Ithaca.
The bigger city.
And I think we were going to do this big mini golf.
And it was closed.
So we went to the Syracuse zoo.
Very sad.
Then we went.
What happened to that zoo?
It was just small and not kept up well.
Is it still there?
I don't know.
I will have to.
We're turned into wings at the Syracuse Hooters.
I mean it was just weird to see outdoor pens.
Because it's like.
It's always.
There's like two or three months of the year.
It's not cold in central New York.
And so we were at the Carousel Center.
At some point.
One of the top five biggest malls in America.
And then we went to the Hooters.
And then went to the minor league ballpark.
So the Syracuse.
Did you get sick?
Is that the sick one?
Yeah I did not feel well.
I did not.
You said it was trice and you were sick both times.
Do you have any idea the culprit?
Well I ordered wings both times.
I think one time I just had a side salad.
That probably got me sick.
Improperly washed produce.
How often do you think a year
you would get like stomach sick?
Well I'm carrying Pepto Bismol
in my pocket right now.
Not right now.
Like five years ago.
Ten years ago.
Because so many of your stories do revolve around
getting sick to your stomach.
It's usually just
poor combinations of overly rich food
and too much dairy.
Like banana and no other food.
That's like an allergy or something.
That's different.
That's something with the enzyme.
Just an enzyme.
It could not be more common banana enzymes.
I'd say like a few years ago.
Maybe like six times a year.
When you tell the stories on here
it does feel like it's like 30 times a year.
No it's just
yeah you heard about it.
If there are six yeah.
I don't know it'd be a tall order
for the listener to count them.
But I'm sure there have been 30 all told
over the years.
So maybe it just seems especially high.
But like Hooters was one where I'm like
eating the wing.
And I got the bone and wing.
Normally I'm a boneless man.
But I like just eating chicken nuggies
at restaurants.
Of course you say nuggies.
Or tendies.
I don't say nuggies regularly.
But I would say it.
I'm comfortable saying it.
I've recently been discussing out loud how I'm annoyed
by the word tendies.
I knew it was only a matter of time
before this would come up on the show.
I don't love tendies and nuggies.
I don't really love it.
In the next episode we record I'm a little
nuggie tendie boy.
Fire up Scott.
If I do it I'm going to be, I'll say this,
in the future if I ever say tendies or nuggies
I am being a little scamp.
So just know that.
But that's not where my heart lies.
That's your devilish alter ego.
Kind of like a bugman buzz buzz.
Yes that is.
I'm Mr. Nuggie.
Well my voice but I'm just like
5% turned up.
I'm Mr. Nuggie.
Maybe just like a positive.
I've found that a lot creepier than anything bugman's ever done.
What do you mean? I'm Mr. Nuggie.
I'm Mike's alter ego.
What are you talking about?
I'm just sweet Mr. Nuggie.
I'm going to kick open the door to Hooters and go
Hey everyone Mr. Nuggie's here.
You'll be the first arrested one in the last two years.
Get him out.
This guy's bervert.
It isn't dissimilar you're right.
It's a similar voice.
I will say this. It fits Jason's whole
thing better than yours.
Jason I'm like of course Nuggies.
You I'm like
send yourself to jail pervert.
He gets
to play in the sandbox too.
I can't have all the fun.
Come on in the sandy is finey.
Jason's trying to help me out here.
Nuggies isn't my vibe.
That is true.
Thank god one of these words has to be
not someone's vibe in this room.
If I'm feeling like a little scamp
maybe I will.
I don't know.
Tendies are a wonderful treat.
Am I a bigger scamp on the show than you are?
I think I am.
Do you think so?
I think my T is high.
I think I'm the biggest scamp.
I think I have regular T.
I think the T thing is mostly a bit.
But I think I am more of a scamp than you are on the show.
You might be but my zero might be set
to scamp.
Wait, what?
My baseline might be scamp.
Like if you were looking at a plane flying level
the level would be scamp.
This is a different Club 3 poll I guess.
Listeners, who's a bigger scamp?
Is it me or Jason as far as the show is concerned?
This is hard for me
to declare.
I just need further definition
of what scampishness entails.
Well, probably you want no part of it.
Fair enough.
Well, I regard certain
possible guests on the show
as being something of a scamp.
But I guess a lot of people would
violently disagree with that definition.
It's possible.
But to me, don't you think he has scampish qualities?
Wouldn't you?
Yes.
I'm trying to think what other...
Is there more like an impish?
Is impish and scampish similar?
I know that his pal Coca Peli
is a trickster god.
That's what I'm getting at.
But scamp...
I think you would think scamp is a little rascal.
And you would immediately think Jason.
But I sometimes feel like I'm actually
not all the time, but sometimes more of a scamp
than Jason is, at least in recent years.
Is this something you thought about middle of the night you wake up?
You know what? I think I'm a bigger scamp than Jason.
And I don't think I get credit for it.
Well, I do want credit. I do want glory for it.
I haven't seen one comment say that Mike
is the biggest scamp of the show.
It's just a thought I've had just right now actually.
In real time you're hearing it.
So I'm interested in what the listener thinks.
Well, that's the decision that we've come to.
There will be no Club 3 poll
after all the divisiveness, and the poll will just be
who is the biggest scamp.
Yeah, okay, sure.
Top 10 scamps episode.
Well, scamps in life, no.
Top 3 scamps on Podcast the Right Hosts.
As far as...
That's what a topic would be good.
So the food.
Hooters has always been bad food.
The other two, unmemorable as far as
a meal is concerned.
So my history...
I mean, I think it bears mentioning in all of our history
there has been a Burbank location
for many years.
I think in the whole time that we lived in or near Burbank,
but I don't think it sounds like none of us went.
This has been closed since 2019
and it was replaced by nothing.
It's sitting there.
And otherwise,
I guess there's a lot of empty spots in that zone.
But that specifically has been
the most nothing.
It's a weird spot in a parking garage.
It's right by the...
It's a tad depressing, I would say.
Next to a second parking garage.
Surrounded by nothing but parking garages and the freeway.
Close to the third
best AMC in a
five mile radius.
I believe on Podcast the Right,
years ago...
By the way, in a four block radius.
Five miles is way too big.
I believe on Podcast the Right,
I told the story of using the bathroom
in that Hooters.
Feeling weird about using the bathroom in that Hooters.
I think I told the story on this show
seven years ago.
That's the last time I was in there.
And when you said it, did I encounter you
with cashier energy?
Possibly.
I think I was made fun of
for the way in which
I told the story.
If it was seven years ago,
it's not a remarkable. I just remember being like,
I need to use the bathroom.
When does that ever stop stories from being told before?
That's true. It's Podcast the Right. I forgot where I was for a second.
Unremarkable. Tell it again.
I thought I was in a grocery store for a second.
I'm trying to figure out your
decision making process there.
Because there's a Barnes & Noble around the block.
I don't think of Barnes & Noble as a place to pee.
Really?
I know what you're saying. It's probably fine.
The telling with that one is you've got to go all the way
into the kids section.
Just use the bathroom and then leave?
Yeah, but I think I used the bathroom.
I think I was really stressed
about using the bathroom and not
paying for anything.
In general, you could just go to the mall.
There's so many places to pee.
Well, the mall bathrooms aren't really
convenient in the Burbank Town Center.
What are you talking about?
They're centrally located.
I've never had an issue peeing in the mall.
You can't imagine how much I've peed in the Burbank Town Center.
I know. It's a bit of a trek from there.
I'm trying to remember if I came out of the
I don't remember. I'll have to go back and look.
But now that I remember it, that is the last time I was in that Hooters
and it was not to eat.
I felt like I was on some sort of
I think I was made fun of because I was on a spy mission
to try to just get into the bathroom and get out.
I think that's what it was.
That sounds right because you operate
in all these scenarios. People are looking at me.
People are thinking that I'm not bold.
People are thinking that I'm not a scamp.
Everyone is thinking these thoughts
about me all the time.
Yes, I do think that. I think everyone
when I was in the Hooters in Orlando, I was like
everybody is thinking, what is this guy doing here?
Old guy in here.
Why is he here?
This guy is the first of all
the first single guy I've ever seen in a Hooters.
Second of all, the oldest guy I've ever seen.
This man, this old man
could not be more of a geezer.
Sometimes it feels like that.
There was no one in there.
Maybe that's really why I didn't want to bring it up.
I was coming into this episode
thinking the audience's thought is
let's have them talk about
restaurants like this because
they'll be so uncomfortable with everything.
Then I was coming in ready to go
jokes on you.
It's not actually uncomfortable to go to these places.
Cut to Mike with nothing but
very uncomfortable tales.
Thank you for fulfilling your end of the bargain.
I did. I'm being honest.
We went to the places.
I'm guilty of going into most of these places.
You are guilty.
Audience decide his prison sentence.
I still have a normie
heterosexual man chained somewhere
in the recesses of my mind.
I'm still guilty of going into the places.
But it always comes with
Send him to the same jail as the people
who run Spencer's Gifts.
That's where Mike belongs.
He should rot.
He walked into a Hooters, peed and left.
Prison!
I do want you to go to jail but it's because of
using the word nuggies.
Yeah, yeah.
This is the weird
thing that my brain does.
I'm trying to illustrate what I do
go through.
What it is, it's a heterosexual man
trying to go through a door.
Then you encounter the spirit of your mother
and then relive
30 years of awkward memories
and then try to go through the same door.
It's much tougher to go through the door.
That's a good way to put it.
I will say the going to Hooters
at iDrive was not
based on any sort of
heterosexual instinct.
It was literally like, I'm so tired.
I need to eat something for cheap.
I don't want to walk anymore on iDrive.
I'm just going to do it here and then leave.
Well, heterosexuals can be so tired, can they not?
I think they can, as far as I know.
I think we can all speak to that.
All three of us have been tired
heterosexuals.
That's true.
It's like, all right, you're going to act.
Everything's fine. Everything's all right.
You've heard my tales on this show many times.
There's plenty of times when everything is fine.
When I'm eating a big meal
at Liberty Tree Tavern, everything's fine.
I don't know. I do work
myself up in different ways.
I was on The Haunted Mansion several days
ago and I was thinking about how in our
live show, you said that you thought
that the old man who's shaking
because he's scared, is scared
because he's looking at you.
He's looking at you in the eye,
which I thought was an encapsulation of your
paranoia. This guy in a room
of a thousand ghosts is scared
of how you personally look.
And I was thinking about that right before I passed
the guy, and then as I passed him,
I saw his eyes don't line up
with any perspective that you could
possibly hit on the ride.
Why do you think he's looking at you?
That's funny. I've never
noticed that he's not looking.
Maybe he's looking at you because you're taller.
Except with your eyes, specifically.
Yeah, that's a good point. I don't know.
He's so intimate.
He's so close. He's not as close
as the dragon on
the Harry Potter ride.
I'm intimate with the dragon.
The intimacy on the Harry
Potter ride is a little bit
uncomfortable.
Wait a minute.
You were asking me how many stomach
aches would I get in a year.
But I'm realizing now, just from you mentioning
the Scooters meal and the Liberty Tree
Tavern meal.
Do you eat meals where
you're not uncomfortable?
Just in different ways.
His discomfort is he has
psychological aches.
He has brainty
aches. Absolutely, I do.
When we were younger,
I did watch Mike
eat a number of
ham sandwiches or peanut butter
sandwiches wrapped in a paper towel.
At once? Or just over the years?
Over the years.
You didn't invite Jason.
What are you up to? Want to watch me eat a bunch of ham sandwiches?
You don't think that's what we would have done
when we were younger? When you were young?
I like that too. When we were young.
When we were young.
2010? 2011?
But in lieu of
a plate timey.
Everyone's a mess
for various reasons.
I'm trying to tell
the listener what's in my head.
I'm trying to illustrate for them.
It's taken a lot of years and it's still not all out of there.
Oh no, it's not.
In that case, the perfect
episode was picked for letting stuff
spill out.
Let me say some of my experience. Never made it to
the Burbank location.
I just haven't been around them
terribly much to the point where I found it
unusual to see one when I was on a family trip
in 2011 when I was young.
I put it all together
because I was like
isn't there one that had
two giant wooden owls outside
of it that were built in the 80s
so they have that Disney
wood quality. I remember thinking
that's awesome. I did a street
view and I think they're gone which is unfortunate.
The big Dallas Hooters
owls were, oh Hootie I should say.
That's the name of the mascot.
So they had two Hooties.
What I remember about it is that that was
where I parked. That's where our whole family
parked in order to go take our tour
of Dealey Plaza and the book
depository.
So
that's a great, that's like
which is also Dallas.
So you can't see
you can no longer see the Hooters out of
the Twin Peaks out of George W. Bush's window.
You can pass by two
Hooties and go learn about the two shooters.
And all
the stuff painted on the ground
like this is where the car was.
This is where agents ran to.
X marks the spot.
And then I don't know if you've
ever been there but
you can go up in the depository and that's a museum
that you take a tour of and go see the window
and go see the spot. But then you go hang
around and then some guy will walk up to you like
hey you want to know the real deal?
And we followed this guy
around and he took us behind up the fence
and up on the grassy knoll and said
we're like does this cost money? And he said
no hey it's only you know pay me what you think
the information is worth at
the end of it. And we
did it and we followed him around for half an hour and I was kind of
creeped out but my dad was leading the charge because he
liked stuff like that. And then he finished and like
okay and my dad said alright well I'm going to go.
And the guy was like
what do you think that might have been worth?
Well he said I didn't have to pay you right? Okay
bye. And then we were like dad
what are you doing? He said what?
That was what he said. I'm like Jesus
we're with this weird guy talking about the
second shooter on the grassy knoll for two hours
and then you don't pay him anything?
I'm still mad at him about that. My breath
kind of like made that noise. I feel like
when you just finished that story. You follow
a guy around with uneasy energy
who said pay me what it feels
worth and then you don't do it
and then you do a walk of shame
I'm ashamed of my dad on the whole walk
back past the two hoodies. Whoa.
Perhaps it's no coincidence this was the last
family vacation I ever went on.
Whoa really?
I don't know if that had anything to do with it.
That's fascinating.
Maybe I'm done with
old mom and dad.
The weirdest thing of all was Donald
Sutherland doing his JFK
character.
He was working a lot at the time.
I don't understand.
He was method. He was in disguise.
Anyway so there's a random
Hooters memory.
Then I went to
I'm sure I talked about it on the show
but when I went to this Orlando bachelor party
a couple years ago we all went
to the Lake Buena Vista Hooters
which has stayed in my mind ever since
because you pass by it going back and forth to Disney
if you're at Universal and whatever. That's not on my drive.
It's not on my drive. No it's like
10 minutes away from Disney
Springs area and I
said this on the show but I was with a lift driver who
pointed out that like see that pond over there
by the Hooters? Somebody drowned in there.
So I will never
not think about that. Did he say it with like
glee? You said that right? Like it was a little bit like
see that? I don't think he was
happy about it but I think he thought it was interesting.
He definitely thought it was interesting. He wasn't like
thrilled. And you know what? He in general
saved me when I had very little phone battery
and took me a long way and I
made a point of tipping him well
just to say that I did not pick
up my dad's jeans when
you're with weird guys telling you about deaths.
You owe
the weird guys money.
The tipping just reminds me real quick because I took
a lift to I Drive
which would eventually be my
Hooters meal and I didn't
the lift driver spent the whole time telling me about how
he's getting like ripped off by the app
basically because it was some discounted
whatever fare because I looked
oh three dollars whatever blah blah
and he spent the whole time and I was
he's like trying to convince
me by like showing me and he got out of the car
to show me and give me a hug afterward.
And I was like
because like all lift
driver has to do and I'm not I'm not trying to pretend
I'm like a hero here. I'm just
like he goes he's like I go yeah oh yeah
I'll give you a good tip like
that sucks yeah that's crazy. Of course this app is
ripping you off or whatever but he wanted to show me
I guess he wouldn't approve it and he's showing me and
then he gives me a hug thanks so much man
and I was like okay that's nice but also I don't
need a stranger to hug me.
Wow. Really intense.
Really intense
and I don't he wasn't even hugging me because I like
he saw it I tipped him or whatever he was just like
he wanted to get out of the car show me
how bad he was getting ripped off but then he
wanted to hug me. He just needed a hug I guess.
And we were in the I was in the car for seven minutes.
It was enough time
for a hug to be married. Yes it was
enough I totally forgot that until this moment
that I got a hug before I did
my long wander down
iDrive alone. Wow we
well he must just he sensed
that you were somebody extremely comfortable
with personal interactions
physical interactions. Yeah yeah yeah. This guy seems like
a hugging guy. He got it
he got it loud and clear. He thought to himself
what I see here is a little
huggy boy.
Well that actually is my
lift name if you go into the app
that I'm little huggy boy so. But you had to do
it with a one and a four in there
because. Yeah yeah somebody Jason took a little
huggy boy the regular one. Yeah yeah yeah he
got his license plate too.
Yeah. Anyway so
that was one and I
in Orlando I had a good time
there and it was so boy
the pandemic had not been over for it wasn't over
then. The culture shock
of being in the Lake Buena Vista
Hooters was like wow I can't
believe this. So then but I felt
like I maybe hadn't had also I
it was just like we just ordered en masse
tons of appetizers and I found it all to be
pretty gross and not great.
Just like you know so
breading heavy fried heavy
I don't think I dug the pickles I don't think
I even dug the way I was not into the food.
It is a universally like hated
food. Yeah. I don't know that anyone
really I mean maybe
one person. Well let me say
where it went then. Yeah.
And I will say it with a little
trepidation because
here's what occurred.
Last week I would
say I went
I looked up where is the nearest Hooters that remains
to us here in Burbank.
It turns out to
be the Long Beach one near the
kind of weird. Wow that's the closest
one. That's the closest one.
There was consideration given to Costa
Mesa which had more of the old
school wood vibe which I'm going to say
I like I like the old what
was the one in Orlando. Is it still the wood vibe?
No it's a new like it looks like
it looks like they wish they were chilies
in there like a new chili. Yes that is
the new that's the thing it is just
like a it's yeah it's just that kind
of like shiny. Yeah.
I like I just want to say I like the
aesthetic of the old
brown. The wood yeah. It feels very
Florida boathouse
and I like the orange. I'm a fan
of the orange. It's like definitely
in your face and obnoxious
but it's just not a color combo you see
a lot and I'd rather be in the like heavily
orange one than just kind
of a like shiny wall looks
like Applebee's looks like everywhere.
I get I mean I'm a big orange fan.
My two favorite purple number one
orange number two. I always as a kid I would
say I want I would I would I wanted like
purple carpeting and orange walls.
That was not a request that was granted
by my parents unfortunately
and my wife probably
would not like that either
despite the fact that I wouldn't mind
pitched it recently recently
she doesn't want to live in the
laughing set.
I mean when you put it
that way maybe I could get away with it.
Would you mind if we knocked out the door and
replaced it with just nine tiny
splat shaped windows?
You could open them whenever you
want say a little pun and then shut it.
Then I'll go go dance.
So I do like orange.
Honestly I never really thought to
analyze the logo in a way but
I do like the orange.
I like that there's an inherent
80sness to it. I just like
the logo which is also kind of gone.
They've tried to rebrand. They've tried to get rid of
Hootie and I could feel a sense
and I think more and more they're just
if they're not doing well and if they're in Chapter 11 land
I think they're going to start re-embracing
the old vibe.
I don't know. It's a really
in the year 2025 I don't really know
how
there's no way Hooters starts now
and is this big.
It starts at a certain time and place
and now it's like
a shadow of its former self
in probably good ways
but I don't know
they go like hey we're back to the 80s
if that plays well in 2025.
I don't think in a huge way but I think
they would probably more often than not
find that people are fond of the old
logo of the old Hootie.
Well people
I'm interested in the Pizza Hut situation
because people I think
especially in the last decade have
shared their fondness for the
old aesthetic of Pizza Hut. I mean Pizza Hut
maybe of all the chain restaurants
going to as a kid other than maybe
like I'm trying to think maybe
old McDonald's because of the Play Play
stuff. Old Pizza Hut is just
so warm and comfortable.
The lamps, the glasses.
Everything about it.
You see the lamps in other restaurants that are not
pizza. That is how much people want.
Right. You can get a made
custom on Etsy. People make you a lamp
that says Pizza Hut.
Etsy or Aliexpress
you can find them.
I have a set of the
plastic cups.
Cups are good too.
Cups are good. They're like four or five bucks
online. So there was this chatter
of like we're going to bring some of this
back to Pizza Hut and that's already a couple years old
and I don't think that ever really came to fruition
but you know we used to
go to the Pizza Hut buffet in high school
in the old school Pizza Hut on
Roselle Road and man
it was
certainly dirty in there by that point. I feel
like when I was a kid and like the turtles coming out
of a shells tour was going on when you would go and get
the cassette tape and
whatever the big book. That's what I got
with the turtles on it.
That was a nicer Pizza Hut.
I forget where it was. At a certain point they
started decaying and then they changed Pizza Hut into
mostly to go at this point.
I don't think they have the room to do a lot of big
sit down. I think so many of them
are just other places. There was some rumor they were going to
reopen because there was one that still was open in
LA maybe a decade ago or less
and they were going to reopen. I heard there was chatter
of it but I don't think it ever came back.
But I do feel like, just to make my long
winded point, I do feel like
old aesthetics in restaurants
I think that
people are finding that people have fondness
for non
boring looking stuff.
Yeah because everything just looks
It's actually occurring to me that
the Hooters that I ended up going to in Long Beach
just is kind of like
it's pretty bland and it's
newly built. So there's like
the custom based one from Yelp photos
looked like dirty. I didn't really want to be there.
At least this is like a nice
you could feel the
establishment being kind of new but then
aesthetically it's kind of boring
and it's just like plain walls with
splashes of orange and I'm like
that's exactly what happened to god damn
Ralph Brennan's Jazz Kitchen.
That's the same aesthetic. They turned it
into a modern boring Hooters which
is such a shame. It was so
weird for something built in 2001
which is kind of when a lot of the blandening happened.
But that place had character
and whatever this is just stinks.
They gotta stop it. The Ralph Brennan's Jazz Kitchen
redo to me doesn't
even match the like
mid century modern or whatever retro
not retro future, retro look
of the rest of downtown
Disney now. It almost looks much more
boring than the like
retro like whatever the new places are building.
So I don't know why
they went with that. No it looks like a Ross
or something.
Non-aesthetic I associate
with like
Cajun Creole food
or even the upscale
like New Orleans restaurants.
There's no personality whatsoever anymore with it.
Let me show you what they do got
here though is that it didn't even occur
to me that what they have is big
giant orange water glasses
that are not dissimilar
from the red pizza cups.
I found this like ooh
this glass like it was worthy of a photo.
It's also right next to
a thing saying that it was
BOGO. I have learned.
BOGO Tuesday. It was
a BOGO day and then
a hazy IPA that I got that
was very nice.
So this is perhaps leading
to me saying that I had a really good time
at the Long Beach Shooters.
Maybe some of it was due to the company
that I was with. Everyone
take a deep breath. Hold something
next to you. Hold the hand of a loved one
when I tell you who I was at
the Hooters with. Was it your priest?
The new pope? The Chicago
pope? Leo?
Yes it was Father Loftus
who my mom said
what would Monsignor Loftus think about the video
that you just made? I decided
can I make it up to you with a trip to Hooters?
Right. Well was it my
teacher Tom from
school? Only a weird guy like Tommy
would join me for it. No.
I went to this establishment with
a friend of the show Bugmane
Puss Puss. I'm so sorry everyone
please don't burn
your phone. Don't take a lighter
to your phone because of what I have
just said. We will get through this. We'll discuss
it at the end.
This was a delightful time.
Maybe something about being
with now. Could you imagine?
Could you imagine that Bugmane
is perhaps a little bit more comfortable with these
places? It doesn't shock me
to hear that. Would you be shocked
to learn something that he told me while
we were there which is that he
over the years
has dated not one but two
Hooters calendar girls?
This is
not shocking to me at all.
Was one of them
Lynn Austin the original
calendar girl?
Not the original. I learned about Lynn Austin.
That's who everybody would be after.
I have some Lynn Austin.
Great.
He did make a point. I was like wow
calendar girls even. He said
white sock era.
This is the thing.
White socks are important.
That was when the uniform was a certain way.
That's what he's saying.
Then
it's time
for the actual meal.
When our Hooters
girl came up
whatever she was wearing left no impression
on me whatsoever. I don't know that
it even was revealing.
I just don't remember it. It is just
a total black hole.
They have gone away from
that vibe.
They got in trouble a few years
ago because they tried to
make the shorts
an even shorter
kind of shorts.
Then people who worked there or had
worked there were
complaining.
What year was that?
It was sooner than you'd expect.
It was the late 20s
or maybe early 20s.
Was it when we were older or when we were young?
Where's the demarcation?
There's a different line for each
of us when that occurred.
It was just like a totally
fine, it was a restaurant.
It was not
bizarre in the least.
For the first time, maybe the first of any
of our stories,
we did a BOGO boneless
wing situation. I loved
every bite of it. I actually
had a good food experience.
I was going to dance.
I think it felt like
juicier,
whiter meat.
I could feel the actual chicken in it.
That's not even
what I typically would eat.
It was that and curly fries, great beer,
frosty beer. I loved
everything. This is a bigger shock than
your dad not tipping that guy.
I was going to ask
what you found to eat.
Maybe that's part of it, but in general,
so rarely, if you ever
hear an anecdote about people eating at Hooters,
the food is awful.
I think it was the bug magic.
The bug knew how to do it. He buzzed his way
in there. I'll order for the table, he said.
Yeah, kind of.
He always
used to be with a server anywhere.
What's good here? You go to them and
she didn't steer us wrong with
anything.
I love Buffalo Wild Wings.
I think those are always pretty
consistent.
I am surprised that that
tasted good. For the first time, fully positive
experience, while it was not an old school vibe
of this location, it was this nice, breezy
zone.
It's this row of
full houses.
I just call them full houses.
I just like when a restaurant has its own.
It's not attached to anything else.
It's its own little house. Next to it is a different
little house.
What a row.
It's Hooters, Chili's, Outback, P.F. Chang's.
All in a row, all along the water.
And then we end that entire strip.
I looked it up because I was curious.
In an alternate universe, all of those restaurants
would just be a small portion of what
could have been Port Disney.
I looked on the map of Long Beach.
They have owned, if they had bought all of that stuff,
and that would have been a small part of a massive
hotel that was just part of that massive
complex they were going to do there.
That's right by the convention center in Long Beach?
Because the Queen Mary would have been
one of the centerpiece of it.
I've seen a couple New Japan wrestling shows down there.
If we do that, we always go to
that Chili's.
Justin Donaldson and I are
the biggest Chili's heads.
We always go to that one over there.
That's right.
What's the quality?
Because it's new-ish.
Chili's is always good.
I don't know what it is. It's the way they reheat
the food in the plastic bag.
I don't know what it is. Microwaving?
I'm aware that there is this recent improvement
in Chili's, and the fact that I did have a good
Hooters experience made me think, oh, this must be
what people are talking about with Chili's.
Because nobody's been saying this about Hooters, but I liked
everything I had. Chili's must be...
I got to go Chili's and took it
to my parents, and my mom
was very skeptical of almost every place.
My mom likes one place. It's Culver's
in Schomburg, Illinois.
You can't have Culver's here.
Oh, I hear about it every week.
When are they going to open a Culver's?
Culver's City. They don't even have one Culver's.
I didn't know you had Culver's when we
were in Schomburg. I've never had Culver's.
Oh, yeah. Culver's is good.
You would love Culver's. No sit and don't stomach ache
from Culver's. Well, no.
Go find a way. That's true. You're right.
Maybe the custard. Too much custard.
I had a concrete. I should have just had a cup.
My tummy's in trouble. I had too much custard.
I had a butter burger.
So, yeah, I...
It's just what...
All that to say, my mom was like,
the corn on the cob is actually pretty good
and the broccoli is pretty good too.
My mom was even kind of impressed with
75% of the food.
Chili's does a pretty good job
for whatever. I don't know what it is.
I don't know what... I would be interested
to know all the different philosophies,
like, again, when I watch a 40-minute
boring interview with
the guy, the Twin Peaks guy,
his whole thing was like,
the big reason we're so successful
is the food and the 29...
the 29-degree beer
you can get. And you can get an old
fashion with cube ice in it.
So I wonder if, like... This is all...
Everything you're saying sounds wonderful. No, I know that.
I'm just saying he's, like, touting, like,
the big draw of Twin Peaks
as the hamburger.
And I just don't quite believe...
Probably not the hamburger, no.
I think it was good I stayed away from burgers
at least suspicious of burgers.
You just gotta not
fuck around. You gotta do the thing that they're known for.
And maybe there's something about the boneless
as opposed to the...
I'm a boneless guy in general.
For whatever reason. I think it's just easy.
I mean, it's all gonna be, like, a little bit weird
because it's all reheated.
So I'm just like, give me the nugget.
Give me the little nuggy.
Yeah, it's already been cooked.
When it's in the bag.
So it's getting cooked again.
Less of a chance to get it fucked up in the restaurant.
So a bottled sauce
tossed in a bowl like that.
So I guess I would love to know
the difference is really what I'm getting at.
I would love to know what the
difference is with chilies versus
like, sometimes you go to an Olive Garden.
Most Olive Garden
experiences suck.
So why? Why can't they get...
No.
Jane really got me on Olive Garden.
Comment after comment.
He's rubbing his hands together.
He's rubbing his hands together like he's...
And you know what? Olive Garden
just started doing deliveries.
So you can get a good chicken
parm
in the comfort of your own home.
Just started doing deliveries?
They just started.
No, no. They only did take out
before.
Only recently. Yeah.
But we've eaten in.
We've eaten at home.
You get Olive Garden to go at home
and it's good?
I got chilies to go so I shouldn't laugh.
I like tutors boneless.
So it's really...
We're splitting hairs here I guess.
I've never had one bite
I liked at Olive Garden.
I've had okay stuff. I just have never
loved Olive Garden.
I'm wondering why there's differences in
chain restaurants. Shouldn't they all have the same model?
If only a podcast would get down
to the matter of figuring this out.
I don't want to talk about that though.
Yeah, you're right.
Much like us, the main topic
is not typically...
I think we're a lot more on point actually.
It's possible as far as food and aesthetic.
Well when we talk about restaurants,
weirdly we started doing restaurants
so they veered away. That's a good point.
But we all talk about
uncomfortable sexuality.
That's a hallmark of this.
It seems like Hooters
has opted to remove
any tinge of that
further of past casual
and to go establishment hoots.
You mean the sexuality is what you're saying.
They've removed the sexuality. People wear
I think normal clothes.
Is there a uniform though at hoots?
I just saw a quick
shot of it.
It's just kind of regular.
They eased off. They relaxed.
Now if you do want just wings
without the rest of the Hooters fun,
you could go to the Pasadena Hoots.
It just seems like a fine...
I don't know.
Or not fine. I'm not sure.
So that's Hoots Wings by Hooters.
But this is different
than the Ghost Kitchen that they somehow
established before the pandemic.
In 2019, they were ahead
of it. And Marnie Sher, who is a
supporter of this show, wrote an article
on The Takeout about all this stuff, that somehow
they teamed with Uber Eats
in 2019 and had
a Hooties Burger Bar
ready to go.
So somehow they pre-anticipated.
Maybe Eiger found out and CEO of Hooters
found out. They were the two
who were told, something is coming, get ready for it.
So they started a Hooties Burger Bar.
But then Hooties Burger Bar is different
than Hooties Bait and Tackle.
Which I had to stare at for a minute
before realizing, okay, that must be the shrimp
aspect. That must be the seafood.
And then Hooties Chicken
Tenders. Not Hooties Chicken
Tendies. And all of this
coalesces as part of...
Because they're all different, because that's very confusing.
And then Marnie explained, no, this
is all part of, collected
under the umbrella of Hooters Digital
Food Court. But Hoots
Wings by Hooters is not part
of Hooters Digital Food Court.
That's different. Oh, that's okay.
Yeah. This...
I feel like... So if you want, and did none of those
places offer wings? Chicken Tenders
is not wings.
It sounds like they're just throwing shit at the wall here.
I think they are. I think they're just trying to compete with
Wingstop?
How many hours
spent people in a boardroom trying to
square this circle of
what is Hooters in 2025?
Well, maybe it's just the owl and it's
wings. Or maybe it's just the owl and it's burgers.
And people are like, yeah, let's try that.
And you're like...
Well, this is the impossible
assignment that they have of trying to
like... How do we
pull Hooters away from what everyone thinks
of when they think of Hooters? And this is
an issue that was faced on the second
ever episode of Undercover
Boss, which I rewatched last
night. Which largely
takes place in the Dallas
double Hootie establishment.
The second episode
of this. So they're doing all this stuff that they stop
doing on Undercover Boss.
There's a Tilted Kilt on Undercover Boss as well.
Yes. I was trying to find it, but weirdly Paramount
and Hulu don't have the entire series.
So the only of the restaurants
I was able to find. There's a clip of it on Facebook.
There's a clip of one. Anyway, you continue.
But it was an
unenjoyable watch.
Except for the part where there is a disgusting...
There's an
associate manager, somebody who makes the girls
do unsettling things.
His name is Jimbo. He is terrible.
And there's that part in Undercover Boss
sometimes where like, this thing is so bad
that I gotta break cover. I have
to say who I am
so that this stops immediately.
And in this case he was like, I
thought about doing it and did
not. What I will do is bring him
to the office and I'll say, stop doing
that. And then the guy will say, I'd
like to keep doing it. And he said, well I'll stop doing
some of it. Go back to your staff and
apologize and then make sure that you are not
doing all of it anymore. And then the titles
at the end said, he
went back, apologized to his employees
and then resigned for his own
reasons. Oh man, that could be
a hundred things. Yeah, yeah.
No, Jimbo, this fella
didn't look like he had a lot
going on in his favor.
I think the Jimbo's thrived in the 90s.
I think that's for sure. This was definitely
for a Jimbo to rise to that
position. Yeah, yeah.
No, not a good feeling from Jimbo.
And ultimately not, I don't think this guy does not
run the company anymore. He's
the son, he was, he describes
how he was just handed the company
by his father unexpectedly.
So can you come up to the boardroom please? Oh yeah, yeah, I've read this.
You are the CEO now, goodbye.
Which not just the CEO, but he
also inherited the title
which I guess any
future CEO has from now on,
World Wild Wing Commander.
And in the episode you see
him park in his parking space and it says
World Wild Wing Commander 2.
Number 2?
Yeah, yeah. Did the father die
in a plane crash?
No, the father,
this is all strange.
The father died the same year
that they stopped owning
planes. We'll put a pin in that
and come back to it. 2006,
airline ends and World
Wild Wing Commander dies.
He had
two sons, one took over the company,
the other son died in a crash
on one of their private planes, not
their airline. It is very sad
and very upsetting when you're watching it
on the show. So,
yes, like one dies in a company
plane and the other takes over the company?
What a Shakespearean
tragedy.
I guess also very dramatic
that even on
television the son is
not able to say that
his father was a nice man.
He was
a guy.
This guy was, and he by the way
is not one of the Hooters Six. Robert Brooks
is the guy's name. He took it
over and ran it like an actual business
because those knuckleheads, they didn't know.
The Six didn't know what they were doing.
So the explosive growth of the company
through 80s, 90s, 2000s was all
due to World Wild Wing Commander
here.
We should also, we never finished
The Sinister Six.
The guy who played with
Dick Butkus, which distracted us
understandably, he later
was part of a million dollar tax evasion
trial. Oh yeah, I saw that.
Which ended in a mistrial.
So, we don't know.
Maybe it was a comedy
of errors, you know?
Accidental tax evasion.
We forgot to pay.
No, you got the wrong guy, you see?
That's L.D. Stewart
and then Ed Drost, a real estate
executive, went on to be one of the developers
of Splitsville. We know Splitsville
from our time in
Downtown Disney and Disney Springs. Both there, yeah.
Both locations. And that turns
a corner on The Six. What else
in terms of this stuff and the lore?
I mean, we could certainly
talk about, I mean, I got a couple
directions to go, but
what are you thinking?
Well, I mean, did you ever go to the Hooters Casino
in Vegas? It's been rebranded.
That's a viable, let me shout
out, who mentioned Hooters
Gilder on our
Patreon said, mentioned the Hooters Hotel in Vegas.
That was across the street
from the MGM Grand, not
Stripwise, but Tropicana.
It is not Hooters
Today. That was what? That was from
2007 to
2019,
and now it's called Oyo.
Yes, Oyo. But it still has a Hooters
inside it. That was part of the contract
I read, that they retained the Hooters inside,
but the whole branding would be different.
I believe I went in there in one, I don't know
if it was the same Twin Peaks
Vegas, I think it was a different one, but
it was depressing in there.
Yeah, one of those. It was not a
hot spot. No, no.
Jason never spent any time in the place.
We were, one time
when we were at a bachelor party in
Vegas, Mike, someone in the
group said,
oh, I'm staying in Vegas
another night. I got a room at the
Hooters Casino Hotel for
like $25.
I do remember looking at websites
around the time. I mean, it went,
it was rebranded recently, but I remember it would be
like, oh, do you want to stay for $30 a night
at Hooters Casino? But this
was before I was like, oh, for like
another $20,
you might, could have at least upgraded
to the New York, New York, or
Excalibur, or MGM Grand,
or something. The cheap prices.
You gotta go the cheapest, yeah. There's a
kind of better quality.
So that, I mean, I don't know,
that ran for a long time, and there's still
Hooters in there, but not a,
not an unqualified success, you wouldn't say.
No. Much like the airline.
Let's talk about Hooters Air.
Which was
referenced in our initial pitches by
Christopher Vasca. Thank you, Christopher.
So yeah, they had Hooters
Air. This is from 2003
to 2006.
That guy, worldwide
flying commander. He bought
something called Pace
Airlines, I believe, like a small,
a small batch. A small
commercial airline.
Which was seven planes. They went to 17
destinations.
They were centered in
Myrtle Beach, South Carolina.
And in a video that I watched
about it, the current head of
the
Board of Chamber of Commerce of
Myrtle Beach speaks as if
the CEO and the airline
are like,
that's, that's, it's
God, and these were his little clouds he flew
on, because he said the amount of good it did
for Myrtle Beach, who it brought to Myrtle
Beach, and then it went away, sure,
but it like got so many
families in the tradition of
We Love Myrtle Beach, and the fun started
on Hooters Air. He's like,
he's so deferential to everything
that Hooters Air did for Myrtle Beach.
Would you believe that Hooters Air had a good effect on
Myrtle Beach, South Carolina?
I would believe that, I guess, in some ways.
You could fly to Orlando
on Hooters Air.
Not the big airport, but the
Sanford, the smaller one.
The,
you maybe flashed
to, oh, so the flight
attendants must have been Hooters
girls. That's what I would have assumed, yeah.
And that's not exactly it, because they
had, because like the amount of
training that flight attendants
require, they did still want regular
experienced flight attendants.
But they didn't make them
wear the shorts. In this video, they
said, oh, they pointed out like it's like blazers,
that were like in a very classy way
embroidered with a little hootie
owl, and it said Hooters Air.
It is,
it's hard not being a server, but then like
imagine you have to like help evacuate a plane
and you're like in your Hooters outfit. I mean,
I'm surprised they didn't try to force them
to do that, because that feels like
that show where people point to the belts
and everything, suddenly people are paying attention.
Right, but you're like in the middle,
you've seen, I mean, we've all seen the videos of people
like just screaming at flight attendants,
and you're like, this is the worst job in the world, sometimes.
But on top of it, you're like,
well, is your, you know, is your
Hooters uniform on before you get to work?
Yeah, that would not particularly help the situation.
Well, they thought of this. It shocks me, though.
Isn't it amazing that that is not the way
that they went? No, they actually didn't have
the primary Hooters stuff,
because they had free food, and it was just
set price. It's always $129,
no matter what, no matter how far you're going,
just flat rate. And food is free.
That's a nice gimmick, right? I think it was
well regarded, honestly.
Was it better than Frontier or Spirit?
The Spirit and Frontier have the bad
reputations now as far as commercial airlines.
Well, they've had the times, I mean, I'm sure
those airlines are worse now than these
were, although this was sooner. Oh, I guess
yeah, because everything's been so bad.
I don't know, I don't know. Maybe
Hooters was like, versus what it's like
now flying Hooters, it's like you were in the
60s of the prime flying time.
Yeah, this is a panhandle,
happening, hopping. You were like having
a cocktail with a pilot in the cabin.
Oh yeah, well I should say the Hooters
girls did fly the plane. Oh, okay, good.
Yes, yeah, yeah. They weren't allowed to be
flight attendants, but you want that, right?
The union's strong. The flight
attendants' union actually is stronger than the pilots.
Stronger than the pilots, yeah. They'll let
whoever in there. Can you
just yell we as often as possible?
Yeah, sure. Just flip the plane flight style
on purpose and say we.
If a commercial airliner would
tout itself as like, we're the only
airliner who will do a flip. Yeah.
All right, everybody buckle up. We'll make sure
it's safe for you. It's not going to be accidental
and the pilot's not drunk and he's not going to go on a big
trial with revelations about who
he is. I think when I was little
thought that that's what happened.
I thought when you were flying, obviously when you see
cartoons, it goes up and down. I think
when I was a kid and I didn't I didn't get on a plane until
I was
16, 17, 18. I was old.
I was old, yeah. So I really was only
on one plane until. The same year
you first went to Hooters. Basically
I went to Orlando. We took
a plane to Orlando
and then I guess
I was like 15 or 16 and
I think up until a couple
years prior to that, I thought the planes
might do a little loop-de-loop. You're
in high school. It's possible I was
a freshman in high school going, yeah you know you do your loop-de-loop
on the way down when you land.
It's possible. So you just
took a trip to Columbus,
Ohio, did you? Well did you get nervous
when the plane did the loop-de-loop?
When they did the opening loop-de-loop?
Did it make you sick to your stomach?
I got on a plane when I was three years old.
A lot of people did.
That's a funny one. No plane.
We always
mostly just went to Orlando and
we drove to Orlando up until this one.
It's a long drive. You'd be exhausted
when you get there.
I've questioned my parents to some degree.
Were you
not doing well financially so much that
you saved a couple hundred bucks?
They needed Hooters Air.
Hooters Air existed when I was younger.
It started right after.
That would have changed
everything. You and your
mom happily flying on Hooters Air.
All issues resolved for you across
the board.
Yeah, no problem there.
The first one I remember opening was
in a big shopping area
close to
the Pennsylvania-Delaware border
and the Company Man
video, the one kind of alludes to this
that it's like when you're
a kid, you think
we all thought something
really lascivious was going
on there. We all thought something
really forbidden was going on.
Mike thought that until a month ago.
He still thinks that.
He thought it as he was opening
the door on iDrive.
Can I ask this question? What was your perception
when you were a kid of this place?
When you were 8, 9, 10?
I don't know that I ran into it
when I was a kid because they aren't near me.
I think they were maybe more near you.
Just a little story.
My friend's dad went to
Hooters and for his birthday,
all the waitresses
took a picture with him.
That's a thing.
I'm sure that happened in a lot of places.
It was displayed in part
of their house in a corner.
It felt weird
to me. It felt strange.
Aren't you upset that your dad
cheated on your mom 12 times?
Right.
I was like, oh, Hooters is kind of a naughty
place. That's probably
the way I felt about it.
And feel.
No past
tenths of it.
That really was
my impression that you either had to be
a certain age to go there
or you had to have an adult.
I think my friend went with his
parents once and I was
shocked that there wasn't an age limit.
Did you go up on your dad's shoulders and did you
put a big trench coat on? How'd you get in?
I think I was. I think you're right. I think I had the
same thought. When I was looking at photos of the
Costa Mesa one, one of the things that turned me off
was seeing two kids
with their shirts off in there.
In a Yelp photo. I am sure that's not
uncommon for a certain period of
time. The shirts, the kids do what
you want. The shirts, maybe
keep the shirts on. Just for restaurant hygiene,
I would prefer. Just for general
ickiness. Now if it's on a beach,
I saw pictures of a
Hooters on a boardwalk
somewhere. I don't know if that was
Myrtle Beach or that was like
Wildwood. I'm telling you, the breezy nature of the Long Beach
There's no way
you wouldn't have a nice time at that.
Being in Long Beach is not. I like
Long Beach a lot. And I think a lot of
As long as I'm eaten by that water,
I'm certainly going to... And when you got
good company, when you got a good pal
with you, who's talking about
the entire time, we're talking about the kind
of things we love on the show. Weird
old hotels, dead malls, theme
parks. This is all I'm trying to say.
He's one of us, you see.
A good pal. And he was like
your Sherpa. Click, click, click, unsubscribe, unsubscribe.
Sherpa. Yes.
Hooters Sherpa. Yes. He helped
me be 1% more
comfortable in a place where there was no
need to be uncomfortable. Yeah.
The most normal
restaurant. It is not, no.
It certainly is different
than it was when we were little.
There's no doubt about it.
It is so bland and nothing and I assume
the incidents are way down
as far as like... Can I play a couple of
things that kind of allude to the vibe
and how they were presenting themselves? When they
had the money to do television
commercials. Oh, right. Yes, please.
There's channels exploding
with these and there's a lot of delightful stuff
because not only did they
at some point they got like big budget
TV nationwide commercials
but before that when they were still more local
and primarily in Florida, they would
sponsor, they would do like
Goularty Elvira type
were sponsoring this weird trashy movie
on Florida TV.
They called it Hooters Night Owl Theater.
This was syndicated to
13 markets and they would do little
skits in between and I think the original
Hooters Girl was in the skits.
Lynn? Yes, Lynn was in there.
So there's a lot of clips
of that on YouTube but then this
is shot like a film. This is, this had
money. I want to find a question Mr.
Park Hill. Oh, let me say the context.
Sorry. The context is that there
is a very tense
Senate hearing going on.
One final question Mr. Park Hill.
Have you ever been to a Hooters restaurant?
Not to the best of my recollection.
Never had Hooters nearly world famous chicken wings?
Or the Big Hoot salad?
Spoiler audience, they are cutting to
the would-be senator doing all of these things.
Not to the best of
my recollection.
Mr. Park Hill, we simply cannot
confirm anyone for this post who has never
been to Hooters.
Dupont Circle. Yeah, come to Hooters on
Dupont Circle. Imagine
the notion of a senator
being so scandalous that a
senator...
Well, certainly times have changed as far as
what you can get away with
as far as publicly as being a politician.
I found several
two hour long clips of clearly
you attending different high school dances
at 45.
Alright, fine. Confirm, confirm,
confirm. Most Democrats confirm as well.
Yeah, right.
No problems here.
But here's another. I guess they liked the juxtaposition
of Hooters and politics.
And speaking of doughboys, when this starts playing
you're going to think Mitch is doing the voice.
Fellow Americans, recently
it's been reported in the national media that I am
preoccupied with Hooters.
I wish to state for the record that I have not
been sneaking out in the middle of the night
and going to Hooters. Reports that I have
been seen eating a big plate of nearly world
famous chicken wings are simply
not true. It's just another
attempt to discredit the policies of this
administration. Thank you.
That's so
funny. I mean, it's so like...
Hooters is such 90's culture.
It's so ingrained
in the 90's. And I'm sure
it was a lot, obviously
it was a lot grosser at that
time because we're in its early
iterations.
The world was like, we've talked about that with
Six Flags Live and stuff, the world
was just different.
I mean, things are still, there's plenty of it.
Hornier, but not in a
progressive
body positive. Yes. Everyone's still
horny. I just feel like people
hopefully, the more people are putting
it in a better place.
It's about where you round your horniness.
What to do with your horniness. But it's so
it does feel, you just feel
the Bill Clinton of it all.
Obviously politicians are doing
just weird stuff, bad stuff, or
whatever. Sometimes worse.
Sometimes worse. We don't do anything about it.
Right, right. So
let's talk about, maybe that's a good
transition point too, and we could
come back to Hooters. We can go back to Hooters and
wherever we want.
We should talk about some of these other places
because we were given the, by the way,
also in choosing this, I don't want to
endorse the,
there is, I think a lot of the ickiness anybody felt
about this winning comes from the term
restaurant. It is definitely weird.
There was an article I found in GQ
calling it the worst portmanteau in the
English language. And I would have to
agree with that.
It was coined by one of the, a different
guy, I believe.
No, I have to find my tab. Not one of the six?
Not one of the six. It was later.
Let us know. But it is like an office
guy. It was like a guy
trying to come up with a name
for a segment of
a sit-down
casual restaurant.
With interesting
clothing on the, but so the,
you know, this, they try to expand,
take this premise away from the 90s,
maybe try to like, I don't know,
what is the new version of this? And I think that's what
Twin Peaks attempts to do.
Now I have, I don't have,
I don't have a ton of thoughts about Twin Peaks.
I think there's less lore in Twin
Peaks. I think it's like,
first of all, the food seems better.
The food, from what I can tell, I went to the Vegas
one and just had a drink, I think, so I can't really
speak to it. But it seems like it's
more of like a yard
house with 3%
horniness. Is that a fair
assessment? And plaid. I don't know
percentage-wise. I don't know percentage-wise.
Wait, no, that one's not plaid. Plaid? Oh, wait,
or is it Dorsey plaid? It's like
Pacific Northwest. Got it.
Similar to Tilted Kilt, but
it's in this family. Well, look, I've just proven that I
wasn't looking at a bunch of photos.
Aren't you proud of me? You proved it. You proved it. You proved you're
not a pervert.
The food was, my memory is just like, oh, this
isn't as bad as Hooters. That's my memory of it.
I don't remember having an amazing
meal. Fine. I liked the,
I liked it ambiance-wise, and sometimes
if you look at photos, I did look at photos of the
interior of the restaurants, and it
seems like some of them do have some like, oh, this is kind of
like a Pacific Northwest Lodge, kind of.
It's like closer to our, it is closer
to like you're eating in a themed environment.
Yes. Okay, so the guy, the CEO
of Twin Peaks. Oh, he coined it.
Well, no, he didn't. I'm actually just
bringing up, he says that
the Twin Peaks girls are iconic,
and they are brand ambassadors.
He wants, he's making that, and there's some sort
of pageant or something, so there's
Oh, Hooters, too. Yes.
Aaron and I, independently, years
ago, have, we have definitely, because they used to air this,
we have definitely watched full broadcasts
of the Hooters pageant, where
people go, and they, it's great, because there's more of them
than, like, it's not just the 50
states, it's people representing all of the restaurants,
most of which are from Florida.
Forty-five of their 400 restaurants
are in Florida. Oh, that,
that doesn't shock me very much.
From Daytona, too, I'm
Julie.
Does that still happen? I feel like they don't do
that pageant anymore, do they? I'm not sure.
But they, I don't know, there's a lot of, like, they do
tout a lot of philanthropy,
and things like that.
Like, there's scholarships. We're sending you to college
is a big thing, I think. I think that was maybe
some, I don't know when that stuff came to play,
maybe that was to offset some of it. That must be some
of the rebranding. Right, they're like, alright, here's the deal.
They also, by the way, did a,
and this is, you can read about this in the sign on the way
to the bathroom, which is the,
that they went into Bob Hope
style, would do USO,
kind of shows, during the Iraq
War, a presentation
that they called Let Freedom Wing.
They also
referred to, they also used the terminology
weapons of mass distraction.
Okay, alright, that's
what you're, I guess Iraq War?
All the fun lingo.
Yeah, yeah.
20 years ago, or 22 years ago.
God, I, yeah,
time-wise, I can't. George W.
Bush, this W stands for wings.
I'm surprised
that, they should have done that in a commercial.
I've never, I've been
lying about what the W referred
to. Right.
Time to come clean. I'm off
the cocaine, but I'm still on
the wings.
Was that Bush?
George W. Bush, George W. Bush
saying, I'm off the cocaine.
That was Bush being like,
you know, kind of bawdy, like
those early 90s commercials.
He remembered from when he owned the Rangers
or whatever. Yeah, he was drinking
a lot back in those, we've seen that video where he's like
kind of wild and drinking
at a wedding or something. I forget that was going around.
Mike, how do you feel
that the new pope is from
Chicago, by the way?
Yeah, we brought him up earlier. How do I feel?
And he's a White Sox fan. He was at
the White Sox World
Series. People have a lot of questions
online. None of these are Mike
thoughts, but people like, you know,
he's obviously had Lou Melnati's.
He's been to Culver's. Somebody tweeted, this is the first
pope that's probably been to Culver's.
That's true. He went to Villanova,
the suburbs of Philadelphia.
He went to Villanova.
Does he like Wilco? That's a question
I've seen asked too. That's maybe the biggest one.
That'll make you convert.
Who's his bozo?
Well, we could probably figure that out.
We could probably figure that out. He's in the background
of that Billy Corrigan performance.
Oh no, shocking photo has been revealed
of Pope Leo hanging out
at Hooters with Tom
E.
Disgraced Mike
teacher, Tom E.
That's how he's billed now.
Has the holy C been
to Hooters?
You call him the holy C? The holy C?
Is that one of the terms?
What does C stand for?
Oh, S-S.
I don't know. It's just a phrase.
I'm not religious enough to
know.
Yeah, I'm still looking for the
person who coined that term.
That's important, but who cares?
Here's what I thought was the funniest
from Twin Peaks nonsense
is that there was a lawsuit
between, because we're talking about kind of the three
primary of this genre,
but there were others and other upstarts
and Twin Peaks
sued another place
called Northern Exposure
that was going to be the same stuff
where it was Mountain and Outdoorsy
and the costumes were the same.
They even claimed, I don't know
how the suit settled, but
Twin Peaks claimed that this guy
came to them and said, I want to open one in
Branson, and they said, okay, here
is all of our secrets. Are you ready to open
now? And he said, I'm going to open
my own idea, I think.
It will be Northern Exposure.
It will be completely different. I will do it
via my company, Grand Teton's
LLC.
And I think they
stopped it from being open, but
he also stole, because his tagline
was great steaks, cold drinks, and free
scenic views. And scenic
views is in the standard Twin Peaks.
These guys talk, just a couple
interviews, some of these guys, especially in modern times,
talk like they invented the iPhone
when they're talking about these places, like
with the phrases they've come up with and the philosophies.
It's like,
really, we've reimagined
what a Hooters would be.
So the hamburger's a little better.
You just spend five minutes explaining.
There's not that much to it.
You really get a sense of the guys
we like talking about.
Oh, that's something I forgot to say about that CEO, is that an undercover boss,
so he determines, here's some of the problems, and here's some of the
sexism, and there's people on the street telling me
they don't want to go in there because they associate it with chauvinism.
So then he goes back to the board, and he's like,
we have to find a way to make sure that this brand,
that we show that it's family-friendly, and that
people can come here. Cut to no
solution. Cut to episode
ends. This is not addressed
again. No idea was had.
The end. Next week.
Tip and dots. Right.
All that to say, too, that
I think we could
open up a restaurant tomorrow,
and it would be fine.
We would have to hire people who knew how to do the
restaurant stuff, but what we could do is the
bullshit. Right, that's what I'm saying.
Because everyone's just doing
invented the iPhone, like that
Steve Jobs kind of
big talk,
or the Disney
story, what
story are we telling here?
I'm saying the iPhone is an actual
accomplishment.
I would have to agree. It is an accomplishment.
More so than the family-friendly re-branding
of Hooters, which seems largely unsuccessful.
Or the Twin Peaks guy talking about
what he, because he worked at Hooters first.
He was a franchiser of Hooters.
And what I found was that their beer was 32
degrees, and
scientists said it couldn't be pushed to 29,
and we found a way. Right,
and you're like, this is an hour
long, and all this guy has to say is that
we made the food better, and
there's women in different costumes.
Not like us, you let us
talk for an hour, wait till you see
all the twists and turns.
We'll take it to some places, not like
this loser.
We could break down the philosophy.
I was on Doughboys once, and then I decided to start
my own podcast. What did I bring
from that experience, and how did I change?
What is the philosophy I have now?
I was at Doughboys, and I learned from them, and I appreciated
it, but I thought, couldn't hosts be even
wimpier? And that's what we reimagined.
Couldn't we?
They're calling it the first
master class they ever gave
refunds on.
Couldn't we bore our audience
more than them?
That's an interesting innovation I brought there.
Longer winded, longer episodes
more frequently. In fact, always.
No segments.
Segments for three episodes, and then we bail,
and just talk and talk and talk.
Our average tangent is five minutes long,
and ours is 6.5 minutes long.
That is an innovation we brought to this
medium, and that's what's interesting about it.
They've had
Bugmane on twice, and everyone moved on.
What if we only talked
about having Bugmane on for nine months?
It would be worse than as if he was
on every month.
The specter of him was somehow
worse than him saying a single word.
Let's do Tilted Kilt.
Let's get into Tilted Kilt a little bit.
Which I don't have much about.
They are down to six locations.
It really hasn't worked out for them.
They started at the Rio in Vegas.
I didn't know that.
What is there?
They're the same thing, but it's Scottish
clothes.
They seem the least defined and the least
good or interesting.
I don't know.
There was some wood in there
though. There was some sort of brown
aesthetic, like old
time rec room.
I don't know.
Maybe it was fine. It just doesn't seem like
fortune has been on the side of Tilted
Kilt. I know there was one in
Northridge, California, where I
spent a little time near the
Northridge Fashion Center mall.
In 2017, it burnt down.
Suspected of arson. Don't know if that
was ever resolved.
I remember going to the
Lazy Boy
store next door, one of the best
purchase decisions
I've ever made.
That was in 2019.
That was pre-anticipated.
If I'm going to have a baby, I'm going to need a Lazy Boy.
I want that as an adult.
I did it. Then the pandemic hit.
I was like, there's a global pandemic
and I have a Lazy Boy coming in three
days. This morning, it ain't
going to be so bad.
I remember getting it in the shadow
of a still charred
Tilted Kilt. I didn't know that was two
years after the fact. I do remember
just black wood. It was scary.
That sounds scary.
Lazy Boy
can you only get
a recliner?
You're talking about just getting
a regular recliner. That is what I got.
That's a good thing
for kiddos. I don't know if you got one.
We have a rocking chair
in there.
The rocking chair is great. The only danger
was that first so many months when
you're rocking that kid to sleep
at 4 in the morning.
Boy is that hypnotic.
I would
fall asleep
and then wake up.
But it freaked out because I had a little
baby in my arms.
That's the only danger there.
It's good for them to fall asleep, but it's good for you to fall
asleep, especially if you're tired.
If you're holding a baby, yes.
Those are some of the most harrowing times.
Those first you know.
You've done it twice.
I've blacked it all out.
To some degree
I have too.
The only reason you'd go back for a second is if you don't
remember any of the firsts.
It wasn't so bad. Cut to it's so bad.
And me now
months later. It wasn't so bad.
It's some biological thing there
that really does kick in.
It's what's needed for anyone to reproduce
because why would you ever do it otherwise?
It needs to kick in for us to live our
lives. Yes.
There has to be chemical surging in your brain
so you don't think of all the shit.
Yes. Why would I have
children when I could spend every afternoon
at Hooters? I could be at Long Beach
every day. That's right.
That's all I got about Tilted Kilt.
Or anything else about
Peaks or Kilt?
I mean nothing that
interesting. Joe Hummel
was the man I was listening to talk about.
After all that time
the boring man who said the boring things
had a boring name. Hey don't sell Michael
Carlson short. Joe Hummel is
extremely boring. And this was on the YouTube channel
Nations Restaurant News.
Also a boring name.
Every bit of this is boring.
It's like a youngish man who was just
so psyched to talk to Joe Hummel
about the philosophy of
Twin Peaks. Freaking Joe Hummel.
This was three months ago too this video.
Fresh Hummel. I for sure
follow the Twitter account of
convenience store
solutions.
Which is just
about new
easy to prepare
foods or new snacks or sodas
coming.
Well anybody from that is welcome on
this show. That doesn't sound boring in the least.
Do you have any recent things you're excited about?
I haven't checked in recently.
I haven't seen many updates recently.
We'll send each other new snack
versions of
something that's coming.
I believe the guy who drinks
a lot of diet
soda on Instagram
alerted me that Dr. Pepper
coconut cream is back.
Coconut cream. Interesting. I'm
interested. I'm not a big coconut guy
but I'll try it. It's real
dicey in the sparkling water sector.
So I'm refreshing. Oh yeah I have
had a coconut. Yeah I don't like that
necessarily. In terms
of other ones there was a place called
there still is a place called Show Me's
which is in Missouri.
Oh yeah
any others in this category?
Well so the guy
you know how many tabs
I have open. I was ready to
go with the guy who came
up with the name and then
I went to the top ten knockoffs.
Let's start with the knockoffs first.
Oh it's Bikini's.
That's the place that this guy who
coined the term came up with.
Which also like apparently I mean
apparently but like in the old
days bikini bars is a big inspiration
for Hooters. This is the
early version. There's a way to corporatize that.
They probably just existed independently.
And slightly more
cheap than just
bikini bar. What do you mean?
Like Hooters. Oh because
you're not wearing a bathing suit.
Perfectly classy. Perfectly dressy.
Does everybody know where the name
is from?
Oh I missed that actually. The name
is from a stand up comedy
piece slash short film by
Steve Martin.
There you go. Does Steve know he
did this? Yeah I wonder.
Carry that around as a point of pride.
I don't think he would be so proud of that.
When he's feeling down. When he's feeling unaccomplished.
Yeah.
Do you ever just wake up. Dude you
named Hooters and got zero dollars
for it. Yeah is it like a
William Shatner thing with the
Michael Myers mask where like it's like
I don't make any money off of that thing
that's made so much money. Oh that's right.
Or does he not know about
it? He has to know about it right?
Is he ever in his stone compound
in Montecito dreaming
of the further money he could have
from Hooters? I kind of think he might be.
He probably should be honestly.
But you know he didn't
make up his mind. Do you think Disney's mad
because they had a character named Hooter?
That was after the fact. That was after later so yeah.
The next time we do an
episode with Hooter as one of the
bases it's going to be that Hooter. Yes.
Bombshells?
Did we talk about bombshells?
No. Did we talk
about Tallywhackers?
That's the one I got. I don't believe we did.
Did you see Tallywhackers?
I've heard the phrase.
Well sure you've heard the phrase.
In reference to this kind of
restaurant. Not in the long run.
Tallywhackers is a little bit different. You wouldn't call that a restaurant.
No this is the
this is the male version of it.
It closed though but this was
the attempt at a male version.
Coxtraunt.
I think I read Chestraunt.
That's alright. That's cleaner. But it should be like
Ab something too I feel like.
Testraunt.
Testicle run.
All these things all have in common
dangerous attire to
carry heavy hot food with.
That is very true.
And cold food and cold beverages.
Ah my exposed skin.
If you were working at Tallywhackers in college
when you spilled all over
you would have been in trouble.
Because you would have been shirtless and wearing little shorts.
So when you were doing all that food service stuff
and
dropping tomato sauce
and cutting yourself
it would have been
a nightmare.
I wouldn't have been in a light blue work shirt.
This was the outfit. Can you see?
It's just little shorts.
Yeah.
It's like the beefcake male version.
And then
something we haven't talked about is they'll call the areas
like still today
the appetizer zone on the Hooters menu
is teasers.
They try to be a little scandalous with the things.
But it's a little harder
I think they struggled a little bit
with the male category
to come up with these because
in this case they called them appetizers.
Yeah.
I don't hate it.
Because I got abs on the brain.
I guess like a rock hard ab
should have been rock hard
appetizers.
Scandalous. I don't know.
This was definitely a little more
aggressive.
You're looking at more of a
Magic Mike live kind of
line up I would say.
There's less clothing being worn
for sure than the Hooters girls.
Right.
This place only
lasted a couple years.
They called them cocktails.
They did that one.
That one was already there for them.
I'm on the Instagram of Tally Whackers
which is still there. You can take a look at it.
And then sometimes
the guys look
normal.
And I say normal just in a regular physique.
And then sometimes they look
like they're bodybuilders or pro wrestlers.
Yeah. Some of those look like
they look like bodybuilders from the 40s.
Like this guy.
This guy is like a statue here.
He's in good shape.
This is a place where
I would really have to work.
If I'm thinking about working there is what I'm saying.
Well it's closed so I can't.
And I think I'm too old at this point.
Are those glass cups?
Or plastic cups in the bar?
I don't think you can have that much
exposed skin and have
glass just willy nilly.
That might have been the issue.
It's dangerous.
It's hard enough to get people to pour
the blue curacao in the ice
span of Bar Rescue.
Well they have. You know what? You can wear tank top.
It looks like some of the dudes wore tank tops here.
You could wear a tasteful tank top.
So yes.
What about Adam's
appetizers?
Adam's appetizers.
That's pretty good.
This is for highlighting all the sexiest parts of the male body.
Is that for sure.
Give me that little chin pointy.
Handhelds. Big handhelds.
Handhelds. Jason. Good job.
Good job.
You should be CEO.
We have revolutionized
the way. We have completely
upended what you
know when you think of Tallywackers.
We bought the
Tallywackers IP.
Jason walking into a boardroom
undercover boss style and he's in
full nice shirt tie
expensive jacket and then just
little blue shorts.
Gentlemen you're looking
at the new uniform.
This is how a Tallywackers
server will dress.
Lights up a cigarette.
We're calling desserts a gentle
kiss goodnight.
I'm out of here. Work on it.
That's why we pay him the big bucks.
Comes in he rocks our
world. I was trying to think of like apataint
sizers but that's to taint
something. When you're going
to ogle some sexy male bodies
you're definitely thinking what if I get
to see some taint tonight.
The sexiest part of a naked man.
Well that should just be like taint messing around.
Classic dinners.
There was a car wash happening
here too. There's a kind of a cool
like black and white. I like the style.
It's like black and white but pink. You can see the pink
car. Oh they color corrected just the pink
up. Kind of a cool look.
I would say overall it looks like it was
some budget tallywackers.
Right in this expand. What happened?
Yeah I don't know. Are they
trained car wash professionals
though? Well you would go to
tallywackers and you'd be like gentlemen
did you pass a certification course
to be cleaning my car? You've got to
unscrew that antenna.
You're going to knock it right off with
your clomazinus. Gentlemen your groin is
rubbing up against this rear view mirror.
What are we doing here?
That's not load bearing.
If you aren't careful that antenna could snap
right off and then bang it straightened your taint.
A taint is not meant to clean
a windshield sir. A sponge will do.
Shammy perhaps a taint
no. Don't soap up your taint and
rub it on my windshield.
I mean sparkling taint clean
that's not a phrase in the proper
car wash industry. You gentlemen seem
more interested in lollygagging
than polishing my
other.
Sticking your tongue out does very little
to clean the car. I would
say it does nothing and no I don't
want you to put it on the hood.
That's filthy for you much less my
car. Yes I do want you to jack
up my car I need some new tires please.
Wait what are you using?
You're jacking what up
now? What is the meaning of
this? That's not going to be strong enough
I don't care how sizable.
Oh you took a pill eh?
I guess it does work.
Well I am impressed gentlemen.
I do have plenty of stains yes
why some birds have recently left their
leavings on the car and I would like if you
whacked them off.
Go ahead I'll watch.
I'll supervise.
What? Put on my glasses to
see better.
Wear my opera glasses
and take a look.
We'll see from far away I suppose.
I can see the micro details of whatever this
whacking off process was going to be.
Jason's Gail Gordon.
Gail Gordon going to Tally Whackers.
Normally I find
the male body sinful
and disgusting but these Adonises
on display
this popped up car wash
are quite something
else. Have we
missed anything? Have we properly
covered this area?
Or is there a strong desire
for restaurants too?
Speak with your votes audience.
I'm guessing there won't be but we'll see.
Maybe this thing will take off.
I had a Philadelphia
connection that I
knew about when I was growing up.
I knew
there was something with
one of the Philly's
wives are like oh yeah we're
okay they go to Hooters.
But the Philly's
spring training was in
Florida and currently in
Clearwater and the person
who said that was
Lynn Austin the original
Hooters girl because she was
married to 90s
Philly's like
ace catcher Darren Dalton
for a number of years.
Darren Dalton wow that's a great baseball player name.
She was one of a word
I've learned her out recently in an
acronym the WAGS
the wives and girlfriends.
This is new?
No I just wasn't familiar with
I knew a lot of the families
and the players.
There were some reality shows
but they do a lot of charity
and community outreach nowadays.
Darren Dalton riding high
on a what?
His nickname was Dutch.
He has it all
he's married to the original Hooters girl
is he still?
No he's long dead.
Wow.
Yeah he played
when they went to the World Series in the 90s
played in like three all star games
like Darren Dalton
when I was a kid Darren Dalton
Lenny Dykstra and John
Croc were the big guys.
Lenny Dykstra is more your guy now.
Croc is the color
commentator for the Philly's
on NBC sports filled up.
He's very fun.
John Oliver did a segment about
funny stuff
because Croc just goes off
on like
not understanding
his streaming services
and like food stuff.
I'm kind of a John Croc figure
I guess.
Kind of an older man who doesn't understand
what's going on.
Wow quote Jason about himself
you're kind of a croc.
Yeah I'm croc like.
You're saying you're the crocs of the show?
John Croc is a wonderful ball play
all star ball play.
Great commentator.
Alright well this episode
then I guess dedicated to Darren Dalton
which we will wind
down I suppose.
And it's been a long one so I'll try to be
brief in handling this matter
but as said at the top
we have had decisions
to make in the recent past
and we need to discuss what is going to happen
going forward in Club 3.
Okay so
since September 2024
the bug main battle
has raged on.
You know I think it started
as you know
a mild intrigue.
Some people don't like it and some people do want it
and we'll see where it goes.
And this has turned into a full on civil war
that threatens to tear apart
the very fabric of our
what happened to our little podcast.
I don't know.
You know what we have now
as if an exterminator is
assessing it like you know what you got there.
You got yourself a case of discourse.
You got discourse all under the floorboards
here. You're going to have to rip all that out.
See I thought you were going to say
a bug main infestation.
Like playing off a bug.
We haven't had a bug main infestation.
What we've had is a lot of
people being upset about the threat
of him even the notion of people I'm sure
upset that he was even discussed in this
episode. Am I not allowed to invite
my friend to a fine establishment
in Long Beach California?
I'm not sure. There's no laws on the books
in Long Beach as far as I know.
Of any kind? Yeah no it's
lawless.
It's martial law.
That's why he likes it there.
Anyway if you were listening
and you were not deeply invested in this
or not like deep in the comments or you might need
this explained to you a little bit. Basically we have
always had this policy. Always!
This has never changed!
The policy has always been
that the runner up in the
prior month's poll competes in the next one.
It rolls over and it gets another chance
to gain a little bit of traction
and then become the winner the next month.
This situation
has backfired because
bug main has been locked in second position
for many many months since September.
It has kept rolling over because
we have never had any sort of rule of policy
in place. What would happen if this
just went into infinity?
I thought that maybe this would end up
working itself out.
We've recently discussed if it happens
X amount of months in a row.
You said a year. A year.
If it happens for a year.
Well yes as of recently
it is starting to feel perhaps
a little bit long and perhaps the
recent discourse around this
matter has grown too tiresome
to handle for even
one additional month.
Decisions must be made
and a decision has been made
in order for things to flow
because the situation of
the buggers all rush
to get him into second place and do so
successfully and then the never buggers
wait for something to kind of
get a little bit of traction and then they all vote
for that sometimes whether
or not they want it.
I think it has become kind of
a strange situation and while we'd like
democracy to just play itself out
again strong leaders need to come in and take
decisiveness. Well there's a bill of rights
there's amendments you know that's what
the system is built for.
The electoral college
Mike's favorite.
Yeah.
We love to
gerrymander.
Alright so we are facing some
founding father challenges.
Here is the decision that has
been reached. Bug main
does whatever he wants will hereby
be retired from the club
three poll.
For the June episode poll for
next month we will start fresh
with five entirely new
topics. Please leave your suggestions
as always in the Patreon comments.
Nothing will carry over.
It will be a clean start. Five
entirely new topics. The winner
of that poll the episode will be released on
a Wednesday TBD in June.
On that same
Wednesday in June
that very day a second
bonus episode
will be released.
That bonus episode will be
Bug main does
whatever he wants.
This will honor the loyal
steadfast bug fans
who for months have voted with
their hearts with their beliefs
who have broken no rules and committed
no crimes. But
this decision will also serve
the never buggers who will be getting
their own separate bug free
episode. The bug episode
is not your episode. It is a
bonus. If you are the kind of person
who says things like I pay my
hard earned money for club three and I don't
want to pay for a bug. You are not
you are not paying for it. It is a
bonus. The other episode which
will be voted on which will be bug free
that is your episode.
I suggest that you consider the
bug episode to be like a bear
in the woods. If you don't
bother it it won't bother you.
No one is making you listen to it.
If you do not want bug we have
heard you. There will be another
episode for you. Gentlemen
how do you feel now that this has been fully made up?
I think this is you know
Henry Clay was the great
compromiser they said of course
in the old days and I think this is a
So Jason is kind of the
crook so I guess I mean all
of us are kind of the clay. I actually
Mike stunts me. I do not remember
Henry Clay. Am I wrong?
That could be right. I am just worried about saying
anything further about we are like clay and then
we learn a lot of bad shit about clay.
There is no bad shit that you could
say about this a perfect decision
that has been reached. Henry Clay yeah I was
right. He was a lawyer and
secretary of state. Secretary of state.
My father is a lawyer and while I
did not inherit his
beliefs about paying conspiracy
weirdos at conspiracy sites
I did inherit his notion of
law and order of being firm
of taking action and of trying
to reach a compromise that makes
everyone happy. Do we not feel like this
satisfies everyone? I think it does.
It is a buggy bonus if you want
if you are that
interested in that. You are so inclined if you want
to skittle scattle over to that.
But you do not have to. No problem. If you are not
interested in skittling or scattling
much less pootie sauce there will be an episode
that honors your interests.
There will not be the blockade
in the poll and I think I have figured
out another thing that
I have not even discussed with you guys that I think
will help in the situation
of future blockades. Oh go ahead please.
I find it interesting for something to get stuck
in second place and like will it make it over
the hill. You know the first time it happened
with the mass magician it was a lot
of fun. We were all having a lot of fun.
So here is
what will happen but just to keep the drama of
the possibility of that happening
I am hereby instituting
Bugs Law aka the
Putty Statute. Runner-ups will now
compete in no more than four polls
before being retired from the poll
and considered for automatic second gate
or even main feed.
Do we all take Bugs
Law and the Putty Statute? So you are saying that it is
four and then we decide or it automatically
goes? I guess that is a question of
is it in four polls?
Yeah I thought it was four
poll appearances. Does that include the first?
I think the total of four
so that there still is
the notion of like oh is it going to
because I think it can be fun. There is some fun to be had there.
I found a lot of this
to be fun until the recent
past. So in order to keep some
of the fun and that is what I would say in
general is remember this is a
comedy podcast. Comedy
is fun. Sometimes we have a poll where
we vote on silly fun topics. Fun
is fun. Remember everyone
fun is fun. I think that is a good
tagline. Okay so
here is what will happen on a Wednesday
in June. I think it will be a very exciting
day. You will have different
paths much like the portals in Epic Universe.
You can choose your path and you
will go through the thing. What is
the thing called?
The Kronos?
Yes imagine when
open your Patreon app.
It will be like the Kronos and you can
choose where you want to go. Do you want to go hang
out in Club Bug Free?
Or do you want to go hang out in Club
Coco Peli? That is me.
You can go either way.
Or you could go both.
And if you as I believe
a lot of listeners are if you
either like all of it
or don't know what the fuck any of this
is about then you get two episodes
that day. You are really the winner that
day. It is going to be a bonus June
if you want it. Yes.
Also you can just plug
in your private R access reader
into a podcast feed. You don't have to use
the Patreon app.
If you want all your podcasts in one place.
People don't know that sometimes.
That is the Kronos
too. There are multiple Kronos. I don't know
what to think.
Think of the one
as the entrance from the Grand
Helios Hotel.
You are right.
And that is what I would say
is that everybody it has been a long
bunch of
months. So everyone get a restful
sleep as if at the new sparkling
Helios Grand. Everybody
rest up because you are going to
wake up to a refreshed poll.
We need your topics and
we will put all this behind us.
And to quote one of Bug
Main's favorite songs.
Put faith in what you most believe in.
Two worlds, one family.
Trust your heart.
Let fate decide to guide
these lives we see.
I think. May as well have sung all
of them.
So that is that.
Now that said,
while this does close out the matter of
Bug Main does whatever he wants,
if this were ever to happen again with
Bugsy Bones does whatever he wants,
Beaumont G. Mannheim does whatever he wants,
or Craig Healy does whatever he wants,
those will be different things and we will deal
with those at a later time.
That will be another few different,
we will have to do multiple amendments.
And those unfortunately,
the Putty Statute do not apply to those.
Because I thought of the idea first.
He's slipping pork in at the last second.
He's slipping these things into these bills
right before they pass.
Henry Clay caught it!
This is delicious boneless wings
as if from the wonderful Long Beach Hooters.
And with that,
you survived Podcast The Ride.
You survived The Bug Dilemma.
Thank you for subscribing
to Club 3. Your bravery
saved the podcast. Well done
William Fighters. And you also
survived an episode about restaurants
that Bugmane did not secretly invade.
What's that at the door?
You said we were
the only ones here!