FOREVER!
DOG!
Warning!
The following podcast will be heard by the live audience and no one else
because we left our Zoom recorder in the locker for Tron Lightcycle Run.
One of your hosts may weep involuntarily due to the recent closure of Jelly Rolls.
To honor this fallen angel, most of our show will consist of group sing-alongs of Bad Bad Leroy Brown.
One of your hosts may weep involuntarily due to the recent closure of Mama Melrose.
To honor this fallen angel, he will spend the show slowly gumming a giant sausage.
And now, live from Icon Park, right next to a lot of very dangerous looking rides,
it's Podcast The Ride!
That was a lot of rigmarole, wow!
A standing ovation because it is standing room for some of you.
A forced standing ovation.
What's going on, everybody?
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a live podcast endeavor that now requires the abandonment of three children.
Three now!
Back at home!
My daughter is potty training currently, and from what I hear, it's not going well.
And I'm not dealing with it right now, but I will be.
You will come home to bathrooms full of pee on the ground.
You'll slip and slide as soon as you walk in the door.
Yes, I will be soaked in pee.
Ground stickiness will only be beer that has fallen here at Tin Roof Orlando.
Hey, everybody, thank you for coming.
Hello, Orlando.
We're back!
Was anyone here last time?
A couple years ago, a lot of you were here last time.
We are thrilled to be back.
We've been dying to be back.
My name is Scott Gertner.
Hi, everyone.
Over here we have...
My name is Mike Carlson.
Thank you.
And I'm Jason Sheridan.
Or as you can see, I should say Jason Bourne.
That's right, folks, I'm fully stuntacular-pilled.
I'm going all in.
Throughout the show, maybe I'll just turn to you and say, oh, my God, that's Jason Bourne.
As they do in all of the movies.
Yeah, well, for anyone listening, if we've managed to find a way to record it,
you are wearing a Bourne's Stuntacular hat.
You're wearing a Bourne's Stuntacular shirt.
Is there a Bourne's Stuntacular underwear that we are not familiar with?
Unfortunately not, and they really got an earful when I realized there was not.
I realized I left my Bourne's Stuntacular water bottle backstage
and my Bourne's Stuntacular pin back at the hotel so I would not lose it.
Those are precious items.
You've got to keep track of those.
Everybody's feeling good.
You're stuntacular-pilled.
I'm pumped.
I pre-gamed at Cafe Tutu Tango down the street.
Are there fans of Cafe Tutu Tango here?
Wow.
Okay, I know I'm in the right place.
I will have to explain this to some people if you aren't familiar.
This is a chain that used to be a chain and now seemingly is only here on iDrive,
which is the case for a lot of chains, it seems.
It's the place where they go to die.
But like 30 years, chains get retirement in one little box.
It is a place where you can have sangria next to a little painting
of Dave Chappelle as Rick James.
I had a lot of fun there.
I had extremely expensive okay tapas,
and I want to share my Cafe Tutu Tango love with you.
Is there anybody here?
Let's do this thing.
Who thinks that they may have come from the furthest to be here tonight?
Does anybody shout something out?
You were first with the LA.
You came as far as we did, and you aren't one of the LA people who came with us.
Join us on stage really fast.
I got something for you.
Hello.
Wow.
Thanks for being here.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Anna.
Hello, Anna, and I'm sorry that I shoved the mic in your face in such an aggressive way.
What's your name?
Anna.
Okay.
You got the answer right.
Here's what I have for you.
Excellent delusion and not scary farm, a great vest.
Wow.
So for coming all of this way across the country from a place where we do live shows sometimes,
but for being here with us tonight, I appreciate it.
Anna, and you get done by a Cafe Tutu Tango artist
because there's artists working in there by Kayla Maria Alves,
a print of an oil painting of Chucky.
Oh my goodness.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for doing.
Absolutely.
Thank you, Anna.
Thank you for coming.
Appreciate it.
Frame that.
Put that above your bed.
Put it on your ceiling, looking down at you like a mirrored ceiling.
And when you see Chucky's scarred face, think of us.
Wow.
So excited to be here.
So yeah, hey, we've been in our favorite place.
We've been in the place that we talk about all damn day every day,
and it always feels good.
I think it's safe to say that there is never a time that we are happier
and more engaged and excited to be doing this podcast than when we are here in Orlando, Florida.
Thank you so much for having us and for being here.
And every time we come, we meet more people, we make more friends.
It truly is like such a heartwarming affair, and we really love to do it.
How are you guys feeling?
You feeling as good as I am, Post Tutu Tango?
Well, I'm feeling so good.
I bought a fanny pack that said Florida on it.
Step one to moving.
If you just start filling, if everything you own starts to say Florida,
it will just be more cost effective to make the move.
Right, because currently all my stuff says California.
So it would make sense that I would have to switch states.
That's how it works.
That's how we all live.
Items that you own, you represent your state.
Jason, and I haven't even, I didn't see yesterday.
You've got to catch me up on some stuff.
How you feeling here in your favorite place?
Pretty good, yeah.
It's not the best place in the world for someone with heat sensitivity
at the start of June.
But you may do because the state is full of industrial air conditioning.
So hanging in there.
You know, Scott, this is the second trip where I've navigated the parks
with an ECV scooter.
Yes, indeed.
Jason is scooting.
You're on wheels.
I am scooting, and I've learned a lot doing that.
Now, last time we were here, I had a top five list
of the most reactionary t-shirts I encountered.
And other than Jane spotting a preteen boy wearing a shirt
that said Jesus won, which I don't know that was really his thing, you know?
I don't know that he was really trying to win.
Won what?
It's unclear.
The 2024 election?
I'm worried that's what it means.
Yeah, so, but I did come up with a top five list of observations
I've accrued navigating the parks with an ECV scooter.
May I share it with you all?
That's perfect because I'm on stage, my audio is amplified,
and you are in the audience.
You have no choice.
All right, top five observations touring the parks on an ECV.
Number five, when you are resting your hands like this on a scooter all day,
you may get a sunburn on the back of your hand.
Oh, no.
Don't worry, it's faded and peeling now.
Wait, did you not sunblock the back of your hand?
Did you not have any lotion just because it's a place you don't necessarily put lotion on?
I think I put on gobs of suntan lotion.
I just probably real quick rubbed the back of my hands not thinking.
You need biker gloves, fingerless biker gloves, studded spikes perhaps like Anna is wearing,
denim, let's figure out a place so you can get some stuff.
Sorry to cut you off.
Number four, I no longer like cobblestones as a design choice.
Number three, when a thunderstorm breaks out,
make sure to cover the control panel or the device will stop functioning.
No, were you on top of a very tall hill or something?
No, that's what we learned like last time, the one day it rained, so I was prepared this time.
Okay, good. You've learned already.
Also, you very quickly realize when a thunderstorm breaks out
and there's lightning in the area, you are sitting on top of hundreds of pounds of metal.
Don't think too hard about that one.
Number two, you will have some interesting interactions.
Like when I was looking at shirts in the Tower of Terror gift shop
and a child briefly leaned over my arm.
I did not notice this, but the mother said, honey, stop leaning over people to look at things.
And I very politely said, oh, no worries, because I hadn't really noticed.
And the mother responded very curtly, yes, worries.
So I've been just walking around, scooting around for a few days, muttering yes, worries to myself.
That's my mantra all the time.
Yeah.
And the number one thing, all handicapped stalls can fit an ECV if you have the will.
So that's my top five for this.
Very good. Thank you so much.
Wow. Excellent.
I wish we had a Paul Schaefer to play jazz out of that talk show bit.
This is the one live show where Paul Schaefer is not in attendance for us.
Are you sure? Are you out there somewhere?
To that kids scolding thing, there's always that thing in theme.
But you are watching absolute meltdowns occur at all times.
I had a great meltdown I thought was worth sharing.
This wasn't even in the heat of a park.
This was checking into a hotel where it was very air conditioned,
but a very normal kind of fight between two kids broke out.
And the mom was being very polite to the concierge or whatever.
And then all of a sudden turned around and said, I don't need two kids fighting right now.
You're going to end up in Disney jail.
I witnessed someone going, I'm done.
OK, I'm done in a park at nine in the morning.
Look, the heat drives people nuts.
You know, you go a little nuts when it's hot enough, you know.
But, you know, not us.
That's the getting to be like to feel like among the people who are having the least amount of breakdowns,
who are having some of the most fun, which is what I feel about all the folks here.
I think I like this group.
Where are the theme park fans who are enjoying it the most?
And I think we've run into some of you folks over the course of the last.
Wait, wait, make some noise if we've seen you, if we met you at some point.
Oh, great, great.
Hopefully meet more of you later.
But, you know, I think we met some of you in a very specific spot.
And that maybe takes us into the topic of tonight's show.
Because, you know, we always want to be in Orlando.
We want to be in Orlando as often as possible.
We sure do.
Easy outlaw, easy. Not yet.
Makes me feel real good is all.
Orlando Mike is coming out.
Orlando Mike's hopping right out of that fanny pack.
The fanny pack is very pro wrestler core.
So it's really, it's adding to the aesthetic in a lot of ways.
I'm becoming my true form.
He's going to be unleashed over the course of the night.
But with this, you know, we always want to be here.
But this felt like a time where it was like we had to come.
It was a calling. It was our duty.
Because it's been a very exciting month in theme parkdom.
There's a lot of stuff that I think we're all thinking about.
A lot of very exciting changes in the last couple of weeks.
Some things have occurred.
Some recent news has happened.
There are things happening that are certainly going to have an epic
sized impact on the Orlando theme park universe.
Wouldn't you say?
I am talking, of course, about the closure of Muppets Courtyard.
Yep. Yep.
I heard some boos.
Let's make sure those boos are for the concept and not for us.
You know, get your boos out, right?
We should do it, boo!
Hold on, I have a question.
Is anyone in the room happy it's closing?
Hey!
We got one! We got one!
You motherfucker!
Get that motherfucker out of here!
Get him out of here!
Enjoy your door coaster.
That guy really loves Star Wars.
What the hell is that waiting area?
The launch bay?
The launch bay. He loves it.
He's glad launch bay is safe.
No, that's right.
They finally heard everybody's complaints about Disney's Hollywood studios.
We want there to be less to do.
Shut down a bunch of stuff.
As we record, I feel like we were here and designed this to be here for history.
We were recording this on Sunday, June 8th, 2025.
On Saturday, June 7th, 2025, just yesterday,
Muppet Vision 3D ran its final show after 34 years in the park.
A sad affair, an emotional affair.
How many people were there for it?
How many people got to see it yesterday?
One last time, yes.
And that's a sad thing, definitely.
But it puts us in a bind.
We've already done an episode about Muppet Vision 3D.
Might feel repetitive to do it again.
There is something, dare I say was something.
I'm still getting used to it.
I'm not excited to say it.
There was something in Muppet's courtyard that we have not done an episode about.
Something that has been...
Yes, Jason?
Fountain.
Fountain, and that's it.
It is the fountain.
Fountain.
No, it's a little bit bigger than that.
It was something of an establishment.
It is something that has been the subject of debate on podcasts, The Ride,
for a number of years.
What is it, you ask, if you haven't figured it out already?
Why, let me tell you.
It's rat pizza.
I am seeing...
Got a jacket right there.
Jackets already.
Okay.
Hey.
We chose right.
Good pick.
Oh, boy.
All right.
So tonight, it is happening.
You are here for the very day after its burial.
A salute to all of Muppet's courtyard, but mostly Pizza Rizzo.
That is our show this evening.
Okay.
All right.
I'm glad we...
See, we debated this a lot.
What topic do we do?
Wait, hold on.
Hold on.
Oh, a change.
A change is happening.
It's coming out.
Strip, strip, strip.
Jason, strip, strip.
Yeah.
I see Beaker.
Beaker was a peeker.
I bought this shirt 26 years ago when they bothered to open the store in Muppet's courtyard.
They weren't selling a shirt yesterday.
Oh, yeah.
What the hell happened there?
There was not a goodbye shirt.
I read somewhere that there was a goodbye shirt offered for Ellen's Energy Adventure,
but not for the Muppets.
What lends itself to shirts better?
All of the Muppets or a weird rotting animatronic that didn't look like Ellen in the first place?
Speaking of shirts and such, please raise your hand or make some noise if you are currently wearing Muppet memorabilia of some kind.
Pretty good.
Wow, wow.
Not even knowing that that's where this was headed.
Can I ask this question?
I hate to keep derailing, but is anyone here wearing any Aerosmith merchandise?
I assume that means everyone because no one raised their hand.
It's assumed they all have something on their person.
That's all the underwear.
That's stuff we can't see.
That's thongs.
Oh, yeah.
What if they used to sell a thong at the Rock and Roller Coaster gift shop?
It was 99, baby.
It was a different time.
One little story from yesterday, now that you bring up Aerosmith, is we did what might be, that's a little scary,
it could be Mike's final ride with the Bad Boys of Boston on the Rock and Roller Coaster,
because they're being replaced by the Muppets.
Now let's boo the Muppets.
Boo!
We can have it both ways.
No, you maybe did your last Rock and Roller Coaster with Aerosmith.
Probably, yeah.
So that was your emotional affair.
Right at the exit, we decided to take a photo with a photo that is up as you make your way out of the ride of the full lineup of Aerosmith.
I told Mike, stand next to that.
And right at that moment, somebody walked by and said, hey, there's the tastemaker.
Yeah!
There's your proof.
Yeah, yeah. Duh.
Mike's like, yeah, that was the one time you saw it.
It happens to me 10 times a day.
It happens all the time.
When you're not around.
Okay, no, but we're here to talk about, I mean, Pizza Rizzo, but I think there's maybe a little bit to say about.
So folks here got to see Muppet Vision one last time.
Would you say that you got sort of like a bit of a rowdy audience where people like, people making noise, talking a lot?
I feel like my friend Andrew is here.
He did one right before the one we went to, and he said it's exciting because everybody is cheering all of the stuff.
Then we got in there and no one cheered all of the stuff.
It was deadly, deadly serious, so respectful.
I had the gall to go, Sweetums came in.
Should we not applaud for Sweetums like Kramer coming in?
And I did a little golf clap, as did people in the row with me, and then it just went away.
It just like went into the air.
And now I'm hearing that in every other show, people were screaming for Sweetums.
What happened?
There's respect, and then there's too much respect.
You all make as much goddamn noise as you want.
Let's make it rowdy like Muppet Vision.
Anyone want to cheer Sweetums right now?
There we go.
Better.
That's for Sweetums.
Is there a member of Aerosmith you'd like to get a cheer?
Careful, careful.
Who's the least problematic of all of them?
The least problematic?
Joey Kramer.
Yeah.
They don't make Joey Kramer's coffee anymore.
The drummer of Aerosmith had a coffee for a couple years, and now he doesn't do it anymore.
He doesn't sell coffee anymore.
See, this is the effect you had.
You said Joey Kramer, and I immediately, part of my mind went, does he have coffee or does he have a whiskey?
And this is what you've infected my brain with, Tastemaker.
Well, I'm not doing a very good job if you couldn't remember.
I was 50-50.
That was pretty good.
True, you did say coffee.
Shall I take it back?
I apologize.
Eat notes, right?
W for whiskey, C for coffee.
What else do celebrities have?
Restaurants that are opening very slowly, like John Taffer down the street?
Oh, yeah.
We'll be back here for that.
We'll talk about that later.
Yeah, yeah.
There'll be no ends to the John T.
People will miss rides and theme parks so much when the one stupid Taffer restaurant opens.
Anyways, but it's all a bummer, and I think it's really hard for me to imagine a Hollywood studios that doesn't have Muppet Vision 3D in it,
because, like, come along with me on this.
Do you all have the memory of you are in the hotel room or you get the VHS because you're coming to Disney World soon,
or you're just watching a special on TV, and what do you see but the 3D and the letters are in your face,
and then you see Fozzie and the pie, and the pie is literally coming out of the screen,
and then it cuts to the audience, and the pie is flying over their head,
and they are reaching up to it like dopes trying to touch the pie.
I'm like, that's the perk to me.
I'm going to miss that so much.
And just as one commemorative thing, and maybe this is something we would all enjoy on this kind of mournful weekend,
I'm going to get my phone out.
Could I ask all of you to pretend that there is a giant pie in the sky above you?
Let's do a little bit of live filmmaking, okay?
Okay, you know what, actually, Mike, can you help me out?
Can you just, like, you know, like the, you know, whenever, like, you know, Marmaduke is a tennis ball.
Will you just point in a direction that you think everybody should be looking for the giant pie, okay?
All right, and your motivation is...
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Yeah, yeah.
Look at the Florida fanny pack.
Okay, well, they already were.
They obviously already were.
I know.
Okay, and your motivation is there is a giant pie in the sky, and you're trying to touch it.
Okay, okay, let's go here.
I'll go fish eye, so we fit a lot of people in.
All right, and action.
Reach, reach.
There we go.
Okay.
Here, and then run all the way to the other side of the stage.
Go, go, go.
Yes, good, good, good.
Okay, okay, drop the mic.
Very good.
Okay.
All right, and now it drops and crushes all of you and you are dead.
That was good, y'all.
Wow.
I'm not even doing that theme parkie.
Give yourselves a round of applause.
You all made a noise without me asking.
That was awesome.
That was nice.
That was really good.
All right, I'm going to try to edit that as quick as I can.
I don't know 3D imaging, but I'll try.
If you can help me out, maybe I can crowdsource it or something.
I will try to get that up as soon as I can.
Thank you for being great actors.
Okay.
Scott, would you be able to do a quick voiceover snippet just at the end
of Kissimmee St. Cloud, the center of the action?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can everybody make the sound of a bow going into a big target?
All right, here we go.
Nope, nope, the arrow goes into the target.
Oh, wait, no, no, isn't it a bow?
I think it's a bow.
I think I said the right thing.
Okay, arrow.
Here we go, three, two, one, arrow.
Three, two, one.
That was really good.
Oh, that was great.
Thank you so much.
Now do the bow going into the target.
All right, three, two, one.
You all made a decision.
You made a decision.
You made it loud and clanky and clunky.
This is great.
This is a wonderful crowd.
I'm very excited.
Okay, anyway, let's shift over to Pizzarizzo, the reason that we are here.
The Cliff Notes for anyone who doesn't know.
Does anyone here not know Pizzarizzo?
Dear, what a room we are in paradise.
Deafening silence.
Wow.
These are smart people.
This is our crowd.
This is great.
This is the most educated crowd I've ever encountered.
For any fools back at home, unaware, next to Muppet Vision 3D,
right around 2016, they kicked out a Pizza Planet restaurant
that didn't resemble the Pizza Planet from Toy Story in any way, shape, or form.
And they put in a new restaurant that is a Muppet-owned restaurant
that is specifically owned by Rizzo the Rat.
This is the famous joke that you can see on the outside of it.
There's a neon sign.
It says, the city's top-rated pizza.
Sometimes some of the letters burn out, and all that is left is, it's rat pizza.
The catchphrase of the place.
I think that phrase is sticky.
I think that's like a reason that this thing is burrowed into a lot of our brains.
But I think there's a lot of reasons it's burrowed into our brains,
partially like the debate that's gone on about it over the years.
Why don't we just get a general, before we even hash out the debate.
Fans of Pizza Rizzo.
Not fans of Pizza Rizzo.
Get these motherfuckers out of here!
Go get Gordon Ramsay fish and chips!
You can stay. I'm sorry, I just got mad.
The fact that the audience is a little torn, that was a little more anti than I expected.
That reflects a little bit that this has been a debate on our show since 2018.
That was the first that I was trying to do the forensics of when we started talking about this and for how long.
Let me just take you through what happened here.
I think around that time, Mike took a trip to Disney World.
He made reference to popping into Pizza Rizzo.
And with apologies, Mike, but I think you can take it because you're tough.
You're Orlando Mike, you're outlaw. You can do it.
You've got a big brave fanny pack and I think you can do it.
I'm going to read something that you said about Pizza Rizzo.
I was wrong. There he goes. He's all the way in the corner.
Uh oh. Now you did it.
He's under the table. We cannot even see the fanny pack.
Go ahead.
Okay. I'll try to do it quickly.
This quote was said by Mike.
It's supposedly a Muppet themed pizzeria and there's barely anything that would let you know it's Muppets.
How do we feel about this?
That wasn't, you know what? It's okay.
That wasn't a deafening boo.
It wasn't so bad.
You survived. You did it.
Was that it? Was it more?
Look at that.
Okay. Yes. Defend yourself. Defend yourself.
Well, look.
It was a quick trip.
So maybe I didn't notice all the little details, you know?
Maybe I didn't notice. Maybe I didn't go in the banquet room or the party room.
Well, I believe that is exactly what happened.
I think that you popped in there and you didn't go to the second floor,
which is kind of where the action is.
It's where the most theming is because really you just order downstairs
and the food is not particularly, there's not like Muppet puns in the titles of the items or whatever.
You go upstairs and that's where you see like, you know, brown derby style drawings of the characters
and it's where you have the banquet room, which we'll talk about in a little bit.
But that seems really like the heart of Pizzarizzo. Does that seem fairly accurate?
Okay. Yeah. I thought maybe you'd get a cheer, but it didn't get a cheer.
You don't have to.
I'm tired. This has been a very interactive show so far.
No, it's just so fun. You know, usually it's just us in a room.
We don't get to point to a bunch of people and make them all yell a lot.
Here we go. Yeah. See, I'm just addicted to it.
Drunk with power, yeah.
That's right. And liquor.
So, but here's where it went from just a statement that Mike made to a debate.
A friend of ours, Doug Jones. Oh, this wasn't even Doug on the show.
This was just he heard the episode and then texted Mike as soon as he possibly could,
Pizzarizzo is good. Yeah.
He made his arguments there, but then he came on and made his arguments on the show.
Here's something that he accused you of.
He said that you walked in, said this sucks, turned around and left.
And he felt that you didn't really give it a chance.
And from Doug Jones, that simple yet effective phrase, Pizzarizzo is good,
I think, has resonated certainly with me.
It's something that I questioned and wondered.
And like, do I agree with this statement?
Will I ever agree with this statement?
It also feels like, and I don't know, around this time, I also just started seeing it.
I remember seeing Jack Black wearing a Pizzarizzo shirt not long after this.
And I'm not saying our show did it because I don't think it did,
but it definitely felt like all of a sudden, like, maybe I unlocked, like,
my evil words unlocked some groundswell in general that swept the world,
because all of a sudden, I feel like the discourse was there
and I was not aware of it before that.
For once, our words did not, like, just kill an aging character actor.
Putting Pizzarizzo in the zeitgeist is much nicer, you know?
I believe our words, from what I've read,
our words have recently killed one of the Hooters in the Orlando area.
Our apologies if that's the one that you liked.
And we, of course, hate all of them, boo, Hooters.
We would never, you didn't tonight, did you, Mike?
I swear to God, if you went and you're not telling me.
Who thinks I went to Hooters tonight?
He would never tell you.
I won't tell you.
He's worried you're going to throw your drinks at him.
So that's one Hooters and potentially the most beloved cast member of Cheers.
Actually, that is not correct, because the episode where we mentioned
George Wint was recorded before, but hasn't come out.
That's a question, how does the PTR curse work?
If it's in the can, but we haven't put it in front of you,
does that mean that we killed the actor?
I refuse to accept that we killed George Wint.
I will not take that.
But what do you think? Did we do it?
Yeah, we recorded it like the day before.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
For me? Was it Casamigos, did you say?
Wow, Casamigos has arrived.
Thank God bless you.
Wow, Casamigos right on stage.
Where'd that come from, point yourselves out?
Yeah, who sent that to me?
This is where the trouble for me is I haven't identified
enough specific brands of liquor to have it sent to me.
You just sniffed that like you don't like it.
No, no, no, I was trying to act cool.
That's it, I could tell.
Do you have your usual tiny shaker of salt hidden in your shoe heel?
I have my little gun in the right shoe
and my little shaker of salt in my left shoe.
Your little gun in the shoe, you are turning Florida.
I guess I've got to do it real quick.
Oh, yeah, yeah, do it.
Oh, you shoot it, that was a shot, that was a shot.
Wow, damn, lime in the mouth.
Damn, dude, wow, wow.
Well, how about that?
You feel that tea rising?
I do feel like my tea jumped 50 points.
They're points, that's not a level of...
Orlando Mike, Orlando Mike's coming out.
I was hoping they were coming up here to scold you.
It's like, oh no, what did Mike do?
Well, we know what he did.
He didn't give Pizzarizzo full respect.
And then you started noticing that a lot of people out there,
like Jones included, like Pizzarizzo.
And something that we definitely have noticed
more and more as the years go on,
if Pizzarizzo is ever mentioned on the show,
we notice that one name is said,
of if you ever do Pizzarizzo on the show,
you need to have this person on the show.
And the biggest obstacle to doing this was that we had not met her.
This had not occurred yet, but now it has happened.
We met this person from the YouTube channel Park Stop
and the podcast Park Talk.
Please welcome Alicia Stella.
Alicia Stella, everybody.
Yay.
You know, it's amazing.
If anyone... Is this on?
I think it is.
If anyone talks about Pizzarizzo for more than five minutes,
I materialize at anywhere you are.
Right. It's like, yes, Beetlejuice scenario situation.
Pizzarizzo three times, here I am.
Wow. Well, and we're so glad that you are.
This is a good excuse just to meet you in general.
And we figured we might end up meeting you, you know,
just tonight right before the show,
but instead we ended up meeting you yesterday.
And why is that? Where were you yesterday?
That's the weirdest thing. I was in Pizzarizzo.
Where was I in Pizzarizzo, by the way? Where did you find me?
Well, you know, unlike, admittedly,
most days of this quick service pizza restaurant being open,
there was not a line and stanchions out the door
anticipating the crowds that were coming.
But on this final day, there was a queue set up.
There was a rope drop for Pizzarizzo,
and who was not just in it, but number one in line,
but Alicia Stella.
You know, it disappointed me, too,
that when I got there, there wasn't already a line
because I thought I was late. Oh.
I thought there's got to be like 10, 15 people that are going to be there
because the park's been open for half an hour already.
And no, I was first and I stayed first for another half hour.
And I don't know if that's like testament to me or Pizzarizzo,
but that place was packed when you found me
at the back of the upstairs like a mafia boss eating spaghetti.
I'm in that back booth.
This is my restaurant.
I can see clear across and seeing it full for the first
and literally last time was magical, to be honest.
Well, that mafia boss, you must have felt that way
because how many people came up to you?
How many people talked to you, recognized you?
This must have been, like, you really must have felt like you were in your element.
I mean, it was next to the bathroom,
so I feel like people were accidentally finding me.
You can't take credit for people needing to use the bathroom.
That doesn't have to happen.
You are obviously very associated with Pizzarizzo.
Can you broadly answer the question,
why is it that for five years we just say,
Pizzarizzo, we've got to talk about it some day,
and so many people would say, you have to talk to Alicia Stella.
Do you know why that was four years ago?
Anytime anyone said even the most slightly negative thing about Pizzarizzo,
I have felt like it is my duty to defend it
because it is not the worst pizza at Walt Disney World.
It is the second worst, okay?
It has A.C. and very little buildings in that whole park have A.C.
So, like, Disney food blog, I love you.
I love AJ. Oh, I love you.
But, man, every single time, the 10 worst restaurants at Walt Disney World
and the thumbnail is Pizzarizzo.
And it's like, AJ, come on, please,
pick a different thing to rag on just once.
Can I, will you reveal the worst pizza?
Oh, it's Pinocchio's Village House in Magic Kingdom.
Okay, great.
It's not pizza.
It's if you put Play-Doh on the carpet,
smooshed it out, tomato sauce from SpaghettiOs, and didn't cook it.
Yeah, I feel like a pizza place in the dead center of fantasy land
is not going to be very authentico, you know?
Pizzarizzo is great because it's small, but it's a large pizza for a rat.
It's rat-sized pizza. That's why it's rat-sized.
Oh, that's all right.
I like how you canonically absorb that. That makes sense.
You also, for anyone just listening to this, as she referred to a rat,
she held up a rat because Rizzo is here. She brought Rizzo.
Hey, how you doing?
You know, when you got to see the quiet Muppet Vision,
was your pre-show also quiet?
Because every time they introduced Mickey Mouse and it was Rizzo,
the crowd went wild in my pre-shows.
Well, this is a sad thing. You know what happened to us?
We were rushed through the pre-show.
I didn't get to say goodbye to the pre-show.
I'm the person who doesn't like cues and stuff,
and I was dying to see that pre-show.
I especially wanted to see Rizzo as Mickey.
I'm really sad I didn't get to see it.
We asked, like, we said, like, we'll just stay. We'll stay.
We'll just stay. And they said, you can't do that.
There are 700 people coming to every screening of this today.
Any other day, you could have done that.
Could have? Why did I listen to that person?
I'm non-confrontational.
I like hiding under tables just as much as Mike does.
I made my pilgrimage to both Muppet Vision 3D and Pizza Rizzo on Wednesday
and just kind of sauntered into both.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. A normal day.
A normal day, yeah.
There was plenty of people in both,
but yeah, it was a little more manageable,
which was why I went then.
Yeah.
So not only people are, you know, connecting the dots,
you know, between you and us, re-Pizza Rizzo,
but you also just, you spoke to a different media outlet
two days ago, you said, about Pizza Rizzo.
Would you like to say what that was?
The story hasn't come out yet, but I spoke to the Wall Street Journal.
They're like,
do you have a moment of your time for a very important interview?
And I get on the phone like, so what about Pizza Rizzo?
The state of the world, and you're calling me, you know what?
It is that important. It is.
We talked for 28 minutes, by the way.
I spoke to them once, and I talked a lot,
and they just used my explanation of what rides are.
Like, they just used, like, this, the Haunted Mansion,
a scary haunted house that you go through in a doombuggy.
And they cut whenever I was like,
here's what's really special about it.
So I just sounded like an idiot with a little stipple drawing.
They contacted you for exposition.
Basically.
Boo, release the transcripts.
Release the full Jason tapes, damn it.
And the stipple drawing next to me is Tony Baxter.
And I'm like, okay, well, this is not maybe punching above my weight here.
Nonsense, nonsense.
Two experts.
Just two people explaining lines.
You waited a line, and then you enjoy the thing.
You are good at exposition, I must say.
Thank you.
Excellent exposition work tonight from Jason.
You are clearly doing, like, a full media tour,
because you're here with us.
You were there all day yesterday, Wall Street Journal,
and then you're doing your on-the-ground reporting and discussion of it,
because I noticed I'm like...
Yeah, I'll be there tomorrow to vlog, so I'll get to do my own coverage, you know.
Geez, wow.
There's so many ways to experience your views on Pizzeria Rizzo,
including on X.
You said, you just posted two photos, and you said,
my final Pizzeria Rizzo, and that received over 2,000 likes.
Massive, you're putting up stats.
You are so, like, the algorithms are pushing people.
One of my posts was up to 4,000.
I did a Last Supper, because that table is, like, really long,
but it has, like, a bench.
So, like, me and my friends were all sitting there,
and I'm like, I'm not in the center, though.
Rizzo is in the center, first of all.
It's very important.
It's a distinction there.
The Jesus of Pizzeria Rizzo.
Yeah, Rizzo won.
Rizzo won.
But, yeah, I didn't see, like, I was just randomly posting things
to Twitter, by the way.
It's called Twitter.
I wanted to.
I should have.
I go home at 3 a.m. in the morning, and I'm like,
4,000, 5,000 likes, 6,000 likes?
What, are people vicariously living through my Pizzeria Rizzo
last experience?
Good, good.
Wow, wow, you provided a VR patch
right into the last day.
When you've done a lot of writing about it,
I also noticed you wrote something for touring plans.
I'm going to read your own writing to you,
because this is like...
Good, right?
Do I have to get under the table?
You are not mentioned in it.
Good, good.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
No, no, no.
This is a thing to be celebrated, I think.
This was years ago.
I don't know what you wrote.
I think you'll sign off on it today.
What you bring up is the struggle of admitting
that you're a Pizzeria Rizzo fan.
You know, what with mics out there trying to shame you.
You said, I'm not going to lie.
It was hard to admit at first
that I actually like Pizzeria Rizzo.
There was a time not long ago
when it just wasn't something you admitted out loud.
Sure, you might go there...
There's a weird Pride story going on in this.
Sure, you might go there and enjoy your meal
between rides on Tower of Terror,
but you wouldn't dare post a pic of the, quote, pizza.
You did still.
That is still an interesting choice.
Well, it's not pizza.
It's rat pizza.
You wouldn't post a pic of the pizza on Pizzeria Rizzo.
Then one day I decided to just let the world know,
I like Pizzeria Rizzo.
It's a coming out story.
You just do a little copy...
Oh, we signed this correctly, calendar-wise.
I think it really shows the trajectory
of trying to improve the image of Pizzeria Rizzo
that just a few years ago,
I had to frame it in such a way
that others could come forward,
that it can't just be me and Jack Black,
that others must know that this pizza is somewhat edible
and this location has AC.
Well, let's talk about...
Why don't we do kind of a gradient
from things that are sort of undeniable about it,
that are fun about it,
to things that maybe require a little bit more debate?
Because in that article,
you said the six best things about Pizzeria Rizzo.
You mentioned the air conditioning.
This is an important aspect, obviously.
That's literally one of the six.
So there is that.
What is your favorite?
Because I noticed yesterday,
you didn't go up and eat in the banquet room.
You ate over by the...
You did the last supper table, as you said.
You ate over by the caricatures,
the sort of classic Hollywood caricatures
of so many Muppets.
And Muppets, it goes deep.
It goes deep into characters whose names I don't know
and won't try to say,
because we'll get a lot of comments and emails about it.
For me, personally,
and it's going to be weird using past tense terms,
but I would sit upstairs.
I like the red and white tablecloth.
I feel like the schmaltzy Italian music,
the red and white tablecloth,
the frozen cannolis that come to you
and by the time you go to eat it for dessert,
it's finally de-chilled.
It reminds me of going to pizzerias
and Italian restaurants of my youth.
This is like the 80s and 90s Italian restaurant experience,
where if Frank Sinatra's playing
or everybody mambo's playing in the background,
I feel like I'm back there in my childhood.
So you go in the ballroom
and it's playing 90s party music.
I want to get up and dance.
That's not what I want.
I want a quiet meal with Frank Sinatra in my ear.
Oh, interesting.
That makes sense.
That's a very well-justified choice.
So are you fond of any of those pieces of art in particular?
There's some fake records on the wall that I'm quite fond of,
little puns there.
There's actually a piece.
There was a piece of The Streets of America on the wall.
This is tough.
This is tough, isn't it?
This is hard.
I'm going to cry by the end of this.
This is some weird get-me-to-cry-on-stage experiment.
It's not a trick.
It's not a trap, I swear.
Yeah, there was a subway station sign
from The Streets of America that closed down
and they put it in there.
So it's funny that that's now got to move.
It's like a time capsule.
We've got to move to a different location.
Maybe it could be part of Monstropolis.
Oh, sure.
They just put an eyeball on it.
Mark my words.
Anything that remains from the Muppet Courtyard
and stays from Monstropolis, they'll paint an eyeball on it.
Oh, yeah.
That makes a lot of sense.
That's easy.
That's only two colors, Max.
Got to save that money.
So yeah, okay, you got records.
You got an Electric Mayhem record.
There was a record by the Mice Girls.
Is that correct?
That's disgusting.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
That being a Spice Girls.
But only four.
Why are there only four?
What happened there?
I guess they were portraying the era
post-Gerber Mice leaving.
Yeah, when Jerry left.
Mice?
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, mousetraps are a thing.
I don't know where you're getting it.
Oh, no.
One of the Mice Girls got snapped.
Yeah, yeah.
Mice have lots of babies.
It's a numbers game.
We're off track.
There's photos all over the wall.
There was photos all over the wall.
Okay, take your time.
They Photoshop rats into real photos.
So it's like just people in New York,
and then there's a rat, and they're Muppet rats.
So it's like, this is Muppet themed.
There was little hidden gags.
Like the ballroom, the banquet hall
has a sign that says who's getting married.
And it's like Phil and Jill.
And if you remember Muppets Take Manhattan,
it's like, what do you think, Phil?
What do you think, Jill?
It was like the marketing people.
Anyway.
Yes, when Kermit forgets who he is,
and then he knows all of these people
whose names rhyme.
Yeah.
This is one of the big things.
It's like a push pin.
Like it's a sign where you push the letters.
Yeah, and then the letter behind it,
you can see faded letters for Emmett Otter,
a jug band that was performing there.
And that's like a deep cut,
because that's not even on Disney+.
That is weird.
That's really strange.
As we hope that Muppet Vision 3D will end up,
damn it, right?
They have to put it there, don't they?
I mean, it's hard to get an applause out of that,
because we all still secretly hope
they're going to move it somewhere else.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Everyone in this room is like Magic Eye Theater,
or that villain show they just opened.
They put real seats in there, clearly.
That's for the Muppet.
Yeah, can't they move it to one of the,
like, five Disney World movie theaters
that show essentially nothing?
There's so many.
You don't like 3D DVD extras?
But I swear, there's one of those
where they're still showing just a preview
of the Tim Allen Shaggy Dog.
No one's noticed.
No one's tried to go in.
Well, Scott, it's a double feature.
It's half Shaggy Dog and half Changing Gears.
15 years.
Let's all correct Jason about the show
none of us have watched.
They're filming it with cast members on Tuesday,
I believe.
Oh, right, right.
Hopefully they get the curtain working,
or at least fake it, have people quietly on the floor
moving the curtain.
Oh, sure.
But they're not going to move the musket
like animatronic stuff.
They're just not going to do it set, I don't think.
No, no.
So it'll be, anyway.
Is there any way to...
It's a quiet sadness throughout the audience.
We're all in the bargaining phase at this point.
Like, can't we just get a mini version
somewhere in the park?
With the large bar in back,
this is essentially an Irish wake for a pizzeria.
That's a good point.
Everyone gets sloppy drunk, we'll understand.
We all have to cope.
It is funny that, though, that this is like,
you know, we've maybe said, like,
I don't know, is the place a little light on theming?
And then the response is, no, there is a cork board
with faded letters of an otter's funeral.
What's great is that I actually covered the opening of this.
I was looking back at my article from 2016, December,
when it first opened, and I'm looking at the bulletin board,
and I'm like, they actually added more photos
and little things to the bulletin board.
So this four-foot space has more theming
than it did when it opened.
So if anything, they've doubled the amount
of Muppet theming in there.
Wow.
It went from 12 Muppet pieces of paper to 24.
Well, this is, let me bring up, this is maybe,
this is a serious debate, this is a serious thing to bring up.
Maybe some of the disappointment,
or just feeling like, all right,
if anyone is not super in love with Pizzeria Rizzo,
was it that when you think of a Muppet restaurant,
you think of a crazy madcap place
with a bunch of animatronics or puppets
or videos of things going haywire.
Like, that might be the, and you know,
and that's probably not the fault of the,
like, they probably got an amount of,
that was the original concept, is what we have just been told.
Yeah, Melrose was actually built and designed
to be Gonzo's Pizza Pandemonium, I believe?
Pandemonium Pizza Parlor.
There's no other room where you can shout that
and expect recognition.
It's amazing, it's interactive.
You can still see the wood,
the rats were going to be above you.
The rafters, the legend is that the rafters were built there
for tracked animatronics to be bringing the food back and forth,
rats bringing the food back and forth.
And there was, something happened,
I can't quite put my finger on it,
but something big happened that I'd rather not get into
because Jim Henson passed away.
Oh, right, that, okay.
There was a plan for a big, giant great Muppet movie ride,
there was a plan for this whole area to be Muppet studios
and they kind of backtracked
and they turned it into Mama Melrose last minute
because they weren't even sure they were going to have a Muppet area.
Wow, right, wow.
Because, yeah, Disney was actually going to buy the entire Muppets
and that got sidetracked for years.
What a strange thing.
So, like, there was, like, the madcap Muppet restaurant of our dreams,
so how does it go from that to, like, many, many years later,
it is suddenly open and there's a couple of bulletin boards.
You know, don't make me say the words modern Disney.
Ah.
Because I try to be positive on my podcast
and it's hard to be realistic and say...
Same aura has been said, yes, you're right.
I didn't, when I, in 2018, when I was criticizing it,
I didn't say these stupid Imagineers, why would they do this, right?
I didn't say that, right?
I don't know, check the, Doug Jones will have to tell us.
Never blame the Imagineers.
Did I say that?
Imagineers have great ideas, it's the money.
It's the money.
Always the money, yes.
No, and that's what, yeah, and if we're mad about things, it's that.
Because I'm sure if you asked Imagineers,
would you like to build 20 animatronics and rats exploding out of every wall,
or would you like 24 pieces of paper?
I think they would pick the animatronics.
But I guess you have to go, all right, well, if this is,
if what was budgeted was, like, kind of a quick turnover of the Toy Story thing,
then I think you can tell that it was done with love
by people who liked the Muppets, who were deep Muppets fans,
and who put those in the Easter eggs end.
They printed out as many things on that laser printer as they could afford.
They put it in as many Walmart frames on that wall as they could.
Color, ink, even, it's more expensive.
You can feel the love was in, you know, the Photoshop.
The theming budget might be $150.
Yeah.
It's like if we asked somebody to leave here, we handed them cash,
will you go make a corkboard and bring it back for the late show?
Have you guys been to Regal Eagle?
No, I haven't.
Audience has. They're an enthusiastic.
We still have a lightly themed Muppet quick service restaurant at Walt Disney World.
It exists.
And it is even lighter themed.
It has four pictures.
One for each barbecue sauce.
How is the barbecue?
I mean, it's really good.
Oh, good.
It's shockingly good.
Good.
Like, I have to, like, beat around the bush on the Pizzarrizzo.
High food standards in World Showcase.
So, happy to hear that.
Well, that's interesting that the food is good.
Because...
So, one thing, I got to, you know, I went into Pizzarrizzo
and I explored it a couple of years ago.
And we'll talk about some of that stuff in a minute.
And I came to appreciate the Easter eggs in the theming.
But yesterday was the first time that I tried the food.
Okay, you know, I'll make my way to the table.
I'm sorry.
And I'll very meekly say,
what would a Pizzarrizzo fan say to somebody who thought
that maybe it wasn't the best food that they've ever had?
Look, I use the quote when I call it pizza
because it's really a pizza bread bowl.
Now, think about it.
So, I just need to change my thinking is all.
If I am thinking of it as pizza, I might be very disappointed.
Yeah.
You don't have to use the modifier very, but go ahead.
You just change the incognito behavioral therapy.
We say change the lens that you're using to look at something.
It's a bread bowl with a baked crust.
It explains the amount of bread around it.
Yeah.
The toppings in the center,
because those are the pizza bowl filling.
It really is.
You get the quickest little smattering right in the middle.
It really is like pizza, but tired of all that cheese.
Yeah, it's a lot of crust.
Yeah, you know, Jason, we weren't with you.
So, we don't know your opinions at all.
What did you think a couple of days ago?
You know, I had walked through it a few times before
and liked it, but Wednesday was the first time I ate it.
And it was a little earlier in the day,
so Jane and I split a cheese pizza which came with Caesar salad.
Now, for years I've wondered,
what is with this tiny Caesar salad?
People must love this thing.
And I didn't realize it came with it.
Oh, you thought people were ordering it in addition?
I thought people were like, oh, I want some vegetables.
The other option just said carrots.
So, I'm assuming it was a wet bag of baby carrots.
You thought it was the new butter beer.
Everybody's having the Caesar salad.
But I went through the mobile order too quickly
because I missed the partially frozen cannoli.
Oh, yeah.
As someone who spent a lot of time growing up on boardwalks,
I love a frosty cannoli.
But yeah, pizza risotto, it was very crust heavy.
Just say it was edible. It was edible, right?
It was.
Ah, woo! It was edible!
It reminded me of back east where it's like,
oh, you want to order in?
Do you want to do this or that pizza?
It's like, oh, I'm sick of those.
We can do DiCenzo.
It's like, ah, it's okay.
I guess we'll do it for a change.
That was pizza risotto.
What a review.
Yes, these created edible.
If they put that in a banner over the door,
people would be like, I guess.
Third or fourth choice, it's something.
It was like my high school cafeteria pizza.
It was definitely some sort of like, you could buy this in bulk.
Maybe it was probably just frozen.
I don't know how they prepared it.
I'm just saying.
But the pizza in high school was probably prepared already.
And it was like 45% crust.
Wait, you didn't have the square trays of pizza
that they cut with the roller?
You missed out.
No, we weren't so lucky to have those.
But then they had just a very sugary tomato sauce.
I feel like it's the same as it was in my high school cafeteria pizza.
What I wrote down was that the sauce tasted like tomato by way of metal.
There was a metallic taste, yes?
Yes.
I believe Dave Meske is with us, your buddy.
I think I'm quoting him correctly when he took a bite and then had some water.
And he said, I think the water enhanced the flavor.
It's like ingredients of a soup add water, and then the flavors come to life.
Oh, I did have a non-alcoholic mocktail.
It was an alcohol-free peach Bellini.
Oh, the specialty of the house.
Yeah, it was the specialty.
And it was delicious.
It tasted like I was just drinking slurpee syrup.
Yeah.
I know, it was great.
We should have gotten that.
That sounds good.
It was.
It was really good.
Oh, boy.
Can I ask, is there a chance, do we know this is getting demolished?
Well, it's in all the concept art.
It is, right?
That's exactly the same building.
Even the big billboard that says it's rat pizza is still in the concept art,
but with like an advert for Monsters Incorporated.
So, pizza razo is what I've been pitching.
Pizza razo, it's always watching.
That's good.
That's pretty good.
Right there, right there.
Because honestly, it's not like it changed that much from Pizza Planet.
They just took away the video games and the fun.
You know what they'll do, too, to your point about the eyes?
It'll be the little bready circle.
One giant pepperoni.
Yeah, one big pepperoni.
And then they'll pass that off as like, why did I only get one?
It's fun.
It's because that's the pupil.
It's the Mike Wazowski pie.
The Mike Wazowski pie.
It's Instagrammable.
This is going to go viral.
I have a feeling there's going to be a lot of Mike Wazowski-themed stuff in the Monsters area.
A lot of just a circle, you know?
Maybe two.
Sounds modern Disney to me.
Oh no, oh no.
What have I done?
Let's talk about the cannoli a little bit.
I felt like narratively as I was disappointed by each eye.
And I really, because I'm like, I have an audience.
I want to come and say the food was wonderful and get a cheer.
And then I'm like, I have to live my truth.
By the way, he was worried yesterday.
Not that I'm not worried now.
I'm just saying, what are we going to tell them?
You literally have the biggest fan of all time of this restaurant.
And I'm calling it mid.
You have nothing to worry about.
It's okay.
I can rely.
Now I know where the bar is.
The bar is at Edible.
But Scott has a car running back over in the parking garage to get out of here if he needs to.
After that pizza review he just gave.
Look, I have spent a lot of years getting booed about living with the land.
I'm always prepared for the worst.
Yeah, see?
Boo this man.
Get him out of here.
Get him out.
Some audiences' reactions I don't like.
But I bet I'm not going to get that same degree of boo about the cannoli.
I wanted to...
Narratively I was like, this must be...
I didn't like the pizza.
This salad, I might say, is the literal worst salad I've ever had in my life.
So it has to be that the cannoli will save the whole thing.
And here's what happened.
I took a bite of it.
I put it in my mouth and I said, mmm.
Because I wanted that narrative to be true.
And then I chewed and I chewed.
And 10 to 15 seconds went by.
And our buddy Andrew Grissom, who came out with us, said,
Scott, I noticed you haven't swallowed your bite yet.
And even I hadn't noticed.
I wanted to like the taste so very much, but it just sat there.
It just sat there like I was chewing a paper towel.
Look, what I left out is that the pizzerias and Italian restaurants of my youth were terrible.
Nostalgia works in funny ways like that.
What cities are we talking about?
What part of the country?
South Florida.
A lot of old retirees.
A lot of retirees.
Ah, Naples.
No taste buds.
Pizza capital.
No, Naples, Florida.
What?
Is Pompano Beach not known for its pizza?
I started...
We did eat in the banquet room, which we should talk about a little more.
Because a lot of the places is tables and it is restaurant style.
And then you have...
I mean, it is this delightful room that is like a room that you could rent out theoretically, canonically.
In story, yeah.
Yes.
And there's signage saying that it can fit 125 people, which equals 700 rats.
Just like that, which I like.
And then it does have this old Italian wedding venue vibe.
I mean, that's great.
It's a lot of fun in there.
Mike, you were wrong to not go up into there in 2018, I have to say.
I was...
Well, thank you for scolding me.
Yes, I agree.
I'm just trying to get you booed.
I'm trying to even the score.
Not going to work.
I know, I know that.
I'm too below.
I know that.
The only person who's not getting booed whatsoever tonight is Jason.
This much we know.
Well...
Will not happen.
Thank you.
And I liked that there was some music playing.
We sat down and there was music playing and you'd see one person dancing.
But mostly people eating it very seriously, much like the viewings of Muppet Vision 3D.
Everybody was so mournful and just slicing and cutting.
Or maybe that was just their live reaction to the food that they were eating.
I mean, it sounds like you're around tourists in 92 degree heat.
Yes, good point.
They're dead inside.
It's day three at Disney World.
That's a good point, yes.
But there would be a sign, hey, we walked in and don't stop until you get enough is playing.
And then eight minutes of silence.
And then another song.
Why is that such a long break between songs?
Plenty of songs to be played.
I think the world has at least a thousand songs they can play.
See, I had a different experience.
There was a bunch of kids and adults dancing on the dance floor.
So it definitely added to the atmosphere.
Yeah, but there's such long breaks between the songs.
Yeah.
You have to give the kids a break so they can go eat their kid's meal,
which is a smaller version of Pizza Rizzo's pizza.
Yes, we got one kid's meal.
That's what Andrew Grissom, our buddy, had, the smaller version.
And I want to say he did not finish the smaller version.
But he was getting up to dance very often.
Now, there is a touch of old Disney in the restaurant in that when you order a soda,
they don't give you a lid, just like the 1970s Disney.
That's a very specific poll.
This was a no lid time.
They didn't care if you get rain drip drops in your soda throughout the day.
Yeah, a little lead paint to enhance the theming.
There are no lids at Disney World anymore unless you go to the DVC lounge.
Is that true?
Yeah, you've got to get the points before they get a lid.
Oh, jeez.
When did they get everything?
When did they get rid of lids?
When they got rid of plastic straws.
Really?
Yeah.
Is it a Biden thing?
And they hide the paper straws behind the counter, so you have to ask for them.
Oh, wow, really?
And they dissolve within a minute, so you have to keep asking for them.
You have to use nine paper straws in one drink.
Wow, I didn't realize that, no, there were no lids.
Now you know.
Now you've all learned.
At one point, a song that I like came on, Footloose, by Kenny Loggins,
and I started making up my own song along to it because it kicked in right as my stomach was starting to feel a little not great,
and I changed the lyrics and I turned it into this.
I'm going to get stool loose, stool loose, diarrhea out my caboose.
He pulled this real quick, too.
I saw it happen in real time.
I had to transcribe it.
It's pouring out of me.
He didn't work very hard on it.
I almost used the queasiness as an excuse to be a little, to revert to my no-launch Queen ways and to not go on rock and roller coaster,
but I fought through the bizarre salad and through the tasteless cannoli,
and I did the ride, and I survived, and I did not end up.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
A cheer.
Let's hold on to that.
Let's hold on to the cheer part.
I like that.
It should have been on the banner.
You may not puke this up on roller coasters.
Good.
But I, okay, you know what I think it might be time to do is that, you know, we've, we've, we've,
this has been wonderful spending time with you, somebody who has a lot of pizza riso credentials.
You know, you know, a Riz, as they say, a lot of Riz.
And there's somebody else here who I think has credentials possibly to match because, you know, we've all,
now we're all people who have eaten at Pizza Rizzo, in one case talked to the Wall Street Journal about Pizza Rizzo,
but there is somebody here who worked at Pizza Rizzo.
Seemingly because of our show.
Seemingly we caused employment.
And I am so curious to ask some questions about this.
So now I would like to welcome to the stage, I'm so happy to welcome one of the best listeners a podcast could ask for,
Malia Schnefke.
Wow, in a Kermit column. Malia, hi, hey, good to see you.
So thrilled to be here with Alicia for the Pride Month episode of Podcast the Ride.
What was just shouted? What was just shouted?
Somebody shouted something?
Queen of Rat Pizza!
Queen of Rat Pizza! Wow!
This is why you get to hold court where people are yelling Queen of Rat Pizza at you.
Now there are two people on the stage with pizza slice earrings.
Did you all not get the memo?
Yeah, I'm sorry. I should have gotten pierced.
I left my mind out for too long in the holes.
Is there a Claire's near here?
Statistically, yes. Very likely.
Most likely. So glad you could be here. Thank you for joining us on stage again here at Tin Roof as you did last year.
This is the only room I've ever been popular in.
This will change. This will change on this day because popularity is deserved.
It's been great meeting you through the years, including that I met you the first time at Pizzarizzo when you worked there.
I did. Very true.
That was one of those Disney World fun little happenings where I indicated that I was there and you threw out,
hey, I'm working if you want some rat pizza, and I was like, yes, I can make that work. I can pop in and do it.
And that was so delightful, I think four years ago or so.
So four years ago, as you may all remember, there was a small thing called the coronavirus pandemic.
And everyone that worked at Disney World got laid off via email at about 4 p.m. on a Saturday.
Oh, my God. Modern Disney.
What were you doing then?
So I was actually working in costuming for some of the shows in Magic Kingdom.
And they all said, we're good. Thank you so much.
And eventually they said, you can come back to work, but all that we have available is quick service food and beverage.
And I thought, I don't need to do that unless because of this show and because of the Pizzarizzo lore,
I thought if my way to work back at Disney World is working in quick service at Pizzarizzo, that would be really funny.
And so I asked the recruiter in my interview, I said, I don't really want to work quick service.
But if you have a spot at Pizzarizzo, I would do that.
And wouldn't you know, in about June 2021, not a lot of people wanted to serve at pizza.
But someone had to answer the call. And that was me.
Wow. What a tale.
Thank you for your service.
Thank you so much.
Now, Scott went through Pizzarizzo when he was there in 2021 and met you.
I went through in 2021 and I asked, oh, is Mel working today?
And they told me they are off today.
Somebody had to do it.
How dare you? You should be there seven days a week.
Saving away for the rats.
Okay. So and you've sort of assessed this as like, you've posted about like, I got a job there for the bit, essentially.
This is a rare, this is an incredible thing to get to do, a bit job.
So lest anyone doubt my credentials, I did work at Pizzarizzo for almost six entire months because I thought that it would be funny.
And it was.
Okay. Day to day, just what are like, was there just a basic fundamental, it is funny and you were proud that like my job today is the rat pizza restaurant?
It was also absolute hell.
Oh, that too?
The people that work in quick service food and beverage are our strongest soldiers.
That job is miserable.
This, I, if you guys are familiar, it might be a little bit past your time, but Club Penguin, the online game, had a little mini game where you would work in the kind of pizza restaurant.
And it would just go faster and faster and you would put toppings on the little pre-made pizzas until you lost.
And that is sort of what working at Pizzarizzo was like.
Except I was like putting pepperoni and sausage onto like frozen DiGiorno pizzas and burning all my fingertips off.
So if you need anything crimes committed, I don't have fingertips because of Pizzarizzo.
Wait, so you have like information, you have like intel.
Oh, absolutely.
I can ask you questions about how Rizzo, like as a boss, like worked.
Okay, how early in the morning are the Caesar salads made and how long do they sit in the fridge?
So they are made actually every day.
And it was one of the fun jobs because you just sort of put on these very long food service gloves and they gave you just sort of a bucket as well as like.
That tracks.
Ah, the classic salad bucket.
Yeah.
And so you would have your pre-shredded lettuce that you would tear out of the little plastic bags and your giant plastic container of Caesar dressing and you would just sort of mix it together.
Like a vat, like a vat.
Yeah, absolutely.
And you would just hand mix it together at about 8 a.m. every day and you would put it in all the little cups.
And like as far as jobs there went, it was pretty fun.
I like the three or four croutons right on top.
Yeah, absolutely.
Especially after they've been in the fridge like six or seven hours.
Just hard as a rock.
It's so good.
So good.
What's the is there something that you like?
Is it all just like the answer is it's it's just frozen and remade and it's just whatever.
Or did you see anything that would we would all be aghast at?
I don't think so.
Like as far as quick service restaurants like at Disney go like Pizza Rizzo and Mama Melrose's did share a like back of house kitchen space.
And so a lot of the stuff that we had was the same as what they had.
And I don't think a lot of people really put that respect.
It's amazing because I spent thirty eight dollars on an entree at Mama Melrose a couple of weeks ago.
OK, but yeah.
But the smell could not be beat.
Priceless wood firewood burning stove in theory.
Sure.
Actually, what was the smell situation day to day?
So this was during covid.
And so I was just wearing the heaviest, hottest denim shirt and pants that you've ever seen in your life as well as like full double masked at the hottest oven you've ever seen.
Just absolutely dying, waterboarding myself with sweat, like cutting pizzas, burning my fingertips off.
But it was, again, very funny.
And I didn't have anything else to do.
I mean, you're right.
Did you hurt your arms hand tossing that dough?
Wait, wait, wait.
Can we talk about the oven?
Is it load bearing?
And that's why it has to be a pizza restaurant every time they redo the land.
When you have a pesto pizza in six to eight years when Monsters Inc.
Land reopens and it's a pesto pizza with the coldest, driest burrata you've ever seen to me.
Mike Wazowski's little eye.
One little olive on top.
Sorry.
That's actually burrata.
There are standards for burrata.
They can't call it that.
But if you draw the O.
And you draw a smaller O inside and then a filled in circle, Mike Wazowski.
Something else happened, not during your employment, but that came from your love of this place.
And that is that what I have caught is that some sort of event was held.
And that, if I am correct, the event was Pizza Rizzo Prom.
That's right.
Who were your, well, you know, at first, tell us a little bit about Pizza Rizzo Prom.
So I think the idea of having a prom in the Pizza Rizzo banquet room had been sort of a joke amongst friends for a very long time.
Because you go there and you have a pizza restaurant.
And you think that it might be fun to put on very elaborate dress and like go hang out there and drink some mobile ordered Bud Lights.
And so when the closure was announced, my friends, Taryn and Allie and I talked about how this was the time we have to throw a party.
And so when the closure was announced, my friends, Taryn and Allie and I talked about how this was the time we have to throw our Pizza Rizzo Prom before they take it away from us.
And so we did. We did it in February. Alicia came. It was an absolute delight.
I spent $160 on my dress.
As well you should.
I spent three months or how long was this since you announced? Looking for that dress.
I went prom shopping. I went total high school on this.
You have no idea. I made the joke that the three like happiest moments of my life was my wedding day, the birth of my child and Pizza Rizzo Prom.
And I don't think I'm kidding.
That was like the best experience.
Was anyone else here at Pizza Rizzo Prom?
I don't believe it.
It's 125 people in that room.
What was better? High school prom or Pizza Rizzo Prom?
Pizza Rizzo Prom without a doubt. I got to be gay there.
It's better to be an adult than be a teenager any day.
The vibe seemed a lot better than my high school prom.
Absolutely. It was so special.
What did y'all get up to? How did you make it special once you were in the prom event?
So right before the prom, I sort of got very scared that perhaps thousands of people might show up.
And I was going to get banned from Disney World because I we had no RSVP process.
And people from like the Disney food blog were reaching out and saying, hey, can we like write up about this so people can come?
And I said, you have one point four million Instagram followers.
Please do not do this so I don't get in trouble.
But all of our friends showed up and we wore silly little outfits.
We had a little costume contest and it was a delight.
We just sort of hung out and ate frozen pizza and did the Cupid shuffle.
Absolutely. Yeah, we had our mobile ordered Bud lights.
We took pictures and that is what prom should really be.
There there was a prom court. There was absolutely.
Yes, we had our little costume contest to sort of, you know, spread the love of prom court out and do something that was a little like fun for everybody.
So we had our different themes and people wore Muppet outfits.
People were kind of traditional prom outfits.
People dressed as Pizza Rizzo. Yes.
My friend Tara and my co-chair had a sort of very elaborate outfit that displayed the entire menu of Pizza Rizzo sort of about their person.
We had people dress up as the actual ballroom complete with like the little ivy walls and stuff.
By the way, co-chair.
There were their positions in the organization.
The loop of music in the in the room.
Yeah, it's small. It's about 30 minutes.
Yeah. Do you know all of it?
Like, could you remember?
You don't have to do it now.
I'm just saying. But you're like, oh, here.
I feel good by James Brown is coming up next.
I feel like there are like at a max 10 songs on that music loop.
And sometimes they just play without the pauses in between.
And then sometimes you have to wait eight minutes for the Cupid shuffle.
The DJ is taking a break. Absolutely.
This wasn't just that something was wrong that day.
This is a known thing about Pizza Rizzo, the eight minute music gaps.
I feel like that's a pretty new thing.
It didn't used to be like that.
Correct me if I'm wrong.
I actually had a concern that the floor was going to give out.
Because if anyone remembers this building when it was Pizza Planet, there was no room here.
There was just a balcony and you can see down into the ordering stations.
This is an addition that Rizzo built.
I don't trust Rizzo and his building code.
So it says it can hold 100 people.
We were like 70 to 90 people at our most.
And we're dancing all the same time on this tiny dance floor.
And I'm like having visions of like those other countries where the floor collapses at a wedding.
And I was so, I literally, I was having a heart attack.
I'm not enjoying the prom. I have to step outside.
I'm like, please don't die.
And loved ones like, so what happened?
How did Alicia die?
Well, long story.
Just as the fortune teller foretold.
But we did get that group photo.
Absolutely, it was so sweet.
It was truly the most special day.
Everybody was so cool and so chill.
And not weird and aggressive, which is what I was afraid was going to happen.
That I was going to get banned from Walt Disney World for inciting riots.
I think Muppet fans, we're a pretty calm bunch, surprisingly, considering how weird Muppets is.
Absolutely, very like earnest, kind-hearted, just like people ready to play.
It was a delight.
There were tourists outside the doors because we had took over the whole thing.
Small children that were like, what is happening?
And they're looking in like, what in the world?
Because we're dressed to the nines.
The assistant manager just making phone calls like, hey boss, there's people in the restaurant today.
What do I do?
There were like three people in business casual that were just sort of posted up outside.
And we sort of took turns going up and being like, hey, I promise we're all going to be cool.
This is all that this is.
We didn't bring our own like Bluetooth speaker.
We're not here to truly like start a riot and chain ourselves to this building.
Like we're just going to eat our frozen pizza and hang out.
And that is what happened.
And everybody was normal.
It was a delight.
Someone asked me where like how we smuggled in the disco ball or put up the decorations on the walls.
And it's like, no, this is how this always is.
It's always finally utilized.
Wow.
And that's potential.
Yeah.
That's one more thing it has.
We haven't brought up a disco ball.
It did have theming.
It had stuff.
I did see a tweet yesterday that, you know, Disney corporate was like asking people in more complicated outfits to please not pose for photos together in order to protect character integrity.
And if there has ever been a phrase that is called for a wedgie, it's we must protect character integrity.
Are you talking about the Muppets?
People brought Muppets so good that they were getting in trouble.
Yeah.
For having Muppets.
And it's like Disney, if you brought your own Muppets, we wouldn't have to take them.
Exactly.
Did somebody bring a Muppet and then have them throw the pizza up?
Was that?
Oh no, I'm sick.
They just throw it in their mouth and it falls out to the side.
They just throw it down, I guess.
We need to protect character integrity for when there's a single three second you'll miss it Janice that pops up when you get a launch on Rock and Rollercoaster.
They're going to move that Wilkins coffee can that was in the Pizzeria lobby into the queue of a new Rock and Rollercoaster and then you'll all see how much we care about Muppets.
There's going to be a flat for Animal on the big Hollywood sign on the ride.
That's what we were saying.
We think the theming on the new ride is going to be you go through Animal's mouth one time, the end.
As the end of the re-theme.
We will be lucky if we go through Animal's mouth.
Yes.
Can I predict real quick, I have a prediction the overlay will take two and a half weeks.
I've already said overnight, but okay.
It's like Price is Right rules.
You're going to win, I bet.
Here's the thing, if they bring back Ken Marino for the pre-show.
That'd be great.
What a nod.
Then I'll be okay.
Well, okay.
I mean, clearly what we're finding here is that this place has fostered community and fun.
So much like, you know, I think it was really about like baking pizza riso your own.
That was the answer.
That's what you did.
It's an empty shell that we could put whatever we wanted into it, literally and figuratively.
Yes, like the pizza itself, mostly empty.
But if you put your own, bring your own toppings, you could have a great time.
But what we're finding, I think, maybe what we're landing on is that that initial discussion of pizza riso is good.
I mean, the vibes feel pretty good right now, don't they?
I mean, it's getting much easier to make that verdict.
And when we were up there and meeting a bunch of listeners and talking to Alicia and seeing it full and packed and people in amazing shirts and everybody so nice up there,
I started thinking about where this all began.
And that like, you know, with the initial debate and pizza riso is good, that statement coming from our pal Doug.
So when I was up there, I texted him and I said, you know, we're doing a show tomorrow and it's going to be about pizza riso.
And I said, do you have a statement about the closing of pizza riso?
And he sent one. But then also then after sending the statement, he said, well, you know, I'm at L.A.X. right now.
I'm coming to the show. So now to make the statement officially here in person, pizza is the longest time defender on Podcast The Ride.
Please welcome our pal Doug Jones.
This is very brief statement.
This is basically what I texted you yesterday.
I'm just going to read it out loud in front of the audience.
Oh, well, thanks for saving me the reading work.
I mean, thank you for flying across the country so I could save my voice a little bit.
I'm so happy to see you, by the way, Doug.
Happy to have you on stage with us finally.
Let's you start at all this.
How do you feel right now?
I'll tell you how I felt yesterday when I texted you.
And then I'll follow that up by just my opinions on some things that were expressed on stage.
OK, OK. All right.
And this will all be very brief.
Here we go.
I never thought I'd get anyone to take me seriously.
Thank you, good boys and fellow Cliffords, for re-evaluating Pizza Rizzo as one of the finest theme park quick service restaurants of the 21st century.
We had to. We had to.
Thank you for your bravery so early.
Yes.
So early.
You spoke up just like you wanted.
Yes, we're speaking up.
But it seems like you have to speak up about some other stuff, too.
Just there was some criticism of the quality of the food.
And I just to that, I just want to say, shut up.
It's it's fucking rat pizza.
Wow.
Doug, you said it.
Aggressive.
It's fucking rat pizza.
I refuse to use the past tense here at the end of the show.
It is fucking rat pizza and Pizza Rizzo is good.
And who's here?
Stay up with us.
And let me say to the group and to all of you, you survived podcast the ride.
Oh, my God.
What a blast.
Our thanks to Alicia Stella.
Our thanks to Malia Schnefke.
Wow.
Thank you for being here.
Our thanks to Doug Jones.
I'm Scott Garner.
That's Mike Carlson and Jason Sheridan.
This was an absolute blast.
Thank you, everybody.
A tin roof Orlando.
Who's sticking around for the 10 o'clock?
Are we going to see again?
Good, good.
Thanks, everybody.
This has been a forever dog production, executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com and subscribe to our
shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever
dog team and liking our page on Facebook.