Five, four, three, two, one.
Tuna ho, it's podcast the ride, the second gate.
I'm Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson.
I'm here and I am excited because we've never really like dove into tuna a lot here.
We've dove, we've talked about subway tuna, which I'm a big fan of, but I feel
like Jason and I especially, and I don't want to get, he should talk for himself,
but I feel like Jason and I are a little tuna boys.
God damn it.
Right away.
I'm so sorry.
Do you want me to leave?
Do you want me to just stop recording now?
And in the first minute you get little tuna boy.
All right, well, let's let one of them talk.
Sorry, sorry.
I thought I was going to throw that to Mike cause I know he was a tuna guy,
but I was afraid I misremembered.
Now what you just said, tuna guy, that was interesting, right?
That has a ring to it, right?
That as I look in this room of older men with gray hairs, I think, yes,
tuna guy is a, I still don't love the tuna part, but then being a
tuna guy is strange to me, but doesn't, isn't that kind of a nice,
do you notice the words that were missing there?
Wasn't it nice to not have one of those weird words weighing us all down?
If we had said, if I had said tuna guy, I was sort of, it was a
negotiation in a lot of ways.
Cause now tuna guys feels good to you.
Tuna guys might not have felt good to you.
If I just came out and said, Jason, I are tuna guys.
You'd be like, what is that?
Why would you call yourself tuna guys?
Yes.
You know, you're totally right.
I said little tuna boys and now you're disgusted.
And now Jason says tuna guys.
And you're like, oh, thank God.
It feels like nothing.
I was trying to deescalate this.
Feel warm, like a warm bath.
Trying to meet you where you are.
This is how Jason, like good cop, bad cop people.
I was bad.
I was, I would talk this out before you guys had it here.
Now here's what I want to say.
Little tuna boy.
I want to say it on this show.
I want to say it with a microphone.
Well, Scott's going to freak out though.
He's going to try to leave.
So here's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to come in.
I'm going to say tuna gun.
And it's going to seem a little bit, uh, calm everybody down.
Look, when I was writing my notes last night, did the phrase a little
tuna boys crossed my mind.
Of course it did.
Then I wrote a lot about tuna and Scott.
I had a tuna based hijinx last night that I, I would say, I, I
mentioned it to my, Jane and I.
He had really to wind up for that, for that anecdote.
This is, well, it took a while last.
Okay.
So we ordered firehouse subs and we ordered from the special from city
walk, just to make sure it was external.
You're getting ahead of him.
Uh, I know this because he texted me separately.
Yeah, I texted him already.
Uh, cause he's a tuna guy.
Um, we ordered from the North Hollywood location closer to Burbank and the, uh,
door to Asher Postmates punted it to the city walk location.
You were forced into the land of nubs.
And it took a while because people had to figure it out.
And, and Jane get up there, park, get up there.
Where is it?
I'm sure there was a delivery pickup area.
There's a second ride chair closer to Bucca.
Sure.
Just
you will never let you just say Bucca, whether you have it right or wrong.
That's one thing, but you know, you're never going to get away with just the one
word there was, so we ordered a firehouse subs and I lucked out cause I
just had a cold two and a sub.
Uh, so mine was fine when we got there, but she did what are like the hot
vegetables toasted, so hers was pretty, uh, kind of a mutant when it arrived.
Oh my yikes.
So, uh, they, they forcibly switch massive.
How much time do you think that added to the old scenario?
Probably half an hour or so.
Yeah.
I mean, not a lot of time in the grand scheme of things.
Stuff in the valley is reasonably close together, but it's like.
It was one of those things where it's like, we'll arrive in 15 to 20 minutes.
Like, ah, okay.
Reasonable time for a sandwich.
And then it just kept ticking up and ticking up and the driver dropped and
like passed on the order halfway through.
And then a different driver had to get, I think they tried to drive
around city walk and then gave up.
God.
So either of you have any normal interactions with food delivery and food service?
It feels, I know I'm getting just one, you know, I'm getting a slanted view
via the podcast, but I feel like you guys don't have one normal meal where
everything goes, you're just magnets for high jinks.
Yeah, I don't know.
I've been mostly high jink free for a few weeks.
I don't recall trying to eat high jink free, you know, what we had
local Chinese restaurants are always great.
And I always try to default to their, uh, restaurant website because
they have their own delivery people.
Sometimes, but then sometimes you get tricked because you
think it's their own delivery.
And then it just sends you to an Uber Eats on occasion.
But no, I, there was a, I ordered a medium hot wing from Holland
Rays and they gave me medium plus the other day.
So that was a high jink worked out in your favor.
But some high jinks are medium plus just meaning a spicier.
So it's not quite, okay.
You can have quite the same spice to your house.
Or did you have to do that thing where you went closer to Allen Rays?
That's a whole other explanation.
No, they now deliver the Pasadena location really quick.
Pause it, pause that sense.
I just want to say this is an episode about the pirate ship that
used to be at Disneyland.
It was an 1855 thing.
Okay.
Now that I've said the topic, feel free to talk about whatever that
is for seven more minutes.
I just wanted to get it in so that we know what we're dealing with.
I appreciate that.
Yeah.
I got so excited about this episode and learning about it.
He never tells me he's excited about episode when we're coming over here.
And today he went, I'm excited about excited one.
Wow.
Yes, because I, I primarily because I learned like all the basic stuff.
I watched a YouTube video of how to make the tuna burger.
Um, then I also read there's a long Jim Hill post about this.
So I learned all this other interesting stuff about it.
Okay.
Great.
So we got a lot to do.
Well, before the interesting stuff, Mike, what were you going to say?
Well, he asked me the uninteresting question, so it wasn't like I
wanted to offer it up through.
Okay.
Holland raises a hot chicken restaurant that used to only deliver.
It only used to deliver up to a certain point in Hollywood.
So during pandemic, I used to drive down to my old apartment, which is in the
zone where it would deliver and pick up the chicken from a street corner.
And I would say, Oh, right over here and act like I lived in the apartment or
whatever, and then I would drive up to Burbank and now the Pasadena location
is in the zone, so I can just order it directly to the house.
If I want from postmates.
Wow.
Sorry, Scott.
What a tale.
I was mostly asking because as you know, I also live in Burbank and I was like,
Oh, Pasadena delivers.
I'd love to have that sandwich.
Wait, what?
Say that sentence again.
I said, if Pasadena delivers, I'd love to have that sandwich.
Okay.
Gotcha.
It almost sounded like you said lovers or something.
I.
Pasadena lovers.
Yeah, that's what I thought too.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's that hoagie mouth.
He just smushed words together.
That tuna hoagie.
It could be a tuna hoagie, right?
It could be a tuna hoagie.
That should become the standard.
Like if there is something you say that we don't understand, we let's just let
that should perennially.
We'll blame it on hoagie mouth.
I forget who invented that originally.
I've only seen the last few years, but that kind of sums up the dialect.
Great.
Okay.
Let's talk about what this is.
This is the chicken of the sea pirate ship.
This was a, uh, original Disneyland thing, not opening day a little bit later.
Uh, August 29th, 1955.
This was in fantasy land.
And though it was a little bit later, it does still count as a part of our
series, which is of course the class of.
Oh, well, what could I have done?
I played the wrong Sammy Hagar set.
I was supposed to play.
That's where it's supposed to be.
Uh, I can't drive 55, but I mistakenly played.
Tequila by Sammy and the Wobbos.
Um, you know, it worked out though, because the next lyric of this song is
my favorite lyric of the song.
Uh, check this out while I'm here.
Might require, uh, that was a little hoagie mouth that he sings.
Uh, she did a mean Macarena to, to the funky cold Medina.
Okay.
This is a lyric he wrote in 1999.
Well, it's somewhat topical, I guess.
I don't want to get us off on a tangent here, but in just in, now that we've,
this is the third one of these for, I've played a little Sammy Hagar clip
and this, this required me.
I was like, let me find up some other Hagar state.
He sucks.
He's terrible.
Right.
Scott, you really don't want to do this.
You don't want to do this.
Sangent timer.
You really.
What, what, give it, okay.
Well, this is a good test.
You need to argue quickly why he doesn't suck.
Well, I think some of the big Van Halen Sammy Hagar songs, does that
count in this, or are you talking about solo?
I think why can't this be love and dreams are great songs.
There's a couple other ones that I really like.
And I like some early Sammy Hagar, Van Hagar, nowhere close to, uh, David
Lee Roth, uh, I'm not, not even in the same ballpark.
It's, I deserve this after that fucking howling race.
I'm happy.
I'm trying to, I'm trying to appease the tangent gods.
I'm happy to talk about what I think about David Lee Roth, who hit the
stage recently for the first time in a few years, fully 70 years old, full
black leather, he looks good.
I don't know if he sounded so good, but he's still saying a lot of
shit that makes no fucking sense.
Yeah, that's what he does.
Yeah.
We're just doing it.
You know, we're doing the big carnival in the sky.
Like that crazy laugh.
He has his bill hater clip went around.
He was telling a story about, uh, yeah.
Uh, I, the van Halen, uh, with, with David Lee Roth is very unique and specific.
And I, I understand better is what I understand why, but like much better
song teacher isn't, it's the John Brian performance pieces versus song thing.
I think, cause I have her teacher is like, undeniably, uh, like explosive
and full of energy and very unique, but like, why can't this be love and dreams?
They're more melodic songs.
And in some ways I, I, I don't know if I like them better, but I do like them.
Um, and then there's early Sammy Hagar stuff that I think is better.
He's certainly turned into a cartoon character of a pitch man for tequila.
And that is not doing anything interesting for many, many years.
I just find him more like power ballad-y snoozy.
And then what I just played is a garbage.
Well, yeah, I'm not a big mass tequila defender.
Suddenly this is another way, you know, you say tune a guy and
now I start, it just helps after hearing little tune a book.
I, I, that same, like not so bad.
Is it sudden?
I hear a bunch of like recent Sammy Hagar and I'm like,
Buffett was a fucking genius.
He was truly a gifted song, more better masterfully written than the last.
I think Sammy was Sammy, even though he had the, he had the tequila
fur, he had the whole like lifestyle brand.
He thinks first, uh, I feel like he almost was chasing Jimmy at a certain point
because of the Margaritaville restaurant, all the success Jimmy had.
So Jimmy was doing that garbage better than Sammy does.
And then yes, the meathead rock.
I could go, I I'm like, I never have.
I wanted some, uh, Casio steel drums more.
He wrote, but Sammy wrote that, uh, song Rick Springfield does.
I'm drawing a blank.
I've done everything for you.
You've done nothing for me.
Like, don't know that he's done.
That's a fun, I don't know, kind of pop rock song.
He has more like pop rocky things in the, in the past.
I feel like versus now, which is just that chicken foot and who'd be
my hoochie coochie man and stuff from chicken foot, speaking of chicken.
Yeah.
Speaking of chicken, chicken in the sea.
See, uh, okay.
Well here I stepped right into a, uh, another tangent.
I don't think I'm going to have to stop the tradition of playing Sammy Hager
because it's going to eat up 10 minutes at the top of.
I've done such a good job, not talking about it that much.
So yes, it's up to you.
It's up to you not to engage me.
I think if you took the, if you'd added up all the time that is in the, just
the three episodes, I think has been a substantial conversation every time.
I don't know where you're getting this good job.
I don't know.
I think I deserve a good job.
I deserve a good job.
Just say, Jason, tell me good job.
Uh, good job, Michael.
Um, I have, uh, no opinions on Van Halen or Sammy Hager.
Like, it's just a big blank for me.
I know, I know Sammy Hager primarily as the tequila guy, the cartoon
character, as you said, like the long hair, the cartoon, the kabo wabo
restaurant, since you're a blank slate on it, let's just, let's just solve it
right now.
David Lee Roth is better end of discussion.
So, uh, all right, moving on, but like when he did jump on the Jay Leno show
and the blue grass jump, he's got the big smile, he's lost like all of his
aura to that once a year.
That's why I love that performance range.
It is so, uh, blue grass jump from like 2000, he looks like the dorkiest man
you've ever seen.
He used to look like the cool, like a cool guy.
Just shaking around.
He looks so much cooler, right?
Like in the last show than he did at that point.
Oh, good.
Yeah.
Well, the overalls aren't going to do you a lot of good.
Uh, okay.
Let's, let's talk about this.
Okay.
So, um, the pirate ship, uh, regardless, outside of all of the, the tuna stuff,
which I guess I'm in for, and I'm probably delaying with the Halen talk.
Uh, uh, this was a, like a, a real staple and you might, you know, probably
I think in 55, when Disneyland opens, I bet one of the most, one of the
10 most impressive things in the entire park was this pirate ship.
Yes.
Credible.
Yeah, yeah.
It's, you know, it's not the size of, it's not the size of sailing ship Columbia.
It's not like, like a massive one, uh, uh, you know, and it's, and it's more
like cartoony that it's more fantasy land.
That's the vibe it's going to be.
However, huge, intricate, what could be more exciting to a kid than the
Disneyland has a pirate ship.
Uh, um, so, you know, it, it's, it's just like, it looked very pleasant and fun
and cool, uh, uh, you know, just, just aesthetically, um, you know, there's,
there's the deck up top and you can wander around there and sometimes
characters would be up there.
Uh, it's like a big network of docs that get you onto it and a bunch of, a bunch
of cannons and so they just like really expertly done, like this seems like real.
Magical or like the promise of Disneyland as presented by Walton, the
show that you get to go to a fairy tale kingdom and you can walk around a real
pirate ship, um, and it's almost weird.
They don't have something, I guess they have Donald's boat and various other
parks have things sort of like this, but it went away, uh, you know, I think in 82
and it was never really replaced by, by an equivalent and I'm sure if kids of
fifties, sixties, seventies must've loved this thing.
Yeah.
I think this not having, I mean, I understand there's more, they can fit
more rides in without a giant pirate ship, but this does feel like one of the
things I'm like, I wish that was there.
I wish there was a version of that here.
I guess if they told me you'd be losing these three fantasy land rides or
something, I get like, I guess so.
But like, but it used to all fit is the thing it moved because this was kind of
where Dumbo is now, like kind of right up next to storybook land, Casey Jr.
And I think when it opened, you could just kind of like see right into all that stuff.
There was no real landscaping per se.
Not a lot of trees just sort of right in there.
Yeah.
And everything it's cause it's all the same stuff in that area.
It's Dumbo and it's carousel and it's teacups, which we just talked about.
And it's all, that's all just like nudged around.
Right.
Why isn't there room now?
What happened?
That is a good, like, if you took away like storybook boats, could you fit the
pirate ship in there and is it better?
Like, I guess this is more of an ended episode conversation, but like, what is
it worth?
What is the pirate ship worth?
Well, the pirate ship and then the skull rock, which came later.
Skull rock too.
That looks pretty cool.
Yeah.
Some of that was not really come up for us before, probably just because we
didn't grow up with it.
Yeah.
But you know, when we did fake rock final four way back, I don't think that was in
the mix and that's early fake rocks.
Yeah.
And it's just, it's real strong.
It looks cool as hell.
I, now I, I, so I think when this opened, it was kind of just in an unthemed pond.
That might not have been so, it looked a little bit miniature golf course, but
then 1960, they add a bunch of landscaping around it.
Uh, the plant work is wonderful.
The rock work is one that just made it like a true lagoon and the biggest piece
of that being, uh, the giant skull rock with like water, the waterfall where
water was coming out from between its teeth.
Um, this is really neat.
This, this does feel like the rare thing where, Oh, it was cooler then.
Like we lost it.
This is what I thought when looking at this again.
And even though when this is another thing where I didn't even realize maybe
until like 10 or 15 years ago that this was here, because it just, yeah.
If you, cause it is one thing where you see like old fantasy land, you go, Oh, I
know why they redid the exteriors here.
These look date, these look dated or whatever.
And obviously now it looks really nice, but then you see this and you go, I
don't know, and I don't want to keep, I'm not trying to do this to hurt, hurt you
Jason, but would I give up Casey jr to get skull rock and this boat back?
And I kind of wish, but they were all there.
They, they, I understand what you're saying.
I'm just, no, why isn't it a problem?
Why is the problem if all the same things fit and there was a pirate ship?
Yeah, maybe it was, it was crowd flow.
It was, everything was moved around because this was a big like choke point.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yes.
I think I feel like we noticed that all of those that like teacups and
Dumbo and carousel were all like a foot apart.
Yeah, it's more than a choke point.
It's just not as bad as it will always be.
It is, but like, I mean, they kind of rebuilt this all in fantasy land at
Disneyland, Paris, because they had the luxury of space, you know, starting
over and redo, yes.
And I, I thought it was really cool there.
I was really excited to see that.
Uh, and, uh, yeah, it's great.
And they, and, and the boats there too.
Correct.
I mean, I was almost most excited about skull rock.
Um, and it's good that it's not Paris one is good, but then it is missing a
little bit of like the cartooniness.
So it's a little less, it's a little more cool and a little less goofy than
the original Disneyland one.
I just really, as I'm now skimming photos of it, I'm so charmed by it.
This was a good rock.
We really should have found a way to keep this rock.
Yeah, I agree.
I, I guess there's, I mean, maybe you could still put it over somewhere.
Matterhorn zone.
That's technically fantasy land still, maybe because there is some land over
there and I know this because of when we were D 23 was happening and I was trying
to figure out where avatar went.
It's like, there is a little chunk, even if you keep Autopia over there, I'm
like, could they put the boat over there?
Oh, so I'm like, well, because motorboat cruise kind of never
became anything, right?
It does seem like they're, well, I think there was the intention, maybe
to try to move it over there, but maybe that's a discussion for the end.
It's just like what happened.
Sure.
Um, but let's talk about what you could do on this pirate ship.
Um, now were there Peter Pan characters running around it that you could visit?
Yes, there were sometimes, but there were also original characters.
You could meet, yeah, maybe you'd see Captain Hook up there, but you
might also see Captain Guy.
Captain Guy was a peg leg pirate and he'd say hi to you.
He'd say, shiver me timbers, whatever.
And like, oh my God, a real peg leg pirate.
How do they do that?
Where do they put the guy's leg?
Does he hide it?
Does he just like put it up in it?
No.
The answer is they hired a Korean war veteran who actually lost his leg and
they made him a peg leg pirate because I found a picture on Reddit.
I think that's Captain Guy.
I think we're looking at Captain Guy.
I think, and he appears to be in a beverage dispenser.
So he's probably saying like, yeah, do you want bib juice or do you want milk?
I love this.
I like, I flashed to him in the hospital, like what happened?
Is it going to be okay?
No, I'm afraid we had to remove the leg.
Oh God, I, what will I do?
I, uh, I'll never be able to find a job.
No, I, I'd have to agree with that unless somewhere is hiring pirates.
I don't know if Johnny, you have a visitor.
His name is Herber Ryman.
He said he has a job for you.
Putting a team together.
Um, so I love that.
And I love the guy.
Yeah.
So is it like, who's it going to be the pirate?
I don't know.
This guy, this guy's going to go, what are we going?
I'm not a captain guy.
I, I assume captain guy was not like the character was not, the mantle is not taken
up by someone later once he retired.
I don't believe so.
Yeah.
No.
But it's tech, it's another one of those where it's like, it's probably
technically Disney IP.
Uh huh.
Technically Disney owns captain guy.
Captain guy was deep in the background.
Yeah.
Once upon a studio.
Right.
Really close.
Right, right, right.
He's running around.
He's hopping around there.
Yeah.
Uh, um, you would also meet another character, the character Paco.
Paco was a real parrot who you could visit and take pictures with.
And the documentation I saw of Paco indicated that he likes to bite things.
Really liked to bite things.
And yes, would often bite visitors.
They in very like, uh, this, this early Disneyland chaos, where you would.
Ride a mule that actually would just lay down and take a shit with you on it.
And then you can meet a parrot who is bite happy.
You might start going for your fingers.
Now there's just the Roman cats and they're either too scared or too friendly
to just give you a big bite.
Yeah.
Oh, and then the castle was full of what?
Feral cats and fleas.
Oh yeah.
There's that room.
That's all fleas is what we figured out.
There was a flea room in the sleeping beauty castle.
To all the fleas that come to this happy place.
Welcome.
Yeah.
So there was, yeah, it was an interesting animal situation in the early days.
And we haven't even, these are all kind of new discoveries to us.
We don't know if there were, uh, locusts.
We don't know if there were, yeah, there was just like, uh,
before, before they built, they built the Tiki room to kick out a colony of
ringworms, just a dense network of ringworm, 10 million of them.
And that was, uh, they attracted them there.
That was an attraction.
The land of the ringworms was an opening day.
We'll get to that one.
You're stuck dealing with the ringworms, Walt.
That's why that orange grove never sold.
The big worm colony.
You're learning the curse of the ringworm.
Real estate agent didn't tell you about that, huh?
He just, he would just say more carefully.
He had a ringworm, just pour some scotch on it and you're fine.
It wasn't a big deal back then.
The little man of Disneyland had a tiny, uh, flute and led the
ringworms out of, oh yeah, yeah.
He was friends with all the fleas.
I bet the little man.
Yeah.
I think so.
He named them all.
Yeah.
He was married to one.
Tough to find it.
That the toughest thing is finding a wedding veil, uh, for a flea.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Well, if you could call it that, I swear they did more fighting than loving.
Wasn't a happy marriage.
I don't know what you want.
Some marriages are.
Some people are in flea marriages.
The little man is still, are they still married?
Cause he's still around.
His house is still there.
They've been separated for decades.
Oh, I didn't know.
So they didn't want to go through the whole thing.
He's Catholic.
I mean, I guess a flea, I don't know what a flea's lifespan is, but
a little, the little man of Disneyland, I assume is immortal.
Seems that way.
Seems that way at least.
Yeah.
No, he'll outlive the park.
He'll outlive us all.
Yeah.
When there's nothing there and he'll still wandering through a
field of little houses.
Yeah.
Uh, uh.
It's like that Twilight Zone episode where it's just a destroyed city and
like a man and a woman from separate sides meet and finally lay down their arms.
Like Disneyland will be destroyed.
Everyone will be dead except this flea and the little man of Disneyland.
And Ducky.
Oh, and Ducky.
The Magic Key Duck.
That's another immortal.
Is Ducky also eternal?
That's if you watch the Instagram, the 92nd Instagram video, it
seems like he's immortal.
He's been there as soon as long as the park is open.
How, how, if I were to try to do that, how would I, does it still exist?
It took me, did you post the link?
Yeah, I think we did.
I, I took a section of it and I posted it on Instagram or on a, yeah, whatever
our social media is, uh, it took me a couple of seconds to figure out again,
how to find it when we were going back to the episode because it's confusing
and he's not, he is, they're not leaning into Ducky.
No, it doesn't seem like he has not shown up.
I think since the video posted.
So he is a, maybe a one-off Magic Key Duck, uh, that if that thing had gone
viral, if I roll a gun or, or if, if your slash our episode had gone viral
paywall though.
So yeah, it's not gonna be tougher to go for.
Yeah.
Ducky is being, um, Ducky's going to Abu Dhabi, but not for the new park.
He's just being shipped in the box that like normal would go.
Yeah, it's a punishment.
Who, who did it?
Who is it?
Did Garfield do it?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, or the little man did it.
Well, yeah.
Who's doing our shipping for Abu Dhabi?
Uh, who's this employee?
Garfield.
Goes his last name cat every Monday off.
It's a stray.
Why did we agree to that?
Oh, it works out in Sunday.
It's weekends or Monday and Tuesday in your mind.
12 lasagna meals a day, except for Monday where 15 are shipped to his home.
I did, this is, this is a dense contract.
We never should have hired this guy.
Jason's jealous of that contract.
If I, could I, uh, on a regular job interview, uh, now just, just asking,
could I, could I arrange Garfield hours?
Cause I've got the Garfield deal, please.
People are, you know, they're mad about Ryan Kugler's sinners deal now, but
Jason wants the Garfield deal.
People are going to be very, the business is not going to be happy
when he gets that Garfield deal.
Not everyone wants the Kugler deal.
Right.
Some people want the Garfield deal.
Um, so yeah, you, you, you climb on a pirate ship, you meet a Korean war
veteran, you get bit by a parrot.
So that, that's all you're having fun up top, but what happens in the bottom
of the ship, because that's a whole big chunk of real estate.
What, what is the, what magical activity awaits for you in the, in the center
of this cartoon pirate ship?
Well, a tuna oriented restaurant, a heavily branded chicken of the sea,
uh, uh, tuna restaurant, maybe the world's only all tuna restaurant.
I don't, I can't say that today.
There must be, there is a thousand niches out there and it could be, uh,
that may exist, but at the time places, uh, kind of count, I don't
guess now I, now here's, I will say right now, I don't think that counts,
but probably because tuna guys, this is what, would you be shocked to know
that I myself am not a tuna guy now in poke form in sushi form?
Absolutely.
But I will say right now I've never taken to or understood the genre of canned
tuna with heavy mayo butter, every whatever is happening in this restaurant.
I've, I've always, I've been aware of this for a long time and it has always
been a nightmare to me that I would, if I, if I woke up in the middle of the
night and I'd been transported to, I'm like, you have been taken, a captain
guy has taken you hostage and you now live in the chicken of the sea pirate
ship and all you have to choose from are the pirate or sorry, the tuna oriented
meals on board this vessel.
Well, there isn't fruit tart with whipped cream.
I would take that every day.
I think that would be my every meal.
Yeah, there is my savior.
Scott, what about like a tuna steak?
Like a, like a big cut of tuna.
Uh, yes, depending on the preparation.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh, uh, no, I like, you know, like, uh, uh, you know, and like the, like the
raw variety or more, like, you know.
Do you do spicy as well?
Do you regular or spicy or just regular?
I, I think I try to avoid that mayo because that's that now you're getting
into the kind of unhealthy territory.
Well, some, well, no, sometimes it, sometimes it's just the tuna itself
as I feel like spicy and it's not with like a little sauce.
Really?
But sometimes there's.
Oh, okay.
Maybe I'm maybe I'm wrong.
I'd be interested in that.
Wait, wait, how did it, but just natural spiciness.
Well, no, it's just a little sriracha mix.
Yeah.
It's not, I don't think it necessarily means it's the like thicker mayo sauce.
It could be like, and I like, I like, I'll do the spicy sauce for the, I just try
to not, uh, you know, uh, if I got options, um, but, uh, you know, all right.
Let me, I w I'm just saying, let me be the party to, first of all, saying
that like, cause I think sushi tuna is a completely different genre of food
than what we're talking about.
For sure.
Yeah.
Um, I like that too.
I have never understood it.
I guess I see the floor now to you, tuna boys.
Uh, if they're okay, what, can you understand why I've never understood
where I've, why I've never gotten that genre?
Sure.
Yeah.
Argument one, it stinks.
I've never, I've always hated this.
I don't know if there's a genetic factor with like thinking, I mean, like I, I
know, I recognize that tuna smells weird, but it doesn't, doesn't turn me off
to eating it for whatever reason.
Why is that said so lascivious Lee?
Doesn't, doesn't turn me off.
Cause I'm thinking about, I'm hungry right now and I keep thinking in my head,
get an order from, you know, get Jason's convenient firehouse.
I don't, I will, the way he said it, the way he made it seem though, there's a
chance that that, that ain't getting here before we're done recording.
No, probably not.
So, so I, you know, maybe I was just, I'm thinking in my head cause like, I think
the best sandwich, if you can get a good tuna melt, that's like my favorite
sandwich, I think on the, and I know, I know many, many people love that.
It's just never been, so I think I was imagining it and like salivating.
And that's why my voice got a bit lascivious, but it was food.
Well, you chose the first sexual lascivious.
It doesn't turn me off.
I love a tuna melt, but I love homemade, like canned tuna and mayo.
I have cans of tuna in my house.
Yeah, I do too.
I do too.
Yeah, I can the tune in my house.
Big jar of mayo.
Um, I, uh, took it for school lunch, uh, a lot, usually when I had like, uh, the
insulated bag, like not really when I just had a brown paper bag, um, but yeah.
Well, here's my question though.
I know that it's like a, in that case, school lunches and can't, and it's like
a food that's around and like, uh, cheap and fit, but you guys, you're still, you
consider yourselves excited about it today.
I love the idea of tuna melt is so exciting to me right now.
I haven't had one in a while.
Cause I don't eat a lot of it.
Cause it's, you know, the mercury, of course.
So I don't have a lot of fish.
This seems like the kind of thing you should be like, I was on the mercury
Reddit and I freaked me out.
I couldn't sleep because of the mercury Reddit.
Like, you probably have like, I mean, you probably can have it a couple
times a week, but I don't know, like once a week or whatever is fine.
It's like with tuna, because tuna is higher in mercury.
Salmon isn't as high in mercury.
It's funny.
I only like canned tuna.
I like it in sushi a little.
I don't like tuna steaks.
I found, find them pretty, I don't know that I've even really had a
tuna steak, so I'm not sure what day to day that I even would like.
Under entrees, you know, I'll offer a chicken tuna salmon.
I will put, I will make a little tuna salad and I will sometimes put it
on like macaroni and cheese.
I will like kind of, I will use that almost as like the protein
and like a pasta dish.
Oh, I'll just eat it with crackers.
Well, I got a couple preparations.
That's, I mean, they sell it as like pre-made.
This, this, by the way, this isn't even one of those things where I'm going,
you guys are crazy.
I like, I've always been, I feel like I've always been in the minority.
I even grew up in a house.
Like my parents still eat, but I've never, I've just always been like, so
grossed out by it, that mac and cheese, that, that's the first thing that's
been said that made me feel nauseous.
Lindsay doesn't like it when I do that.
Oh, okay.
All right.
I got, all right.
She's not as big of a fish fan.
Now I partly, a lot of people just grab the chunk light tuna.
Now that's the really cheapy, but if you buy the solid albacore, which I think
chicken of the sea, that's where the name came from solid albacore is kind of a
more mild chicken or more mild tuna.
And that's where it's like, Oh, it tastes like chicken.
That's where the name comes from.
Let's talk about the name.
Let's talk about a chicken of the sea, that branding, because I think it
probably makes all of us flash to newlyweds Nick and Jessica, which then
quickly makes us flash to their fantastic variety show work and how much
great material came after newlyweds.
Uh, but, uh, the, the most infamous moment from that show where she's
confused by what she's eating.
She thinks she's eating chicken and points to the can as proof.
And he says, no, that's just the name of it.
It's tuna.
And she was, you know, derided for this and made to made out to be an idiot for
this as time goes on, I'm like, Jessica, I think is right, not right, because
she's not right about what she's eating, but this name is stupid.
What is the point?
Why it is confusing.
I don't blame Jessica for being confused by, yeah.
I mean, she, I guess she should know what she's doing and I suppose that's the
thing where you would be like, but the, but it being explained to you, like
you're stupid, like, no, duh, it's chicken of the sea.
Like if you were like, imagine getting that kind of explained to you.
Why did they name it that?
That's weird.
Yeah.
I it's a, I think it's a, I think it's a, but I don't find it clever.
I think it's stupid.
Well, a lot of these companies to sell canned chicken, like chopped up
canned chicken similarly.
So you can just drain it, dump it in a bowl with mayo and make chicken salad.
But if somewhere else did fish of the range, I like fish of the range.
Are you an idiot?
It's not fish.
It's fish of the range.
I feel like it's a name that's been grandfathered.
Like it would never be a new name for a product.
Yeah.
Too confusing.
Yes.
But since it's old, it has old timey penis for sure.
Right.
Yeah.
We, I grew up and I, we always did like chicken salad, just, or a
tuna salad, just with mayo and a lot of pepper.
I know some people like celery.
I don't really like celery.
Ooh, I love celery.
Really?
Yeah.
I know it's pretty common, but that's kind of why I like raw celery.
I'll just eat like celery.
You get a bag of celery, you go to car chomp chomp.
God, really?
Yeah.
I'll throw a really at you for that.
I don't even need a ranch.
I will take a little ranch if I want, but I can, I can just.
It's like the blandest.
Sure.
Yeah.
It's like negative calories.
They say I can eat.
I can do that.
I can do like plain oatmeal.
Oh, I love plain oatmeal.
Yeah.
I don't need any, I happy to have brown sugar or something in there, but I don't
need, I can do a plain oatmeal.
No problem.
I believe that you, you're all into plain oatmeal.
We're plain oatmeal guys.
But then we're also experimenters.
There's a lot of range, you know?
Scoop of peanut butter, dump scoop of jelly, essentially a peanut butter
jelly and taste sauce in your oatmeal.
Oh, what the fuck?
Taco bell, Caliente sauce.
That's not something you've done or would do.
I haven't tried it.
I would try for the show, but.
Okay.
You're all right.
You're not too far from like congee, like porridge, like Chinese porridge.
Oh, I would like to have porridge.
You of course had porridge.
So that is often prepared as a savory or grits.
Like, yeah, was it, was it a tough transition to move
in with your fiance, the comfort of the bears?
The three bears.
I, you know, cause your bed there was just right.
Porridge with them.
I might, yeah, I, yeah, they buy one on Amazon.
They're just going to like, watch this.
They slice it open.
It just puffs up.
Yeah.
It's vacuum sealed.
It's crazy.
Scott, were you, a big tuna Mac house at all?
Tuna Mac?
Tuna Mac, tuna macaroni.
No.
My family, oh, we would make hot tuna Mac and cold tuna Mac.
Now my mom squares cold tuna Mac, which is just tuna salad, basically
tossed with cold macaroni.
She squares that's a picnic side.
I think that's a full meal.
Hot tuna Mac.
She squares that to picnic side.
No, she squares that is a picnic side.
The distinction of picnic side specifically, not just a side dish for a meal.
That's what I love.
That's why I'm laughing.
I am declaring that meal.
I have the court of Jason is ruled.
Bang, bang.
That is meal.
We would have cold tuna Mac if we were doing hot dogs and burgers.
Did you make the cold tuna Mac?
She would make the cold.
Okay.
Cause you couldn't buy, I was just wondering like, cause you know, we would
buy a macaroni salad from the deli all the time and we love them, but you
would put tuna in it.
Just, yeah, just you make a box of, uh, this is like a pantry food.
This is like, you make a box.
I did that.
That's kind of what I was saying earlier.
Macaroni, you run it under cold water and drain it.
Then you dump in tuna and mayo and you mix it all around something going on
with you, but you're both like lit up.
Like I haven't seen you.
Yeah, we're tuning our hard core tuna gun.
Now hot tuna Mac was a big in the winter.
Wait, hold on hot tuna was the side or not cold.
No, I had to Mac has a meal because it's hot elbow noodles.
Uh, you dump the tuna into a can of cream of mushroom soup and cook it a little
and then dump it in the macaroni and mix it.
And here's where I'm, here's what's starting to flash into my head is that
you two are liars.
And I'll tell you why I proposed that we do this episode and I said, we'll
keep that like an hour, right?
You both said yes.
You knew perfectly well that you had two hours worth of tuna material.
There's 15 minutes on tuna Mac alone.
Given both the hot and the cold.
Yeah.
You both, you both knew you did.
You conspired about good cop, bad cop, and you knew that this was going to be
two hours because you're tuning.
Well, there's also at the school cafeteria in high school, everyone be
like, Oh, it's tuna day.
And I was like, yes, it's tuna day because they would make, it was a
pita pocket with tuna with a lot of relish.
And I'm like, tuna with a lot of red, this really good tuna, the relish.
That's interesting.
I've never had that before.
Sometimes I still dump a spoonful of relish and it's wonderful.
I didn't realize I was going to be so excited until he kind of juiced me up on
the way over here with his excitement.
And I went, Oh yeah, you're right.
And then, then I think sometimes it's sometimes he's riding in your car as if
he's headed to his execution, as if you're going to shoot him in the back of
the head, you're taking them to the farm.
A glum Jason staring out the window today.
He was banging on all the surfaces.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bye bye here.
Let's blast some, uh, let's blast some Hagar on the way over.
Yeah.
He's like, Hey, turn it up.
What is this music?
Something I got a spring in my step today.
I'm thinking about max hot tuna, max salad kind of day.
Sammy.
Hey, he is wide.
What?
Sammy.
Okay.
Tom Hanks from Elvis.
He, he's what?
Oh, okay.
I guess, I guess I know what you're saying.
Okay.
Wait, you might Mike explain it.
If you think you understood it, explain it.
Is he, are you talking about when, when Colonel Tom Parker realized that Elvis is
white, he, he's wide.
Yeah.
He says that about Elvis.
That's why I didn't understand it because you were doing a voice.
So it turned white into what?
He's a lot.
There's a lot going on.
I know.
I took me a second to figure out where we were going with it.
Is that you could have changed it maybe to like figure, cause sometimes I'll
call it like, it'll be white albacore tuna.
So, so maybe Colonel Tom could discover, Oh, that's that albacore is a lot.
He's solid one albacore, not chocolate.
Yeah, there we go.
That's a good punch up, right?
Somebody is hearing tuna on the radio.
What's worse?
Look, I don't, that's a whole nother issue.
I just wanted to understand what Taylor more to the, to see me.
He's, he's the red rock.
Yeah.
Oh, he's a red.
That would be good.
Well, he's red.
I don't think I would have to hang out.
No one would have gotten that either.
He's red.
He's a red.
You hear that voice, you know that that is, but then isn't, wait, you're
doing like a Southern voice, but that, but Colonel Tom Parker was that weird.
Like he was like Dutch or something.
Look, if you're going to get in the accuracy issue also, that's too, we
don't have time for that.
Yeah.
I think he's doing kind of a crazy.
There is Southern in it.
That voice is kind of a, unplaceable.
Um, anyway.
All right.
What other genres do we need to do?
The tuna boys need to, I don't know.
I think I hit all my tuna.
I got, yeah, I just, I really, I haven't had to know.
I really actually haven't had it in a couple of months.
Now that I think about it.
But you have, you have in your house, but you haven't, you
haven't cracked into those cans.
You're saving them for nice occasions.
Yeah.
In the same way that I still have Scotty Pippen's bourbon digits sitting
on my counter on open, it's very valuable.
Yes.
I think that's right.
I don't know that he's actually still, I don't know that they're
producing his, his bourbon anymore.
He's moved.
He's moved on to his, to his tuna brand, his can tuna brand.
God, I wish he's certainly very involved in crypto and it's the most,
some of the most fascinating, the accounts on the internet and
he is whoever's posting for him.
Maybe it's him is posting motivational speaking and crypto stuff like so much,
so often posting and it's really fascinating.
And I used to do those fun ads where he like dunked a sandwich.
Now he's doing, now he's just talking about crypto.
It's all crypto.
He had a popcorn that he had endorsed a year or two, two that I was following.
And I don't know if that's still in play, but it's just, it's that again,
that's too long of a tangent.
He posts weird AI pictures of himself.
It's really, it's all Anthony, other than UFOs, it's all Anthony Geo.
And I text about is Scotty Pippen's Twitter.
Do you think it is a Cal God hat?
UFOs, 60% UFOs, 40% Scotty Pippen's AI art.
Scotty Pippen's AI art and the guy who just be like rise it, like the rise and
grind sort of type of posting and then like air drops for crypto tokens.
Now Mike and Jason's texts after this, 90% tuna.
I'm literally trying to figure out where I'm going to get a tuna melt tonight.
Cause I need to eat one for dinner.
Like, I'm like, where, what I, what I'd recommend to you is to, uh, postmates
it from the most inconvenient place possible.
Does you just, does anyone else, I guess, like a coral house.
Yes.
I should go to a diner.
Right.
I should go to some sort of a diner type place.
I should go to a diner on the way home and get a tuna melt.
Okay.
All right.
And then you get, and then you'll have a lot to say you get to now is that now
what kind of chunks we talking, what do we think was the base of it?
And do we think that base would have made a good hot Mac or would have been
more of a cold Mac, more of a picnic side is what it would have been.
Cook outside.
Well, I just like that.
But I would take that for a school lunch for sure.
My mom made a big batch cold tuna Mac or hot tuna Mac, which is also good cold.
Uh, I would take the same thing.
It's just the heat is different.
You just said hot tuna Mac is also good cold.
Wouldn't it be just the cold?
No, it's the cream of mushroom.
Like, oh, it's a little different.
Excuse me.
You did say that.
I'm sorry.
Well, now that everyone's salivating, now that everyone's nice and not turned off,
we can read what they have, what you could buy at this.
Yeah.
Well, I guess first question is like, so this would have been paradise for you.
Tuna guy.
Oh, I would have gotten off this shit.
I would have killed for a simple triangle cut, like chicken salad sandwich in
Disneyland killed for it.
I would have killed for like, just a, I like just a very plain
sandwich sometimes like.
So you're saying like now these days you would kill or you wouldn't kill today.
Just like,
this guy just wants to kill.
He's looking for any, he's got, yeah, he's got murder on his mind.
The only thing that calms me is canned tuna fish.
I feel like this explains psychologically some of the dynamics that you guys are
not only tuna guys, you are hardcore tuna guy.
I had no idea when I stepped into the room and the fact that things do it, that
I do end up being a divisive corner of this triangle is the explanation always
there in the tuna affection.
Is that it?
I don't know that we've ever, this is where, this is where the personalities
diverge when we were eight years old.
I remember when we were at like a pizza restaurant or two with like large menus
and it was like personal pan, you got your own and blanks like, Oh, this one
is tuna, I'm going to get bossa nova and sunset had had a tuna pizza many years
ago that I had and I may have been high while I ate it and this is like 15 years.
I think the guy was high.
You thought it up.
We went into, we, my friend was in town.
We went to a guy's house who's now kind of famous is on a TV and we got weed from
him because my friend wanted it and then we got high.
I didn't like it.
It made me feel weird.
We went over to bossa nova on sunset Boulevard and we had, I had a tuna
pizza, which was delicious.
I ate maybe all of it in one sitting.
I see.
I have a memory one time when I was studying abroad in Germany for a party,
they brought over, Hey pizza.
Whoa.
Pizza's here.
It was tuna pizza.
I, and most of the people around me recoiled.
I already found this to be the grossest thing they've ever seen.
Are you anti-anchovy?
Not necessarily, but I just think it's.
Extremely rare that I've ever had question.
What's everyone's opinion on canned fish, sardines, anchovies, oysters.
I don't recall ever having sardines.
I have no, no, I can say that firmly.
I've never had sardines are weird because it's just, it looks like a little fish.
So it's a little weird to eat it right out of the can, but they are good.
And I haven't had them in years, but.
Oh, I loved it.
I think I read a profile of Simon rich once and he was like, Oh, a lot of
times for lunch, I'll eat like sardines on rye with brown mustard.
And I had all that in the house.
I was like, yeah, it is good.
And you liked it.
It's good to see that you were eating the corpse.
Sure.
I eat their spine.
The things you've forgotten, but then that you remember that Simon
rich likes to eat canned sardines.
It's good.
Omega threes.
It usually comes in olive oil.
Yeah.
That's why his writing is so sharp.
Threes go to the brain.
It is good for your brain.
Okay.
Let's let's read what they would have had at your parent.
Yes.
Guy tuna guys.
Come on.
Take a deep breath.
Tuna guys.
You're shaking.
You're jostling the microphones.
Yeah.
Okay.
So when you walked in here, you would have had your choice of many delicious
sounding items, tuna, clipper salad.
Do we know what that is?
What is clipper about?
Uh, I, uh, Jim Hill caught this too.
A tuna boat salad and then a tuna clipper salad.
A clipper is a slightly bigger boat.
Clippers like a sailboat.
Oh, right.
Right.
I see.
Okay.
So this is one of the things.
Yeah.
You would get a big boat of tuna.
Right.
Uh, is what that was there.
Like this was in the pre Instagram days.
Yeah.
Why even bother to make food look interesting when it wasn't, you couldn't
Instagram about it when you couldn't go viral, like those crazy blacktap shakes.
Yeah, I know.
They should replace blacktap with a place that sells a tuna salad in a boat.
Well, well, no, same deal.
It's still like wild milkshakes, but get that cake out of here.
Give me a big loaf of tuna right on top of that crazy, crazy shake with a big
thing of tuna does that genuine because I, as I just said it, I sort of was gagging
while the words were coming out of my mouth.
I do believe that both of you would eat tuna milkshakes.
Oh, no, don't be gross.
But if you put a scoop of cottage cheese next to some tuna, I wouldn't be mad at
you.
The devil is grinning at his face when he said that to me.
He was being like funless.
I might say thank you, I'm not mad at all.
Yeah.
President Nixon wasn't, I don't think he was in the wrong to eat a scoop of cottage
cheese and pineapple every day.
I bought cottage cheese for the first time in years of the last week, actually.
Let's just establish he knows Simon Rich's go-to meal and President Nixon's go-to
meal.
Nixon would have a scoop of cottage cheese.
I believe that was his breakfast, cottage cheese and pineapple.
That one's kind of a no-name.
I don't like cottage cheese either.
Yeah, I haven't had it for many years, but I bought it because my mom used to make
us cottage cheese and yogurt and you would mix the two together.
Wait, why?
Yeah, they're pretty close.
What do you mean?
Well, that's a lot of dairy.
Oh, it's certainly a lot of dairy.
Yeah.
But that for whatever reason, that was the way she would, I would get that
delivered, that it would be with yogurt in it.
So if the milkshake was cottage cheese, it's in a milkshake glass, but it's a
bunch of cottage cheese.
I would try a big tuna block on top.
That doesn't seem so appealing to me.
Now, if you were to take hot tuna mac or hot tuna salad and put it in a sort of
milkshake container with some sort of fun dressing on the top and you would walk
around sipping the hot tuna salad or mac or you would walk around a theme park
with a hot tuna mac or in like in one of the fun cones, like in the, in Isla
Burke or in Cozy Cone in Cars Land, you get a little tuna salad in one of those.
That would be not bad.
I would have to break off from the group.
If you ever did, if this was ever, if there was a cone of tuna around at a theme
park, I would have to go be somewhere else.
Well, Mike and I would never both get that because we'd be too busy each
holding a cone of tuna and then holding hands.
We wouldn't be able to eat it.
Oh, we would be intertwining our arms.
We'd be eating each other's wedding bouquets like this.
It would be like the thing where your arms, with champagne flutes.
Sharing the champagne.
We'd share the different Cozy Cone meats at Cars Land or Cozy Cone,
whatever it's called.
I forget.
Oh man.
And then, okay, now you have this, this phrase, which genuinely creeps me out.
Tuna dietetic salad.
I'm like, what is dietetic?
Yeah.
I guess dietetic, I mean, that's a word that is still around.
It's kind of like the science of diet.
Right.
It's just not a word that we really use anymore.
It's very clinical.
But that feels like, yeah, that feels like a word that was invented in the fifties is
it like, okay, the people who think that diets are a good idea, they want a name.
Let's give them a name and let's make it, let's make it sure that it's a name
that shows that they're nuts.
Well, that's why that's people away from them.
Like the story is about the invention of the Cobb salad.
It was like, oh, it's a bunch of stuff, but it's all chopped very finely because
I don't know, an actress or the owner's wife, there's different stories.
Had digestion issues and they're like, here, this will go down good.
But it was just ham and tomatoes, egg, it like just chopped up a bunch.
Okay.
Oh, so the chopping was, it was, so your stomach didn't have to work as hard to
digest it.
Um, I, but, but so dietetic tuna just means like a little bit less of all the stuff.
Right.
Less mayo, less, uh,
salads back in the day were mostly buttermilk based dressings like mayonnaise.
Well, this, yeah, that's what I assume that 1955 tuna dietetic salad is just
what was probably like just halfway to how we eat tuna today.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
Like it was probably like, oh, we now would consider a normal way to prepare it.
Tuna dietetic salad kind of got, and whatever the hell the boat was, I don't
even want to know what that boat was like.
I don't know why I don't want to know what it smells like.
This is, it's all been on my mind because as somebody who does not like the smell
of tuna and then I think about like the craziness of 1955 Disneyland where, and
I've said some of this on the show before, but that we're like, everything's
melting down.
There's like, maybe the water machines aren't working or the bathrooms aren't
working and women are melting into the concrete and then all the food that's
available is like candied veal.
Yeah.
Everything's like candied veal, coffee, and cigars.
That is the smell of hot July Disneyland upon opening.
I need a refuse from this.
Honey glazed veal.
That's the children's menu.
Like Junior needs to eat something.
Oh, finally some honey glazed veal.
I need to clear my palate.
Hand me a cigarette.
Ooh.
Um, but so yeah, like I, I need like, I just need some refuge from this.
How about like, is there anywhere I can find some shade?
Ah, here we go.
This is a pirate ship.
Oh, the pirate ship is full of tuna.
It is loaded up with tuna.
Yeah.
It's been with no air conditioning and it's been heating up.
This is a tuna furnace disguised as a pirate ship.
I always found the notion of this so gross.
The smell of air.
You're in coffee with a boat of tuna.
Tuna.
That is, that truly makes me nauseous.
And you guys handle coffee in a tuna boat.
Eating or smelling how everybody doing it.
Eating it.
Yes.
Back and forthing it.
Please.
Of course.
Uh, I am interested because like just the way, you know, air circulation was in
buildings back then, what the smell was.
It might've been awful.
Um, but I think it attracted the cats.
Well, they would just, you know, when they, the, cause shrimp cocktail was also on
the menu and they sold canned shrimp.
Um, uh, you're making a shrimp cocktail.
They're making the cocktail sauce fresh either to dab a little of that, or you
get some of the worser out as you dab and might burn a little, but it'll get the
smells away.
Why are you, why are we dabbing?
I think you were, you were gesturing towards your nostril.
Like, it looked like you were like doing a cocaine gesture.
Yeah.
That's what it was.
No, I mean, like you're spreading it under your nose cause it's like, well, that
might sting a little, but it smells better than that.
So the employees, the employees, you're saying, yeah, if you had to work there and
you didn't like the smell, just every morning put horseradish under your nostrils.
That's what like a cop has to do when he goes to like a murder scene or something
to like prevent, but it's the same thing.
If you worked in the tuna restaurant at Disneyland in 1955, just dip your nose
in the horseradish.
Right.
Scoop out that part, make sure the customer.
You can have a little cocktail sauce on your tongue.
Maybe that'll get a little stuffy.
Have you ever done that?
No, no.
All right.
I didn't think so, but I wondered.
Yeah.
You were, you were saying it as if from experience.
Just, this is what you do.
You know, I'm just saying I saw on the menu shrimp cocktail and I'm like, well,
that's cocktail sauce can be very potent.
Yeah.
Depending on how you make it or the manufacturer.
And when it was unregulated, it would make you blind.
Are we shrimp fans?
Are we shrimp cocktail fans?
Yeah, I'm totally fine with shrimp.
Shrimp.
Good.
Okay.
It doesn't stink to me.
Oh, I got very ill as a child, young child when I ate shrimp.
So I don't, that my family was just like, yeah, he's probably allergic to shrimp.
So I just have not eaten shrimp.
Is that what, is that a shellfish?
But I eat plenty of shellfish, so I've just never tried shrimp.
So you're in a situation like I am with the corn dog.
I haven't had corn dogs since I was four years old because I got sick after eating
one, even though technically what I ate at FanFest was probably a corn dog.
I was like, no, that wasn't a corn dog.
You don't think so?
No, I don't think so.
Yeah, that was more of the Korean style.
Oh yeah, I guess you're right.
Brother, I got corn dogs in the freezer right now.
You come on in, you come on into the homestead.
I'll microwave you corn dogs at home.
Without children.
That is, corn dogs at home is a little wild, but I don't want to judge.
I think if I'm going back to corn dog, I'm going.
My mom likes to send us groceries sometimes.
So sometimes you never know what you're getting.
And thanks mom.
Uncrustables.
Yay.
Thanks mom.
Scott, we always have Uncrustables in the house.
She loves Uncrustables and she got me into them too.
Uncrustables.
That is very funny.
She had a bad headache or a toothache the other day.
And I was like, Oh, maybe I'll just have some peanut butter toast.
And she's like, Oh, I'll go grab.
I was like, you know what?
Just toss me an Uncrustable.
Don't, don't go through it.
Don't make it.
It's easier, you know, just toss me an Uncrustable.
Just toss me an Uncrustable.
Um, I will, I will eat a corn dog at Disneyland.
I haven't decided when, but I will do it.
And we will talk about it.
No one's making me do it.
That's good.
I will.
Jason wants to make me.
Yeah, I do want to make you.
Yeah.
And you know what?
Opt for the ketchup over mustard.
Cause the sweetness matches the sweetness of the cornbread.
It's delicious.
This is, I've never seen you two more excited and I've never seen you more
sexual than this, than this food discussion.
We're both using tones.
Well, I've never seen you.
I've just heard about it.
Yeah.
We've heard all heard the tales.
Um, we haven't even gotten to the best entree.
Let's get to the best entree.
Well, you, you, you take the reins.
Well, I'll say this cause I know more about it.
Cause I watched someone make it, uh, it, the tuna burger.
He's in the, one of the Disneyland like Walt's recipes guidebook.
And I watched, uh, Jim Hilton link to a YouTube account, making it
called the unofficial Disney guide.
I was kind of surprised by what it ended up being, which is they just made
tuna salad and then they made like who made special sauce, which I used to do
when I was a kid, which you just mix mayo and ketchup, and then they spread
that on a seeded roll.
That's what they called salsa in 1955.
Yeah.
Uh, you spread that on a seasoned roll.
Uh, you dump in the tuna salad and like three pickles.
Then you put the top bun on and then you bake it.
And they're like, yeah, it's, I mean, it's pretty good.
It's just kind of like you warmed a tuna sandwich.
This sounds and looks so bad to me.
I have no desire.
I thought he was going to make tuna salad, sculpt it into patties and
then put it in a pan and fry it.
I like, um, but no, I think it was just like, Oh, it just had the clipper.
You know, the, the pirate ship kitchen was probably just like a glorified
microwave and a bunch of fridges and freezers.
I think so.
Yeah.
Uh, um, well, the, that just seems like kind of, it's just going to get squishy
fast.
That doesn't seem good to me at all.
Yeah.
Uh, um, but the one, and this is what's always haunted me about when you just,
you know, I'll introduce it the way that I, you know, cause I think you guys
probably also, as I do end up on this site, yester land, which is great with
tracking, you know, there's a lot of great old photos of defunct attractions
and kind of take you through the history of them.
Always been a very well done website for many years.
Um, but they, they, but they kind of like pitch you the places as if, you
know, from a different narrative voice than theirs.
And I, I copy and pasted this.
This is the way yesterland gets the end of this place.
Are you hungry for a tuna sandwich, a tuna burger or a hot tuna pie?
No, I am not.
I'm not hungry for a hot tuna pie.
It sounds awful to me, but tuna guys weigh in.
I don't know what now.
I don't know what one is, but I'm recoiling from the phrase.
Well, I think because like a chicken pot pie, I bet it's similar to that.
So if it's literally just like breading and tuna, that's fine.
I'm not saying I'm like so excited about that version of tuna, but
further on the menu is it just says tuna pie pastry shell.
Yeah.
Like, okay, I guess so.
I know that meat goes with pastry.
Yeah.
So I'm, I'm assuming maybe it was just tuna salad in a little weirder
because we've, we've, you know, there are places, you know, it's almost
in the empanada family or something.
Yeah, it is plenty of places.
We're red meat or chicken go with more of pastry shell kind of, but like
this has not taken culturally here in 2025, I think you gotta, you gotta
look hard and hard far and wide to find somewhere that makes tuna pie.
Well, it's like, it's like a pasty, you know, it's a hand pie probably.
And yeah, Mike, I think is right.
Like it is like chicken pot pie.
And I think we certainly ate our fair share of hamburger helper
and tuna helper growing up, which was just, you bought the box of seasoning
and pasta and then you tossed in the meat.
I'm going to guess that you ate more than your fair share of tuna helper.
Oh, I feel very unfair.
Uh, I, but if you use a milder tuna with cream sauce, it's good.
I'm looking up tuna pie Burbank and I'm going to see if there's a place
you can get it, get that door.
There's a good papoosa place, uh, on victory.
Maybe they have a tuna one.
I don't know.
Maybe you can order a papoosa, scrape out what's in it and put
a bunch of canned tuna in there.
Okay.
Yeah.
Re-seal it.
Just like there's an epinada place, seal it back up like an envelope.
World's world.
Epinada has been there forever.
Yeah, I know what you're, what you're describing is good sounding.
You're acting as if that is, uh, related.
I wear it or we're not going to find anywhere in Burbank with a tuna pie.
I don't think so, but I mean, I'll, I'll keep looking.
I don't think there's not an, there's not an obvious answer when you do a Google.
But you must be dying for it.
And that, like, if you could leave here and know that within five minutes,
it would be, I, I would prefer the tuna melt still, but I would, I would be
interested in trying the tuna pie.
What is, uh, Sarah Connor say at the end of T two, three to eight, the battle
continues and that's Mike trying to find a tuna pie, the battle didn't
last very long of me looking it up.
But you certainly will continue.
You were, I was defeated today, but tomorrow is another day.
I will fight on.
I will eat tuna pie.
I will eat as hot as possible.
That's also hot.
And this was on it.
This is another, that, that this I don't like.
And then there was also, there's a site called Dave land.
That also has a lot of great old photos, especially of this really, really good
for photos of this pirate ship.
Uh, but then, you know, mixed with, uh, here's like firsthand accounts of
somebody who are memories of this place.
And this, this account of somebody describing going there and saying, I
remember getting a hot tuna burger with chips and a root beer lunch, the root
beer lunch is a strange way to phrase it.
First of all, but then hot, all caps, a hot tuna bird.
Let me tell you, this is a sculling, hot, hot as it could be.
I don't, I, I, I'm so nauseated by the idea of this pirate ship
exploding with hot tuna.
Would it be better for firing out tuna out of, I know I don't think so,
but doesn't the, I just don't trust how in 1955 they're giving me piping hot
tuna in a burger or in a pie.
I think that's just to differentiate from a cold tuna salad sandwich.
But that all caps has intention to me.
Oh, really?
That's yes, that's what I'm saying.
It was a hot tuna bird.
Well, you didn't say so hot.
Like the engine of the, or whatever you would, it wasn't a steam pirate ship.
I assume it was a sailboat, but you would still, if there was an engine, you would
just throw in tuna in there, like on a railroad.
Shovell in some more tuna.
Right.
And just hot.
And they, but they would pull it out sometimes to, they would cook it also over
those, over those coals and give it to the people.
And if you ask nicely, if it was your birthday, like Johnny can stand, uh, just,
just like aim line up with one of the cannons and a captain guy will say, fire
the tuna and then just a hot ball of sculpted tuna get fired into his face.
They let him drink.
They give him a big glass of the water from the can tuna.
What if you ordered a can, a tuna cannonball and it was a perfectly
spherical piece of tuna, that'd be fun.
That's that.
Yeah.
Well, that's getting into too much tuna territory.
It could be a smaller though.
If it's like the size of the car, that is like a baseball.
Yeah.
Baseball size ball of tuna.
Maybe not too much.
All right.
Yeah.
Just a standard tuna ball.
Tuna in the tennis.
We're talking not, not softball.
Let's not go crazy here.
It's not a softball.
Yeah.
No, it's not.
No, that's entirely too much tuna.
Oh, yeah.
What damn a baseball worth of tuna.
Easy.
Oh, of course.
No, are you kidding me?
All right.
Well, I can eat a foot long subway tuna sub full of tuna.
That's a lot of tuna.
That's like, as far as like ice cream scoopers full of tuna.
That's like six scoops.
That is so many scoops.
Uh, now it's hard for, I can't picture like I'm all right.
Well, let's just, okay.
So we've established that both of you can remember we're talking just pure tuna.
There's no, there's no, there's no condiments to go with it.
There's no bread.
There's nothing else to distract from just the tune itself.
So you, we've established that you're comfortable eating a baseball of tuna.
Yeah.
You could do that right now.
Let's go.
Let's just keep going.
Bigger football.
Um, to share, I think regulation football, it's not, it's not a deflate gate
situation where we could, the smaller, oh, post deflate gate.
Right.
Uh, is it, it's not tuna salad.
Um, it's just regular tuna dry.
You know, you guys are going to have to tell me how you're preparing it to get
it into the bottle because I definitely couldn't eat a football size dry piece
of tuna like that big.
That's too big.
You guys declare the preparation.
What you say, what it takes for you.
And I don't like the sharing you get, you have to split up and what, what is
it going to take to get you to eat a football size tuna if they took tuna
salad and they sculpted it into a football, an NFL football, I could eat it.
Okay.
No problem.
Uh, what about a little filling, but I could do it easily.
Let's go bowling ball and let's just maybe declare a big, let's declare pounds.
That's going to be the easiest way to, uh, you know, do you think you could do eight?
Do you think you could do 12?
And that's not necessarily true, but that's not because it's lighter.
I'm just sort of talking for size of ball size of ball.
Okay.
Size of ball.
So like a nine, 10 pound ball.
Yeah.
You think you can clear a nine?
Keep in mind, you got those finger holes.
So that actually gives you a little break.
You got three finger holes that, and that's, those are three less.
That's three fingers worth of tuna.
You don't have to eat.
It's not hollow.
No, cause it was hollow.
No problem.
No, no, it's pure.
But there are holes.
It's pure tuna.
Yeah.
With the whole, with the holes card so that you could, if hard enough, pick it
up and potentially even a bullet down a lane.
If it, okay.
I could eat the football.
I think mostly no problem, but I would feel a little bit
like, ah, those last couple of bites.
I do think I could finish that much tuna, but it would be a struggle.
The last 25% of the ball.
You would really need the emotional support of a group you were eating in
front of where this a man versus food situation Jason cheering.
Well, let's turn to Jason now.
I don't, I don't know if we've got an answer on football or bowling.
I was skeptical about the football.
I think I would just need to load up all the accoutrements and talking
relish or chopped pickle, maybe a little lemon juice, um, uh, maybe some
chopped egg mayonnaise, certainly.
Chopped egg takes due next level.
Um, and you need the whites and the yolk and just one, uh, let's see.
Uh, maybe a squirt of mustard.
Um, but I don't, it would you be, would just, just to complete the bowling
ball image, would you be fine with the squirt of mustard spelling out the
word Brunswick what specifically it's a bowling, the bowling ball.
That's a brand of bowling ball.
Well, if the good people at Brunswick were involved, uh, I think I would,
they're sponsoring this event.
Yes.
I would give it a shot, but if Mikey eats the full bowling ball, I want
him to get like a champion ring.
You see, you're just, you'd rather cheer him on that.
You think I would be number one in this cheering section with like the little
Simpson, um, Homer Simpson, triangle flags.
Okay.
Would you, would you eat the triangle flag if it was made of tuna?
Oh, sure.
Those ones are really smart.
I think tuna salad, especially you've got the mayo in there.
Tuna salad goes down so nice.
It goes down really, so you could end up eating what you could end up eating too
much because it's, it's pretty smooth.
It's a, it's like kind of like White Castle.
It's like a liquid, like White Castle Firehouse, like they're one of those
places where they just load up vegetables and cheese and sauces.
And I was like, when I was eating it, I was like too much.
I pulled some stuff off, but I should have pulled more.
Were you pulled off the vegetables?
I pulled, well, I don't like tomatoes and I pulled off the onion too.
Cause onion on cold sandwiches overpowers everything.
Was it not cooked onion?
Cause like a raw onion.
Okay.
So I guess I can see what you're saying.
I would, I would, I'm a big tomato guy.
I'm a, I'm not as big of a raw onion guy, but I'll eat them.
So tomato, very acidic.
Yeah.
Okay.
Great.
This is the one of the first things that's been said food wise that I
haven't had an objection to.
Okay.
Great.
Let me throw out one more bowling thing.
Yeah.
If there's 10 bowling pins that are all compact tuna, how many could you get through?
Uh, one and a half.
One and a half.
I think that's a good realistic.
Yeah.
Again, I'm pushing it to do that, but I think one and a half.
And the momentum of the, the electricity that you.
Yeah.
It was a whole thing.
Cause you gotta remember, you're going to have that tuna excitement.
You're going to have that tuna sensuality that I've seen on display.
Are you talking form factor?
Are you including the weight too?
Uh, I'm not sure.
We, uh, it's, I'm saying that whatever weight tuna actually is, is just
pressed into the, oh, that's actually better.
Cause bowling ball balls tend to be heavy as do the pins.
No, that's what I was saying that I think an eight pound bowling ball sized
ball of tuna is not necessarily going to be eight pounds.
Yeah.
It's lighter materials.
Right.
So keep that in mind.
I wasn't choosing a, when choosing a weight.
I was keeping it in mind.
Yeah, I'm a smaller guy, so I'm not going to talk too big.
I'd only go with one pin.
I let Mike have that go for the half, go for the gold.
I just, whatever.
Cause you know, I know what's coming on the other end of this.
I, I, there is going to be an avalanche of comments from other tuna guys.
I just, let me just say to out loud to the person at the, probably the one
person out there who's with me on this.
I'm, I hear you.
I know that this episode has made you get close to throwing up,
imagining a full bowling set made entirely of tuna.
And I just, I acknowledge you.
And those were your questions.
So come say hi to me.
Yes, Scott, I will say, uh, I'll give you some credit.
The one school lunch, uh, that never sat right with me was a tuna sandwich
and a little juice box of you who, cause that made it really taste like dead fish.
The you who you're saying?
Was bad.
Now, God knows what's in you who it's mostly water.
So you would not have gone for the chocolate drink.
That is one of the items that comes with the, that is weird.
Tuna pie, please.
And mom will have a tuna boat and we will both have chocolate drinks with that.
Thank you.
Fine.
Servicemen aboard.
Coke zero and cool ranch Doritos both have very prominent flavors.
So they, they kind of, you know, is that a good thing or a bad thing?
It's good.
So it's not like you're not really tasting the tuna.
You're tasting something else when you're going back and forth.
Were you anti you who in general, when you were, oh no, I loved you who, and I drank it.
But it was just like, if that was what was in the fridge for the week, you know, you
who juice boxes, which we had a brand of juice boxes back East called sipsies.
And we just called them all sipsies.
So I still call them sipsies.
And then I have to kill myself mentally and say, you would be a sipsy.
Are you who?
Yeah.
You would be a sipsy, but a Capri sun bag would also be a sipsy.
Oh, Capri sons are sipsies.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
They were all kind of sipsies.
Rules of sipsy.
So, um, I don't, I mean, is this not vile to that?
It's nothing but tuna options.
And then the drinks are coffee, milk and chocolate drink.
But what is bizarre to me, milk is like a heavy drink.
Obviously.
Uh, uh, but that is, that is such an old school lunch, you know, like a big
tuna salad sandwich and then big glass of milk is like, that would be like, no
one would bat an eye at that in 19, whatever 50 something.
Yeah.
But I don't know if you guys bat, I think you, I think you guys could, I think you
could do the eat like wall challenge.
No problem.
I think I could do it.
I think I also would have loved to stand in front of the ship, which I learned was
made partially of Douglas fir and partially of polished mahogany.
I believe that was a Jim Hill.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
Douglas fir.
Two fine woods.
Well, the thing is though, as the years went on, those fine woods were not
entirely what it was made of because as the years went on, the ship sitting in
the lagoon rotted away and when pieces rotted away, they would replace those
with concrete, which were more viable for just standing the test of time in a
lagoon, but what this leads to is that, uh, uh, time passes the, the, the fine
people at chicken of the sea took their confusing name elsewhere and they stopped
doing this branding in 1969, it became captain hooks galley.
At that point, there was only one tune, uh, option instead of, uh, 19 or whatever.
Uh, uh, but you know, so it still stood as part of the fantasy land, uh, experience
for a number of years until the fantasy and redo in 82, 83, uh, and I think it
was on everybody on the top of mind for everybody, for Tony Baxter, he bemoans
this, that he couldn't, uh, get the thing moved because they started looking into
it and like, well, can we just like, you know, I think they'd even carved out a
place that was maybe where we were talking, maybe about cruises, maybe in the
small worlds lead up area, but they started looking at it and like, wait, a
bunch of it is concrete.
That's not going to move.
But the rest of it is all wood.
That's rotting away.
This was kind of like not kept up very well termites.
I believe termites too.
Really?
They went to strap the boat down and to move it.
And they're like, this is filled with termites.
Wow.
They had already, we were learning about all of the weird creatures that
used to be at Disneyland termites.
They separately put the figurehead of the ship, which was Catalina, the
mermaid, of course, Catalina, the chicken of the sea mermaid.
We know Catalina.
They modified her a little.
I think Jason's first crush from the tunic.
Yeah.
The tuna can lady.
Can I admit something to you?
Sometimes I go home at night and I kiss the can.
I got to practice on something.
I asked you, do you want to make out and you're telling me about a tuna can.
Um, they, there was a story that they put the front of the ship and the
figure on a forklift, which stopped short and then flew off the forklift and
shattered the figurehead and the, I guess that's the stern of the ship that
shattered and then the other thing was rotting away, but they wanted to move
it to the end of storybook boats because they said, oh, storybook boats
starts with a big thing.
You go through the mountain of the maestro.
It should end with a big thing.
Oh yeah.
And that'd be a good place for it.
Cause it's still a lagoon and it needs a finale.
And you know, we've never talked about that ride.
We've never done an episode about it.
I guess it'll come in class of 55, but there used to be this thing where the
finale was that they would point to the like, like just the functional area where
the boats are sent when the rides over.
And they would say, we call that never, never land because you can never,
never go there.
Have we ever talked about that?
I don't think so.
That's what it always was.
Mike told, I've never spoken that on the show.
I always thought that was really funny.
They would just like make use of that in this, you know, in this ride with lots
of charming miniatures, the final thing you see is just like a bunch of flappy
plastic is where boats go and get fixed.
So they would make that joke to try to acknowledge the underwhelming finale of
it. Eventually that got replaced by let's try what it's like.
Is it like the Ariel's kingdom or something?
Like, I forget what the very end, but anyway, it was like, it was such a bad
finale of that ride that they just made a joke out of it.
So to have it end with the pirate ship would have been a much more spectacular
really great joke, though.
But they always, they worked so hard on hiding the entrance to the maintenance
base that talks for like the, the phantasmic floats in both coasts and stuff.
And there's nothing I want to see more than unthemed boring maintenance base.
Sometimes you get lucky in Indiana Jones, the door will be open.
Oh yeah.
You know, you see a car vehicle go in there.
You ever seen that?
We got to see the Spider-Man scoop workshop.
Oh, that's right.
Yes, we did.
Lid up, see like, that was very cool.
Yeah.
Because one of them was being, you know, had been repaired and was being
programmed, so you saw it go through all the motions.
Like that was crazy.
It's doing the ride without moving through the ride, but you can tell,
okay, that's the big drop of that.
It's spinning around the pumpkin or whatever.
Uh, wait, it's not a pumpkin.
It's a, it doesn't throw pumpkins.
It is a pump.
Yeah, I thought I was like, damn, I'm making, I throws pumpkins.
I'm goblin.
It is.
Okay.
Yeah, he throws Goblin does too.
They all throw pumpkins.
So anyways, yeah, this ship brought it away and then parts of it
shattered when they tried to move it and move it.
And that was the, the end of that.
And we have no, and it is one of these things that is like a treasured memory
for lots of kids of original Disneyland era.
And then I think it's maybe a disappointment to some people who go
and like, oh, that's right.
There's no pirate ship.
And yeah, though I always, my mental fondness for it kind of came from my mom.
And I, before the episode, I was like, oh, I gotta ask her about it.
Cause she's probably got great stories.
I said, do you have any strong memories or specifics about the
chicken of the sea pirate ship?
Cause I swear she would speak glowingly of it.
And then she wrote back, vague.
I believe you could board it and walk around.
Thought it seemed huge and interesting.
The end.
All right, mom, that's all we got.
That's all accurate.
Uh, you know what I, uh, I guess I thank you guys for having so much tuna
information because my mom was correct.
And there wasn't that, if there was only that to say about it, then we
wouldn't, we needed an hour 10 of tuna material in order to flesh out the episode.
Well, I also found, uh, one of the van eaten gallery auction catalogs.
They were selling some stuff from this, uh, chicken of the sea pirate ship
restaurant barrel seat, because that was the little stores that you would eat
around the lagoon, you know, they would, which that looks really, it was always
described as like, yeah, yeah, lovely.
Like shaded area, like a nice place of calm and fantasy land.
So they were, they were selling one of those.
Yeah, that's good.
But they were all so that they were estimated going for two to $4,000.
Understandably, but they were also selling a chicken of the sea pirate ship
restaurant food tray liner that they're, uh, they said an unusual and
understandably extremely rare food tray liner from the chicken of the sea
pirate ship restaurant and fantasy land.
And they make sure to note normally thrown away after the meal.
This particular one was saved as a souvenir, complete with creasing and
staining from what was short of a bin, a tasty tuna treat.
Ew, tasty tunic tree, old tunas.
But they were estimating, they were estimating that was only going to go
for 50 to $100 and I was like, fuck, why didn't I bid on that?
I didn't see that one in whatever exhibit.
This was part of you.
If you came up to me like, guess what I got?
I just bought this menu for a while.
That's so cool.
You give me a big hug because you're so excited about what you bought.
And then I'm like, so what's the way that looks a little weird though.
Oh, it's just a 60 year old tuna stains.
I would have like shoved you away.
I would have gone and taken five showers.
That is sold.
That is an episode where I've been grossed out.
That is one of the grossest things I've ever heard.
Yeah, that is driving away, Mike.
And I just chanting to not time to not time.
We're going fishing after this.
It's the glee with which it was presented by Van.
What was sure to have been a bunch of sticky fingers covered in tuna juice.
They got their grubby little tuna paws all of you.
You don't say that with an exclamation point.
This should not be celebrated.
I miss it when I first started reading that description and I kind of peeked ahead.
And I was like, that's a tasty tuna treat.
Yeah, it does. OK.
Hip hip hooray.
Somebody got somebody's eyes were a little bit bigger than their stomach
and they ate too big of a tuna boat.
And maybe some of it dripped out of their mouth onto the menu
and onto the placeman.
Naughty little tuna boy.
They were being lotty little tuna boys.
I mean, look, dripping with excitement.
Could it just been pastry shell grease or something?
It could have been pastry shell grease.
It could have been any number of weird.
Could have been chocolate drink.
There were so many wonderful goose that went great together.
Yeah. At this wonderful restaurant.
You guys have got it now.
You guys got to be.
It's going to kill you that you can't go to this today.
I would love to be brought back from the dead.
I would. Well, OK.
What do you take it?
Would you get rid of in order to bring this restaurant back, Jason?
Oh, jeepers.
You got one Disneyland or California Adventure.
You can pick either one.
Pick a pick any ticket.
Sorry, Florida Space Mountain.
You're just a little too rough.
That's an easy one.
It's an easy one. You got to go to Disneyland, I think.
Oh, now I have to go to Disneyland.
Yeah. OK.
E-ticket is or it can be D as well.
Can I go over to California Adventure?
Yeah, OK.
Sorry, web slingers.
You're like a ticket is a web site.
Well, there's no argument here.
Is Casey Jr. a D ticket?
No, no.
See, I think I guess I made the rules.
I have to play by them.
Bye bye, Snow White and Pinocchio.
Those aren't E tickets either.
You don't think those are D?
Well, you changed the rules to D.
I think they literally weren't.
I think, like, I don't know.
Really? Maybe I'm wrong.
I don't know, because they were simpler back in the day.
All right. Well, Rise of Resistance gone.
All right.
Well, you can do that without batting an eyelash.
You're dying for that to be gone.
I'm trying to figure out if that was.
Yeah, were those because back in the day, especially, those were really cool.
C ticket was Rocket to the Moon.
It was sitting on those shitting mules.
It was Canoes, which were named something that I'm not going to read out loud.
Could you feed the mule a little bit of your uneaten tuna meal?
You could feed the mule anything, Michael.
OK, well.
They didn't pay much attention.
This is strange, actually, that C tickets, Snow White, Peter Pan, Mr.
Toad, all of these were C tickets, but the ability to ride on a real mule
and to see what it what it pukes up onto the dirt trail in front of you.
That was probably worth examining at some point is like what was what?
Yeah. What was everything assigned?
Because Florida had the ticket books.
Was it capacity related that like you could get a lot more people through?
Oh, I don't think so.
Yeah, that's why I never thought that.
But I'm just trying to think why those would be C versus mule rides.
Yeah, that's that's that's what the strangest even back then.
Or like crowds or wait times, you know.
It was was mule ride, like a more popular guest attraction.
I loved the mules.
He only bit my leg once.
All right. Well, boy, I don't know how you're going to come down from that.
Well, I do know you're going to come down from this.
You're going to place an order as soon as we're out.
That's right. All right.
Well, enjoy your hot tuna nights.
You know, for now, you survived.
I barely survived podcast the ride.
Thanks for subscribing in the second gate.
If you want to dig even deeper.
Thank God about different topics.
Join us on our VIP Patriot Club three or you get one more bonus
episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
All right. Well, then we'll keep talking about other 1955 stuff soon,
including Frontierland's Julie departed Fort Liver,
the old West Fort loaded with liver burgers and hot, hot liver spaghetti.