Welcome to Podcast The Ride The Second Gate, where today we discuss more iterations of
Fantasmic.
Will it leave you, the audience, feeling enthuseasmic, or will you find it anti-climaxmic, and will you be apathetmic?
We'll find out. I'm Scott Garrier.
Hi, I'm Mike Carlson.
Orgasmic.
Or will you be orga- Oh, that one's already-
That's real, that's real.
Oh my god, I didn't have to change that one.
Wow.
That's what they should have called this whole show, obviously.
Well, yeah.
It would have been right there.
If they wanted to be-
Jason Sheridan, hello.
I didn't have a mic, but I sure enjoyed that opening joke.
Oh, thank you.
I'm being sincere.
I'm like, I'm worried it was going to sound sarcastic, but I really was along for the ride.
You were worried it was going to sound sarcasmic.
Sarcasmic, yeah.
There's really no end to the words that you can put the branding of our favorite mouse in.
Sarcasmic is when Minnie is like, Mickey, do you need help?
And Mickey is like, oh yeah, I don't need any help, thanks.
But he does need help, you're saying.
He does need help, yeah.
He like, the fridge fell on him when he was trying to move it or something, and she's like,
Oh, I'm fine, I want to be down here.
Right, right.
It's like a weighted blanket.
And Anvil fell on his foot, and he's like in such pain.
And Minnie's like, do you need something?
And he's like, no, I don't.
I just need to go to the hospital.
Come on.
I like the cartoon problem that you picked.
I like that cartoon characters would be moving anvils around their homes so often.
Did Mickey ever get hit with an anvil in Disney cartoon?
It doesn't feel right.
It feels more Warner Brothers, but certainly on the table.
I don't know, has Mickey been hit by an anvil?
He only shows up in that skydiving sequence in Roger Rabbit, right?
He's in it again at the end, isn't he?
Yeah, but I don't think he gets hurt.
I mean, Disney's going to allow the characters to cross-pollinate,
but they won't allow bugs on Mickey violence.
Right.
They were never going to stand for that.
Well, if anybody knows, does Mickey get hit with an anvil ever in his long career?
Yeah.
He should.
He doesn't take a lot of the abuse.
I mean, that's sort of Donald's role, Goofy's role in a silly way.
It was Goofy's role one terrible night of the Hollywood studio show, which we'll discuss.
But no, I think they save Mickey from...
Yeah.
Lonesome Ghosts, Mickey gets a little beat up, but not as bad as Goofy.
But not, yeah.
I don't think there's...
I can't remember.
Don't scuff the suit.
Oh, thank you, Goofy.
I don't need help.
I'll put the fire blanket on myself.
Mickey has the Vin Diesel rock claws in his contract
that he can't look weak in a movie.
It must be the same thing.
He's such a big star that he can't lose a fight.
Yeah.
Like Steven Seagal losing to Hanson Franz.
Right.
So The Rock and Jason Statham all have a no anvil clause in their contract
to make sure that they don't look foolish in one of the movies.
It's like a wrestling holdover.
Yes.
Well, you mean an anvil or you mean an actual...
No, you can't lose.
It is, but our action stars also have it.
So it's not exclusively wrestling.
Well, our hero.
Well, yes, our hero.
Sylvester Stallone and John Voight and Mel Gibson are going to save Hollywood.
John Voight.
Wait, hold on.
I know about this.
Yeah, he's...
I know what he's talking about.
I'm just saying that.
He's in that list, yeah.
John Voight is in the list.
Oh, he's on the Trump list.
Trump appointed three people to fix Hollywood.
Right.
And one was, yes, the three stars of equal status.
87-year-old John Voight, who surely knows where he is at all moments of the day.
He knows what's hip.
Yeah.
And he knows his name.
Right.
This much we know.
Folks, today we are returning to the world of Fantasmic.
Realized it had been about a year since we covered this on the main feed, since we first
handled the Disneyland stalwarts live attraction, which has been running on the
Rivers of America, a show characterized by very memorable music, by a fun construct
to put a lot of Disney characters all in one place for Mickey to do battle with many
great villains in Disney history, but not get his suit scuffed up in any way.
No rips, no tears.
No need to go to a tailor.
You know, we had fun talking about that a year ago.
We said, we'll put it on pause and then we'll come back and we'll handle Disney World.
We will handle Tokyo Disney Sea, which is no longer running.
And we will handle whatever becomes of Disneyland's Fantasmic.
I don't know if you guys remember that this was sort of the because we put up an episode
right before it was about to come back because it had been gone for a year or so because
the dragon at the end of the show caught on fire.
Instead of just breathing fire, it breathed fire all over itself and burns to a crisp.
It's been one of the most dramatic, I think I said at the time, metal displays in Disney
history.
You know, you just brought up the Paris fire that Peter Noon from Herman's Hermits noticed.
The World Showcase Paris.
Not yet, not real Paris.
Notre Dame did not burn down again, seen only by Herman's Hermits star Peter Noon.
Peter Noon playing outside Notre Dame, playing all the Herman's Hermits hits and then it
catches fire.
No.
No, this was, but you know, and like this happens here and there.
There's little, you know, there's fires, there's accidents at theme parks, but they are not
usually caught on, clearly on camera from 5,000 angles and it was really insane when
this happened.
Also, yeah, the thing that like thousands of, hundreds, thousands of people are watching
that night, the focal point of everyone's attention catches on fire as well on its own
little stage.
Yeah.
That's more rare.
It wasn't the Sindbad show at Islands of Adventure and a prop that people don't even
know is coming caught fire backstage and then there was some smoke and people like coughed
a little and is that supposed to happen?
Yeah, probably.
This was at the, and didn't it cross over into the moment where the dragon, who is Maleficent,
you hear Maleficent's voice screaming in horror because like it was like five seconds off
from when the dragon is supposed to be defeated.
So there was certainly a minute where, okay, screaming, it is like, it's burning alive.
I guess Mickey won, but then Mickey won a little too hard.
Yeah.
He was winning for 40 horrifying seconds.
I don't want to just win, I want you to suffer.
I want you to scream, I want your relatives to be thinking about it, I want them to need
counseling.
I want to bankrupt your children.
Leave the gun, take the cannoli.
What is that?
I gotta ask for that reference.
That's the godfather.
Okay.
That's the instruction to Michael.
I should know that, I guess.
Everybody's got cinematic blind spots, sometimes the most famous ones.
Sure.
But anyways, so some of what we were heading for last year was, okay, well when this thing,
you know, we'll do a sequel episode and we will discuss whatever exciting change transpires,
whatever is, because we know it's coming back, but they haven't said what they're doing about
the finale, they haven't said what they're replacing the dragon with, and as soon as
we realize what that is, we will come back guns blazing with an exciting episode all
about it.
And then quickly we saw what it was.
Maleficent the dragon was replaced by human Maleficent on a big pole.
Long, two words, baby, long Maleficent.
Oh, that's right, that's a much better phrasing for it.
Long Maleficent.
You know, you're scared of her in Sleeping Beauty, but what if she was giant?
Oh, you mean like she got, and she has giant proportions?
No.
It's as if her head and torso are the same, but her legs are now 130 feet long.
She's like the Marvel Comics villain Stilt Man.
So the normal size body, just the legs are very long.
Very long.
Do you know, Michael, do you in your day to day life relate to the character of Stilt Man?
Yes, I think oftentimes I think of him and I feel sympathy for his plight.
You know, he's a bad guy, but he's just misunderstood.
Enough annoying flights and crotch crushed rides on roller coasters will turn you into a Stilt Man.
Yes, that's correct.
And luckily, I haven't been supervillainized yet.
Maybe when I go to Epic Universe this next time during our live shows,
all the crushing will finally turn me into sort of a Stilt Man like supervillain.
You got a couple rides left. You got to see what they do to your crotch.
Right.
Hey, aside real quick, because I wanted to ask you, because you did do Stardust Racers.
I did, yes.
When you were there, just a chatter I saw online, was it stinky?
OK, I've seen the stinky question asked about the area.
Is it always, is that the term it's always used, stinky?
I've not, I don't know. I can't remember. Jason likes the word stinky.
I also like the word stinky. I don't know that I've seen.
I saw people saying there was bit of a smell and someone else pulled up a map showing a water reclamation.
It's very close to Epic Universe.
That used to be a weapons testing ground where Epic Universe was.
Do we have any idea what weapons were tested on what is now Celestial Park and Darkmoor?
And what and what were those weapons?
How have those weapons been used to wreak havoc on our world?
Well, something they tested there brought all the monsters into one big house.
That's true.
And I am scared.
That's true. I think maybe it was more like airplane engines, but I don't know that 100 percent.
I don't think they were shooting nukes off like 10 minutes from Islands of Adventure.
Yeah. Yeah.
I don't think that's what was happening.
And it wasn't like the weapon that Bane stole.
That blew up the football.
Like a big fancy, like kind of modern, big orby kind of nuclear weapon. It wasn't like that.
That imploded that football field. No, I don't think so.
I think maybe at the least it was like airplane engines, I think.
Yeah.
But then there is a water treatment plant nearby.
And I heard somebody maybe on the day we were there say that it's nearby.
And I've heard people mention.
I heard somebody on the day say it'd be stinky in here.
Yeah, I was wondering what that was about.
But I don't I didn't notice stinky epic universe.
Well, freshly planted plants require a lot of mulch and fertilizer.
So that could have been.
I mean, it just is what it is.
Maybe we were lucky and the wind was blowing the right way that day or something.
Because I've seen multiple people say, yes, it smells.
And then I heard people say epic universe smells worse at night.
Oh, my God.
So I don't know. I'm not sure.
And yes, Stardust, I think Stardust is Stardust.
There's a big open like pie where you can see right into a break room.
And there's a lot of you can see a lot that way.
And I think perhaps the treatment plan is that is over there.
Because they need to plant some trees you can't see over there.
But also maybe it would block some of the stink.
Yeah, so I don't know.
I didn't detect like a Gary, Indiana style smell, meaning like Gary, the town of Gary, Indiana, like stinks.
You drive through portions of Indiana.
It smells.
Do we do recall when we talked about with Ashley Crystal Hairston about the Tacoma aroma?
Yes, I think I'm trying to remember what the response to that was.
That I feel like people said it is slander that the Tacoma aroma is gone.
Does that seem familiar to anyone?
Vaguely.
I'm trying to remember what the sense we got of the Tacoma.
Like if it was still there.
Yeah, so the Gary, Indiana stinky Anna.
I don't know what they call it.
Yeah, I haven't driven through there in a while.
Gary, Indiana has a scary stinky Anna.
That's a fun.
Yeah, I don't know what the fun name for it is, but I guess we could maybe be the ones that coined it.
But yes, anyway, Jason, bring a big clothespin when you go to Epic Universe for your nose.
A big comical.
That's right.
Just in case we're there on a particularly smelly day.
Now, if touring plans as Len Testa could change his app and his books to let us know when the smelliest days of Epic Universe.
Yes.
If you could have somebody also now measuring stink level when it comes to Epic, I think that would be a good idea for him to do.
OK, yeah, from neutral to P.U.
Right.
Like a skunk.
How many skunks or how many like Limburger cheeses?
Like you could do a fun scale.
Or it's four skunks.
But then you get on the particular lease that it's like it is a it's a skunk with diarrhea with cheese diarrhea.
Yes, you could show the skunk eating Limburger cheese and then it coming out the other way.
I mean, that's returned from a brief business trip to Gary, Indiana.
Right.
These are fun ideas for Len.
If he wants to use them, he can.
If not, whatever area people would need to buy that.
Right.
There'd be a much like you want to know wait times, but you need to know stink.
Yeah.
So we'll see when we're there in June.
We'll see how it is.
Assess this stink.
Yeah.
And also, and please, anyone let us know any intel you have about the military history of this spot.
What what what ghosts remain besides the ones in Darkmoor?
What mutant hybrids were created there?
But anyways, yeah, Tom Maleficent is what we've had for for a year now.
I don't know if that caused the delay in us doing an episode.
If there was if it was like, huh, I think we can wait a beat on that.
I don't think anybody needs us to talk about giant legged Maleficent for a while.
No, I guess we I went straight to legs, but we don't know what's under there.
And she's in it's it's sort of, you know, presumably production wise, she's on some kind of hydraulic lift.
But, you know, in the storytelling, it's probably just it's like a big flowing draper gown or something.
Yeah.
So it could be that that's like all like celestial power underneath, like that she it's a bunch of like she's flying or something.
Like you're saying the evil forces are getting her to fly.
Yeah, yeah.
There's like a bunch of like projection swirling star dust or something.
There's like energy.
I see what you're saying.
Maybe she's not long, but her dress got long and it's full of energy tentacles or yes, tentacles under there.
That's a good idea storyline wise.
Yeah, hard to say.
Practically.
It's kind of like when your local municipality needs to trim some real tall trees that are getting too close to power lines.
So but it could be like because like in the old California Adventure show and I mean, obviously in the Aladdin movie,
genies have sort of a tail thing.
They don't always have legs when they're flying.
They kind of have just like that flowing.
You went to the show before you went to the movie.
Well, you know, because not because I love I do love the show, but I go to the show because I bet it's a similar hydraulic lift.
When Jafar turns into the genie at the end, he shoots up in the sky and there's a whole like kind of red ribbon.
Under his leg.
So you could also say he has tall legs as well.
But I bet it's a similar hydraulic lift to that Maleficent is on at the end of Fantasmic.
No, I've heard the opinion that this because this tall Maleficent has has existed as an option as the B mode.
Yeah.
In both Disneyland and Disney World.
So people have plenty of audiences have seen tall Maleficent and been impressed by tall Melissa.
I've seen the opinion that well, you know what?
If you don't know there's supposed to be a dragon there and then you get to see the tallest witch or whatever.
What's she?
What's Maleficent?
Yeah.
Good question.
I don't know if I can use a phrase from that was used in the prior episode.
An old crone is a more official job title than old crone.
Is Maleficent a sorceress?
That sounds right.
She's like a queen or something.
No, I think if I had remembered any of the first Maleficent movie that I did see, maybe I can answer this question, but I don't remember any of it.
And I did watch it.
Wow.
The Angelina Jolie Maleficent.
But I think Maleficent is a sorceress.
I know that.
That's confirmed.
And I do know that Maleficent's father is going to save Hollywood.
Well, that is a very good, very good point.
She's certainly a mistress of all evil.
I'm seeing that as well.
Does that help?
Are you looking at t-shirts now?
That's something.
T-shirts?
No.
Would you wear a mistress of all evil shirt?
Yeah, you would.
I would.
Me?
Yeah, maybe.
All right, maybe.
I hadn't really thought about it.
It just seemed like something they would put on.
Like, new shirts are out, you know.
Yeah, his and her.
And the mister mistress of all evil.
Yeah, mister mistress of all evil.
You should get that.
You and Jane should get those.
Yeah.
If they're vintage, though.
Well, yeah.
Well, the hubby and wife shirts I bought on Amazon.
Oh, those aren't vintage.
No, no, they're not.
Did you get in trouble?
Huh?
Did I get in trouble?
Because they're new shirts.
Well, no.
No, I think I got in trouble more for their content.
Oh, so you didn't get in trouble.
What are these shirts?
I'm sorry, what?
I was buying some pre-wedding, like, fun stuff.
And I bought...
Toys and stuff.
Yeah.
I bought...
Target stuff that you taught us about.
I bought t-shirts.
The one had, like, a little Mickey.
And the one had a little Minnie, like, circle.
And it said hubby and wifey.
Mostly so I'd take a picture on Instagram.
I was really looking for bootleg ones.
But unfortunately, Disney kind of realized people would buy that.
So those were official Disney shirts.
Oh, they were?
On Amazon.
Oh, I thought they were bootlegs, too.
Through the Disney storefront on Amazon.
So why did you get in trouble for the...
Was it for hubby or was it for wifey?
She was like, I can't believe you bought these.
But what do you think...
Which word do you think was it?
Both of them in tandem?
Both of them equally, probably?
Yeah, I think they were both, sort of.
Trying.
It sounds like the kind of thing I would be more upset about
because I don't like putting E at the end of an arbitrary...
No, it's Y. It's Y. You're okay.
No, but the sound, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
But it didn't say little hubby boy or anything.
No, I tried.
Believe me, I searched.
Couldn't get my Redbubble account to work.
I'm a little hubby boy.
The handsomest little hubby boy.
Could you add another word?
We keep adding words on to make it even worse.
Here's my conundrum is that I'm fighting to...
What I could do is pivot and change the topic,
but I'm so...
This is a video game battle
and I'm so knocked down by every time you say one of these
that I don't have the strength to change the topic.
I truly do.
I get beaten down by everyone.
I gotta build myself back up.
Jason, what was the last thing you said?
I said handsomest little hubby boy.
It could be handsomest, stinkiest little hubby boy.
Oh, stinkiest is good.
Naughty is good.
Naughty, stinky little hubby boy.
That's really making it worse.
Why do we want these sentiments together?
You want to be a boy, but you want to be a husband,
but you want to say the infantilized word hubby,
and you want to be stinky?
You want to be a stinky hubby.
I'm little, but I contain multitudes.
Look, just the fact of the matter is
Jason's a naughty little stinky little hubby boy.
That's just the fact.
Sorry.
That's who he is.
All right.
Well, we can restart the boss battle.
I don't know what.
I think we're...
I don't go too hard on Scott.
I'm teetering.
I'm tipping.
One more is the knockout.
Restart from checkpoint for Scott.
Oh, phew. Great.
Yes, thank you.
Load me up with a bunch of hearts.
Okay.
Back to the Hollywood Hills in the theater.
Strength back.
Anyway, it's funny that this is where it landed,
that this is fine for them,
and that maybe we never get a dragon again.
Yeah.
Dragon might be gone.
Because it feels very modern Disney company to say,
you know, you're good.
Right.
You don't need to, yeah.
Because we're going to pay more and get less
kind of world with them, and that's a lot less.
It's a lot less.
And also, I hate to be conspiratorial,
but it makes you think, doesn't it?
It makes me think,
did they burn down the dragon for insurance money?
I'm not saying they did.
I'm just saying it hasn't come back.
Yeah.
Is there...
How much was that dragon insured for?
I think the answer is no,
because if the replacement is a paid union performer,
then that's never Disney's...
That's a good point.
That's never what Disney would rather have.
Yeah, that's a good point.
But have we seen the Lloyds of London piece of paper
that says the Maleficent Dragon is insured for $1 billion?
That's right.
This famous stuff of so-and-so having their gams insured.
Yeah, right.
St. Charisse.
It was St. Charisse.
St. Charisse had her...
That's right.
She was a dancer, and she had her legs...
Supposedly, the legs were insured for $1 million.
That's what Jason insured that naughty little
stinky hubby boy shirt of his for a million dollars too.
Yeah, it did.
In case it gets burnt or lost.
I know, and he knows it's a gold mine too,
if that gets recreated illegally.
Right, yeah, we want to prevent it.
It's the most relatable, adorable phrase.
What gal out there hasn't dreamed of her little...
Having her own little stinky hubby boy?
Who hasn't swooned...
They're all thinking it.
As a girl, oh, someday my little stinky hubby boy will come.
Will come, yeah.
That's the song.
Didn't sing the right melody.
It's an off-brand melody.
Yeah, anyway, we'll see where it goes,
but I guess all this leaves Disney World
with the one functioning dragon.
Yeah.
I mean, maybe not on all nights,
because as I said, it happens there.
Sometimes you do get Tom Maleficent instead.
Yeah, it is a bummer.
I don't know.
It's been a year.
It feels like they could have rebuilt the dragon in a year.
I agree with what you...
When you say, like, yeah, maybe that's it.
Yeah.
Who knows?
Yeah, plenty of time.
They didn't do it,
and if people are still showing up, then why...
Maybe we said this before,
but in reminding myself that situation,
just that besides the complexity
and how big it was and the big staging area,
that thing had 60 microprocessors in its head,
like a special effects package in its brain.
Right.
Like, that thing, that was an expensive head.
Yeah.
I mean, when it happened,
people must have been partially like,
oh, God, this is dangerous.
What if it breathes that way
and a whole part of the audience gets singed?
A lot of people probably, once it happened, thought,
oh, okay, that's $10 million right there
or whatever it is.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Probably more.
Yeah.
I bet it's like 50 or something crazy.
50 million just in that dream?
How old is it, too, at this point?
It's been around for a long time, so...
Sure.
Maybe it's, I guess maybe,
I was going to say it would be cheaper now
if they built it, but maybe not.
Maybe it's just such a unique piece of technology
that they made a couple of them.
I think the last upgrades in Anaheim
were in the late 2010s.
Yeah, so maybe that.
So recent-ish, but less recent
than like the Millennium Falcon processors.
Everything always costs more than I think it does.
Say you didn't know anything about theme parks
and you go on Rides of the Resistance,
does it seem like it costs half a billion dollars?
Well, to people who enjoy the ride, maybe it does.
That's not if it gives you
a half a billion dollars of enjoyment.
I'm saying...
No, I'm saying if you were the kind of person
whose heart is open to liking this ride,
you might think this is very impressive.
I bet it costs half a billion dollars.
I mean, you would definitely say,
no, you would definitely say
because it doesn't feel like your friends are there,
this feels like 50K or 100K.
Friends are priceless.
Yeah, the friends are so much more money.
But I feel like if you didn't know anything about this stuff
and you're like, oh, that's $100 million to build that,
you go, oh my God, so much money, of course,
versus five times that.
I always feel like things are more than I would think.
Maybe I'm in the minority, I don't know.
I think, though, this was not, I don't know.
There's only estimates out here,
but I think the whole show costs 30 million,
so I don't think that one dragon costs 30 million.
But I'm sure it was a ton.
That makes sense.
I'm just saying I'm always kind of surprised by numbers.
Well, it probably all goes to very boring things.
Again, to bring up Lentesta,
they were talking about how economic troubles
could be tough for the parks and for expansion projects
because of just the cost of steel.
Hoarding steel, you think building a big dragon,
that's great.
Well, yeah, what it really boils down to, though,
is where's Disney going to get the steel?
Yeah, sure.
It would be too bad if current things, you know.
But then there's also other current,
like Universal is going to have their brand new park open,
but there's a million different travel advice
to travel agents internationally
or cautioning people about going to the United States
or academic organizations going,
maybe don't go to a conference.
Don't present it.
Maybe do it over Zoom.
Don't go because there was already
some other professors detained.
Yeah, and that is mainly because of the Epic Universe stinkiness.
There is concern that it will spread rapid.
Sure, it's just Orlando right now,
but as people, that's like a pandemic.
People travel to Epic Universe, they bring it back with them,
and before you know it, the stink is in California,
the stink is in New York.
It could just be the stinky steel
that Universal's been using,
because they could be building the Horror Nights thing
out in Vegas with that stinky steel.
We don't know.
That place, yeah.
They could be building Taffer's Tavern with stinky steel.
Well, there's no doubt they are.
First of all, he's building that with the cheapest.
He's building that with whatever the weakest little pig
built his house out of.
Was it straw?
Straw.
Okay.
Straw that sticks the brick.
No, he's building ...
This place is made of straw, and it stinks.
Good.
I like it.
Money goes to my pocket.
He was in Disney World, and might still be.
He was in Disney World for weeks when we were there.
Wow.
He was in Orlando, I mean,
maybe just overseeing every little part
of his Taffer's Tavern construction.
But I swear, a couple days ago,
another picture of him and Nicole, his wife,
you know, of course, from the show,
in Disney World watching the fireworks.
They were there for so long, maybe they still are.
Well, they might have been searching out the costume
used in the show of his double, Governor Ratcliffe.
I was going to say,
dragon burned down for insurance money,
Ratcliffe, dirty Ratcliffe costume
dumped on the side of the road as a tax write-off.
Backed up and run over several times.
Make sure those giant lips can't ever be pursed again.
Well, yeah, we'll see what happens in California.
I guess let's move to Hollywood Studios,
where they got their own Fantasmic in 1998,
in October 1998.
So I think there was some discussion
with Fantasmic being a huge hit out of the gate
in Disneyland.
Where do we do it in Disney World?
Does it make sense in Magic Kingdom?
Just do it in Rivers of America,
just like we did in Disneyland.
I think it's a smaller Rivers of America there,
a little bit, or it's a lower water table
for various dull reasons.
Even what feels extremely packed in Disneyland,
I think you've got even less.
And soon there will be, of course,
no Rivers of America at all,
unless the price of steel shoots through the rim.
Maybe we'll all thank Mr. Trump
for saving the Rivers of America, accidentally.
Well, the man in the rocking chair on his porch,
it's no telling how he would.
I don't know what that means.
Oh, on the Rivers of America,
they have the little cabin that you see
at the beginning of Pirates of the Caribbean.
In Disneyland, the riverboat goes by him
at some point in Florida.
Oh, just in Florida?
It's the same guy?
I actually didn't realize that.
I don't know if it's exactly the same,
but it looks really similar.
And there's not as many show seats.
Some beat-up merit attractions.
Could be like as a beat-up brother,
like the beat-up old man on the porch
in the rocking chair.
Pirates of Anaheim is siblings with the guy,
and we don't know.
That's interesting.
Yeah, well, as with Sunny Eclipse
and Officer Zizek's in Tokyo,
you consider them siblings or cousins
when mainly the same mold was used
for two characters.
Right, right.
Just like a lot of the pirates
are brothers or cousins
of the presidents of the United States.
Unfortunately, due to the hold
on live-action remakes,
the nasty rocking chair brother universe
is paused right now.
And they were going to get there,
I think, soon enough.
They were going to get there.
That's all they had left.
So it didn't make sense to do it.
Magic Kingdom didn't make sense to do it.
Epcot, because they've always been covered
with nighttime spectaculars.
No Animal Kingdom quite yet,
so Hollywood Studios got landed on.
But of course, you've got your little lake there
with Gertie the Dinosaur and whatever,
but that's not big enough to do Fantasmic.
So they had to figure out,
they had to build a massive complex
in order to do this,
the Hollywood Hills amphitheater.
And if you've never seen it in Hollywood Studios,
that is the deal.
In Disneyland, you have to just kind of like
stake out a spot around the rivers of America
before the very possibly standing room.
In Hollywood Studios, you can sit and watch Fantasmic,
and it is a massive amphitheater
built only for this.
I don't think, okay, I will admit,
I've never been to this in Florida.
I've never seen it in Florida.
So I don't know the venue.
When I saw a video of it
and the camera just looked left to right,
I was like, holy shit.
I knew it was big back there.
But I'd watched videos of the stage,
but I'd never seen how massive that venue is.
It's bigger than the Greek theater.
It's bigger than the Universal amphitheater was.
It's simply massive, entirely for Fantasmic.
I haven't seen it in a long time,
but we saw it early on when it had opened,
I guess in 99 or whatever.
And yes, my memory of it was just like,
whoa, this is a huge thing.
I mean, I guess I wasn't thinking.
I didn't know I was going to be analyzing things
in the future or whatever,
but I do remember feeling like, oh my gosh, this is huge.
It's a little, the scale is a little uncomfortable.
The numbers I saw were 69,
600 seats and then 3000 standing.
Did you say uncomfortable?
Huh?
Did you say the numbers were uncomfortable?
I think he found it uncomfortable
because of the number 69.
That's what I was getting at.
Oh.
Although wait a minute, who are we talking about?
Yeah, yeah.
It's just nearly 10,000 people.
But you say uncomfortable because of the,
it's almost intimidating in size.
It's intimidating in size.
It's a little nauseating to get in and out of, you know.
It's not even stinky there.
It's still nauseating.
It's not stinky there.
Well, depends on how hot it was in Florida that day, friend.
Nights can be very warm.
Yeah, I just, yeah, I probably saw it 98, 99.
And yeah, it was just, I mean,
it's better than just the traffic jam of standing
around the rivers in Disneyland,
where it's just like stanchions and ropes
and cast members with flashlights and it's kind of.
Disneyland is so much cooler
because the show is taking place at the Rivers of America,
but it is kind of a nightmare depending.
Yeah.
But a very wonderful thing
if you're trying to do anything else in the park.
That's true because it sucks all the people over there.
Which I don't know, I'm not at Hollywood Studios
enough to attest if that's true.
Like, does everything else clear out a little bit?
Yeah, I'm sure it does.
I would have to because they're still running this
and there's a reason they're running it
and it's because people go to it.
So I have to imagine there's a little bit.
I just love that they're adding a show
that they typically do two a night,
but maybe three, I don't know if they've already done that,
but that's a ton.
So much, yeah.
If you're going to get 30,000 a night all told.
Yeah, I mean, it is set back far enough
in the way that the Gibson Amphitheater was set back.
That used to be at Universe Hollywood.
You don't really know.
While Phantasm is going on, you just walk up to the tower.
Tower, no problem.
Who knows what the wait time is?
You wouldn't know it's there.
It's not.
I know where it is, but you wouldn't know.
It's a little trail to take it to,
which was the case with Gibson, as I recall.
And there's a theater, another purpose-built theater
for the Beauty and the Beast show
that's been running for ages and ages.
It's for one thing, and it'd be hard to do much else there,
although I'd love to see a regular concert happen
in front of the...
It'd be like a mini Red Rocks.
Like a Copperfield dinner restaurant.
You could enter from the parking lot or Sunset Ball.
Well, there was a time where there was a sign
that advertised both, where coming to Hollywood Studio
or MGM Studios at the time,
and they had equal say on the sign.
One was Phantasmic coming soon.
The other was Copperfield's Magic Underground.
There was a time when this was the future of the park.
Wow.
Yeah, it was advertised outside of it.
What a bummer.
Do you think it'd still be there?
No.
Well, but Disney World is where the restaurants still...
T-Rex Cafe still goes.
No, that's a good point.
Some of the only remaining rainforest cafes.
Planet Hollywood in this bizarre form.
I think there is a world where only, only
Copperfield Magic Underground,
although maybe it was shut down in the last couple years
due to legal travails.
Yeah, no, you make a good point.
I'm still, if I had to bet...
It's gonna survive anywhere.
If I had to bet, I still would say no.
I think Pandemic might have done it in, but...
Yeah.
Well, that definitely put a pause on the original iteration
of the, like, five, six minutes
of the show is Pocahontas action sequences.
Yes, that is finally the hard...
Yeah, Pandemic caused big changes in all of the Phantasmics.
I think it kind of went away at Disneyland.
It went away permanently at Tokyo.
It caused, like, a big reset in Hollywood Studios,
where when it came back, it was different.
That is one for sure.
In terms of, like, how it was gonna be different
by putting it into this Hollywood setting,
they were more concerned with the theme of the park
at this moment in time.
And I think there was some discussion of,
is it just the same show,
and it's this fantasy show that comes from
a Magic Kingdom-style park,
or do we have to acknowledge the Hollywood theme in some way?
And apparently, there was a take and a pitch
of it being more about cinematic moments in Disney history,
which this sounds okay, because I think what was talked about
was a full-sized Nautilus battling a giant squid.
That would have been a part of this.
That does sound pretty good.
I don't have...
I've never seen that entire film, 20,000 Leagues,
but every time, there's something,
like, everything in Tokyo relating to that,
and a great walkthrough in Paris.
Like, this is a thing they've knocked out of the park before.
Nothing gets Tony Baxter more excited than a Nautilus.
He loves the Nautilus so much.
So I feel like that always gets extra care.
Anything Nautilus, Jules Verne-related,
is just, like, really great and still remains really great.
It must have been in the sweet spot
of what people grew up with,
and I think that must have been, like, a jaws of its era,
like, a really next-level or a Star Wars maybe,
in that, like, it's really immersive production design
and, you know, like, transports you more than a, you know,
like, a caper comedy or something up there.
Sure.
Kirk Douglas does some little sea shanties.
It was probably mainly the sea shanties.
It was probably mainly.
I don't think James Mason got involved in the sea shanties.
Too bad, though.
Yeah, it's a shame.
One can dream.
But that, yeah, that didn't come together.
I think that was probably too, like, giant scale even for this,
because this did end up extremely massive in scale.
If you've never seen it in Florida,
where, you know, they were kind of inventing from the ground up
in terms of America already,
you've got, like, a gigantic rock wall,
a mountain, essentially,
that is the backdrop and then still a big body of water
out in front of it.
But something I didn't know, and forgive me,
was this a TPM vids or where had the history on this?
You guys ever heard...
Yesterworld, Yesterworld is the answer.
You guys ever heard this history that,
and this is a clue, like,
that's how we know that this was in the works,
is that there was a soundtrack released for Fantasmic in Florida,
and it had a track that indicates something
that was supposed to happen in the show,
and it was pulled last minute,
and that track was called Mickey Walks on Water.
I guess in this time, when doing Battle with the Dragon,
Mickey would have Christ-like performed a literal miracle.
Mickey would have finally ascended
to what we all know he's capable of,
which is being a cartoon Christ.
Wow. I actually missed this.
Yeah, I had never heard this before.
This is a pretty amazing piece of intel,
and I think the only clue is not the soundtrack.
There's also the people had...
It's either construction photos of when they were building it
or it's footage from when the lake has been drained
in more recent years,
but there is, like, a big plate or something
that is, like, right on the surface of the water
that was meant for that illusion.
Oh, boy.
Yeah, Mickey was going to walk on water,
and then I believe that Eisner himself
requested that this be removed
because he thought, I don't want people to think
that we are saying that Mickey is Christ.
Which I say, lean into it.
It's amazing.
He should have died at the beginning of Fantasmic
and 30 minutes later, risen anew.
That's a rare...
You know I hate to say this, a rare L for Eisner.
Yeah, I know.
It hurts me to say that.
This is in a time where it starts to...
He was getting a little more hit or miss by the late 90s,
and that's a big miss.
I know.
Big miss, and it should have been...
He should have suggested, I want him to walk on water,
but I want it to be when the water is all on fire.
He should have had him walk through the water.
Walk on water and walk on fire.
Walk on fire and water at the same time, yeah.
Flame retardant suit.
Yeah, hopefully.
I'd also like him to turn stone to bread.
Do we have technology for that?
Can we hand...
How many people in the venue?
6,900.
Can we hand each of them a stone?
And when they look down, it has become bread.
How many fish do we have to get per show to feed the audience?
They saw those numbers too.
The numbers didn't crunch.
That didn't make sense, sadly.
Tarzana made a little more money.
Mickey walking that now...
But the show becomes very different.
It's about him being forced to march all the way up to the top of the mountain,
being whipped and spit on by Jafar and Ursula along the way.
At one point, Minnie wipes his face with a towel,
and the image of his face is left in it.
Kind of a full passion play.
He's betrayed by a goofy for 30 cartoon coins.
You know how they could have sold it to Eisner?
They would pass around a collection plate during the show.
You get a lot more money that way.
It would be like paying for itself, essentially, after a couple of times.
People won't even think about where it's going.
That's just what happens.
People are used to hearing this story, and then a basket goes around.
Before you know it, you got quarters, you got dollars, you got hundreds, quite frankly.
Look at all this money from this basket.
All right, collection plates going and everything.
Splash plates on Splash Mountain.
Star Tours.
Rex passes a basket around.
We're going to mail them to people at home.
Listen, the Walt Disney Company is your new god.
I'll be taking questions for Joe, our old layers now.
There's enough land that we're building a place of higher learning
and a place for sports to be played.
It's been a place of worship.
A place of worship of us.
A town needs a place of worship.
They were getting close.
I think if the Disney decade had worked out by 2000, you have the first church of Mickey.
Mickey Church, yeah.
Well, maybe they would have started with more of a humble chapel just to get the ball rolling.
That would be so popular that they would say, all right, now we need a new purpose-built amphitheater.
Mickey's person of the theater.
Starbucks and the Lobby, they eventually got that deal going.
Is there a church being built in Cateno?
How does that work in the Disney?
In a private...
Yeah.
I should ask my parents, my parents who have now been to Cateno.
Right.
Now, I think people...
I posted a tweet that was a screenshot of an interaction I had with my dad.
They were taking a trip down there and he sent a picture of Cateno, mid to half-built,
some random kind of blank spot of it, and said, we're moving to Cateno.
I knew that was a joke, but I don't think all of the audience knew it was a joke.
If you saw that, my family is not officially moving to Cateno yet.
I wouldn't put it past them because they toured model homes.
I guess I got to get my mom and dad on the show, Cateno with Ken and Kathy.
Right.
Because they've seen the model homes now.
They've seen...
There was something that my mom really liked.
She said, I think it's really neat that the whole idea is story living.
She did?
Wow.
Really?
She completely took the bait on that.
Really liked story living and then said, and you know what I like is that the restaurant
in town is called The Plot Twist.
Oh.
My mom likes clever.
She's a teacher.
She likes clever.
You were so clever growing up, and I like clever.
Right.
Isn't that clever?
It's a plot twist.
Wow.
But that similar sort of sales pitch sold my parents on the vacation club.
Uh-huh.
Like touring the samba rooms and buildings and stuff in the mid-dime.
That'll do it.
I guess I got to get the full report.
It was impossible to explain to them the level that Cateno comes up on the show because my
dad said, well, you should do an episode about it.
I'm like, well, it's a runner.
We talk about it a lot.
It's like, oh, so people are excited about it?
No.
I would say it is a runner that people aren't.
And then he's like, but I went down.
It's really nice.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, I don't know.
Hmm.
There's a lot of texture here.
I don't know where to begin.
Yeah.
It's really expensive.
Well, it sounds like it's not out of the realm of possibility.
It seems like they liked it.
I think they did.
Yeah.
It was pretty positive report.
And again, it's like a couple buildings there right now.
Right.
I think it's like a dry lake.
I don't know.
And they like it this much already.
Yeah.
Maybe.
I think I will have to issue a correction in a couple years.
The characters are moving to Katino.
And that means me and the gang too.
I was going to say, yeah.
For all.
If you go.
That's my family forcing me to join.
If we all split them, it's a little much for us.
Yeah.
But if we split it between, you know.
It was meant for two, for retirees.
But we can fit a family of seven and eight here.
I'm moving to the Salton Sea.
I'm buying the dip of that ecological disaster.
It must be a little bit of meat on those old fish bones.
Dry out.
35 years ago.
It supposedly has a very unique stink as well.
Speaking of that.
We're covering all the stinkiest places today.
Yep.
So anyways, we didn't get Nautilus.
And we didn't get, we didn't get Mickey Christ.
Damn.
And it's too bad.
Yeah.
And I've been pitching that as a cartoon for years too.
Like we love to, we buy the old stories.
We just know why we do Cinderella.
Why don't we do Jesus?
And it's me.
It's the part I was born to play.
Look, you see these four wall movies.
They sell out theaters from the church groups.
You see sound of freedom.
Okay.
We're leaving money on the table.
Why is nobody pitching that I bust up a pedophile trafficking ring?
This is what today's action heroes do.
They're saying I'm in charge of what?
I bust through a door.
We can make, we'll keep it fun.
We'll make it ducks.
I bust through a door.
There's 50 ducks in there.
I say, you're coming with me.
And then I shoot a grenade launcher right in the face of the biggest creep.
My sidekick is Percy Jackson and that points people to Disney Plus.
It's, you know, it's a no brainer.
Youthful sidekick.
So, you know, they had to settle.
We all had to settle for just plain old stuff.
The stuff that we know already.
It's projections.
It's moments from our fair movies.
It's I think I forget if I said the phrase in the last episode, but I should have said it barges of love.
We have the barges of love section where the adult contemporary versions of Beauty and the Beast and Whole New World play beautiful slow dances.
So, you know, the show, the Hollywood Studios, Fantasmic doesn't reinvent the wheel, but maybe you don't want it to.
There's a lot of classic things that you want.
It's the song that you want.
You know, it's Mickey shooting fireworks straight out of his arms, which seems to me like Christ could do.
And that shit is hardcore.
There's museums in California.
They have the exploded spark gloves and it's wild.
That is true.
That's a real fact.
That like have blown up.
Where that they've just been used to death.
They're all singed.
Is that right?
Really?
Wow.
Yeah.
I think a museum in Orange County, one of the annual Disney anniversary exhibits.
There's always stuff like that, which is cool.
Will you shoot at Orlando's live shows, will you shoot sparks out of your gloves?
Indoors?
Yes.
That low ceiling?
Yeah.
Straight at the audience.
Yeah, of course.
Okay.
Or Vincent Various when he appears.
I'm not saying any of us necessarily are him.
Shoot him with sparks.
Yeah.
But yeah.
Well, there'll be sparks will fly whether they are literal or figurative.
Yeah.
There's a long history of shooting pyro in small bars and clubs.
It's a long proud history and we'll join it.
Yes, we promise.
Do any of Taffer's Tavern drinks have a little sparkler on it when you order it?
They will for the first nine days and then that will be retired forever.
Because you think there was a chance we could get one of those sparklers and run out to
the venue Tin Roof, which is a couple blocks away from Taffer's Tavern.
I mean, yeah.
I can't think of a better way to get fireworks.
Yeah.
In Orlando?
In Orlando.
I'm assuming the fireworks laws in Florida are, yeah, whatever man, go nice.
I think that's probably right.
If you blow yourself up, that's on you.
Yep.
But let's talk about things that are different in the Florida iteration of Fantasmic besides
just the seating situation.
Because for a while, it is remarkably similar.
And you're like, okay, well, they pretty much brought everything over that we enjoyed about
the previous.
But then there is a part where screen projections, missed projections stop, everything goes dark.
And there's a very dramatic just like junk and a whole scene has been presented and is
already in play on the stage, a scene teeming with dozens of performers, some of whom are
quickly performing stunts.
And what world, what magical Disney realm have we entered with so many great fairy tales
to choose from?
Where have they taken us in the year 2020?
Why, they have brought us to the world of Jamestown.
And of course, all of our favorite characters from Pocahontas, full Pocahontas thing, still
going, what, 25 years after the release of the film?
Something like that.
Well, 95 was Pocahontas, right?
Yeah.
So 30 years later?
Oh, 2020 is yeah.
25.
Yeah, yeah, that's 25 years.
Yeah, the movie comes out in 95, Fantasmic opens in 98.
So that's like a choice to go like, all right, a big chunk of this show is going to be Pocahontas.
We have polled, we've asked around and we sense that there is still as much enthusiasm
about this here in 1998.
And we promise there will be just as much 20 years in the future.
Yeah.
Oh, and people mostly like the English colonizers pillaging the land.
So let's get a lot of that in there.
Well, let's be fair.
It's not as if they, they aren't, this isn't some weird version where they're presented
as the heroes.
Well, I guess John Smith.
John Smith is a hero.
Only, yeah, let's be fair to the movie, Fantasmic.
Only one of them is an awesome swashbuckling hero.
Right.
But one of them is a horrible villain.
And that is, that is Radcliffe who resembles, I believe resembles John Taffer if you take
his colonial stuff off.
I think it's funny.
Taffer definitely could come in and plus up the American colonies for sure.
If he got right off the boat.
I don't want to go into the bit.
I'm just saying.
Get all this out of here.
All of it.
I mean all of it.
I need more lights.
Lighting everything from underneath.
That'll make this place sing.
This might take a, what does he call America?
John Taffer is going to rebrand, in this or any era.
Yeah, yeah, in the original.
Yeah.
So just like, like we're calling it sports world.
What's the number one?
What's the most popular thing in this country?
Sports.
How are we going to tell people?
We're called, America has been rebranded.
All right.
Everyone in America turn around.
Count to three.
Three, two, one.
Whoa.
That's right.
It's now the touchdown.
His home run coast.
You can see all this water from here.
Home run coast.
Home run coast is almost bet too good.
Yeah.
But it's close.
I really like it though.
Yeah.
That's one of the areas.
Like we have several nooks in this country.
Gun Plaza.
Every colony now has a gun plaza.
Yelling and everybody throwing tea in the harbor.
That tea is expensive.
You're wasting tea.
And for what?
To make a point?
A political point?
We don't want this place to be political.
It's going to drive people away.
I had Tea Tender come in and weigh all of your tea supplies.
And it shows how much tea you've gone.
We're measuring the tea in the harbor.
You're a lifetime subscription to Tea Tender.
It's over $2,000 worth of tea gone.
What are they calling it?
The Boston Tea Party?
This is a party to you?
You think this is fun?
Wasting money is not my idea of fun.
And it shouldn't be yours.
Shut it down.
We shut the harbor down.
Why do you keep laughing?
You laugh every time I say it.
That was what I saw.
I saw a music venue yesterday.
I saw an episode.
And the guy has a nervous t-
Like the owner has like a pork pie hat.
He goes, haha.
Like after every time someone says something,
I'm like, you are a terrible owner.
And he's like, haha.
I relate to this.
I've been a nervous laugher my whole life.
I relate to half of this guy.
The nervous laugher, yes.
The pork pie hat, no.
I've never been a pork pie hat guy.
You're not a little pork pie hat boy.
There's still time.
Not yet a little pork pie hat.
A little stinky pork pie hat.
Naughty little pork pie hat.
There we go.
We're looking for more words.
That's going to do it.
I'm teetering.
All right.
Hearts, hearts, hearts.
Energy, energy.
So I do think it's funny that Radcliffe is portrayed
by a big, like he has a big plastic face.
He's a mascot.
Yeah, yeah.
And then everyone else in the scene
is just a face character.
Yeah.
Everybody else is a regular human.
Except for him.
I mentioned that, Jayden and I were watching this.
I mentioned, she's like, well, you got to think like Jafar,
they kind of have expressive cartoony faces.
Sure.
So having to see it from a distance,
they probably didn't want to have just an actor do it.
But it's very funny, the Jamestown miners, sailors,
there was one point where I had to rewind it
because it just looked like a guy in a camp shirt
or Hawaiian shirt and jean shorts
handed Radcliffe something.
And she's like, oh, no, that's not a crew guy.
Oh.
Huh.
It was just kind of clothes at some point.
They were just kind of wearing warmer weather-like clothes.
Yeah, gotcha.
Except for Radcliffe, who's wearing like 80 pounds of plastic.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Constricted vision, all of those heads
have got to be tough and fantastic, wherever you are,
whether you're in the boat, whatever it is.
The one thing that you really, I'm like,
watching this, I never watched the full Pocahontas sequence.
But as canoes start going by,
you have to do some math of the sheer volume in 25 years,
no, wait, it was open in 98, that's for the movie,
so a little over 20 years,
the sheer volume of whites playing Native Americans
every single night in this production.
Oh, yeah.
Putting on wigs in order to, I assume,
I assume that it was kind of like, who's around?
You get in there, put it on.
Yeah, 1998 rules apply.
Far away rules apply.
Yeah, yeah, so in two performances a night
for 22 years, this might be the most,
the highest degree of problematic.
More than old Hollywood in general?
In any lake, I'll at least go with lakes.
I think that makes this the most problematic lake honor.
Oh, yeah, I never thought about lakes.
It's like high schools in the Midwest
doing like white Hamilton, like all white.
What you have just flashed me to
is my Catholic high school's
very unfortunate production of Flower Drum Song.
Yeah.
I would like to say no more about this production.
No more, goodness.
I think there's been many productions,
I think the regular,
I think the feature film Flower Drum Song has its problems.
Yeah.
I'm gonna take a wild swing.
Same thing with Miss Saigon,
same thing even with like half of Weston's story.
Oh, no.
That's true.
Our poor high schoolers,
they were just following orders.
They just wanted to shine on stage.
That's the phrase you need to use.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That absolves everyone of everything.
But jumping ahead to the newer version,
there is a little Pocahontas,
and Pocahontas singing
Just Around the Riverbank?
Just Around the Riverbank.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Which doesn't happen in this.
There's a lot of quick hits in the new one.
This is just like the full war.
This is just like, right, it's the,
again, this is about Mickey's imagination
and what can he imagine.
No, he can imagine anything.
In fact, it gets out of control from how much he imagined.
What are you gonna imagine tonight, Mickey?
I've just been thinking about the colonization of Jamestown.
You know, it's just some unfortunate politics at play
if you think about what this nation was built on.
We all gotta reflect on that sometimes.
I think we should reflect on it
for at least 10 minutes of my imagination.
That could be a stunt or two,
but I want you to reflect.
I think we should do a while on that town,
Croatoa, that just disappeared in the colonies overnight.
Pretty weird.
Think about it.
Walter Knob was really on the right track
with a lot of his teachable things
and his learning center.
This thing we didn't do.
I'm choking, sorry.
I'm just eating while I'm talking here.
That's a big meal.
I do meals and meetings at the same time.
I have to do it, sorry.
Mickey, put the club sandwich down.
There's a pool ball.
You can't have both.
I just think what you gotta do is you gotta teach your kids
what they're different.
You gotta teach them about the laws.
You're foaming at the...
You gotta teach them.
You gotta teach the kids.
Do I have to choke you?
You have to choke me out.
Not unchoke you.
Oh, sorry.
I got confused.
There's a lady coming to choke me later today.
That's a different thing.
Okay, that's a different...
You don't want the food for that.
Well, gosh, Mickey, if you keep going like this,
you're gonna burn out.
Yeah, I know I am.
But that's why Miss Stern comes over later
to calm me down.
I already hit the Jesus age of 34 now.
I didn't think I'd live to see this.
I'll tell you.
Everything else is just gravy.
I asked the question to the listeners,
or I actually asked it to you,
what it was called when you pay a woman
to step on your balls with a high-heeled shoe.
And many people on Patreon told us
it's called cock and ball torture.
Cock and ball torture.
So I'm talking about I get a lady come over,
do cock and ball torture on me later,
calms me down, got a high-stress job, you understand.
Sorry to be so vulgar, but it is what it is.
I think Jesus died at 32 or 33,
so I'm actually winning,
and that's why I should walk on water.
Yeah, I'm winning.
I'm for sure winning.
I say winning.
Remember that.
He was right.
Jesus did not live to get to do
a lot of cock and ball torture.
It's not in the Bible, but, you know,
I'm adding to it.
I'm making...
I'm sort of taking the legend
and running with it.
That's the whole thing.
I'm choked again.
I'm doing it.
Sorry.
Big piece of bacon, you know.
Sometimes you get that stuck in your throat.
This is bacon from the store.
You didn't kill the three little pigs.
No, I killed the three little pigs.
You did kill the...
Oh, God.
Sorry, I'm losing it again.
Yeah, I killed them for sport.
The sandwiches from the commissar.
It's the only goddamn edible thing in that trash can.
You killed them and you didn't...
You weren't even...
Like, you didn't even use every part of the book.
I used it for sport.
It doesn't count as using it, sport.
That's fun, essentially.
Oh, it was a warning.
So, you get some stunts in here.
John Smith swings on a rope.
Yeah.
There were, I think, a lot...
I think a common phantasmag mishap
is John Smith missing on the rope.
Oh, man.
That would happen from time to time.
I don't think he totally waked out or anything.
Yeah, it's not so weird.
This is the TPM vids.
TPM vids condensed a lot of the different fails
that have occurred over the years,
one of which being that he used to swing very wide
onto a little set of steps,
and pretty easy to miss, and he would,
but then he'd just kind of have to hang
and wait for the lights to black out,
and then he'd just sneak away
and pretend like it didn't happen.
There's so many people, there's canoes,
there's canoes with flames,
there's people who have, you know,
there's stunt performers,
and it all just made me go like,
okay, there's another thing.
In 22 years, how much money was spent
by the Disney company on performances of,
on this little Pocahontas play
that would occur on just the Pocahontas segment?
Like, how much, what's the line item
right pre-pandemic for just what does Pocahontas cost?
Right.
How many performers in there?
Did you figure out a number?
They're all running around,
I couldn't count them.
What do we think?
20?
At least 20.
Yeah, 20-ish or so.
Then canoes get in the mix.
At least 30.
30.
Disney is mounting an expensive Pocahontas
each and every night until COVID-19 shuts off.
Well, stuff all costs more than I think,
so I'm gonna estimate roughly it costs per night
to do the Pocahontas scene, it costs $200 million.
Just $200 million every single night.
A blockbuster movie every night.
Oh my God.
I bet it's at least, what do you think,
$25,000 for the Pocahontas scene?
It could be, yeah, I think so.
Yeah.
Yeah, nightly, yeah.
Maybe.
Because how many of those actors
can pull double duty at the end?
Oh, that's true.
Changing and then running to a quote unquote boat.
But can, is that enough time?
I don't know if it's safe.
Yeah, yeah, and then like,
and we're talking about elaborate costumes.
Can you put on a baloo right after that?
Right, right.
Can you tear off a problematic wig
and then get into a bear suit?
How fast can you do that?
Right.
I don't know.
Good question.
It just was, it's so funny
that this was going for so long,
and it kind of takes the slot
where of like Peter Pan and pirates
and pirates swinging on ropes in the pre,
and while I'm always happy to see Peter Pan
get replaced by anything, by anything,
this still remains, it's very strange
that this is what this real estate went to.
During like the one bubble sequence,
were you happy to see like Jiminy Cricket
almost drowned in a bubble or Monstro show up?
Like, are those the parts of Pinocchio
you like the best?
Oh, in the movies.
In chaos.
I am okay with, I have no issue
with any of Jiminy Cricket,
but I also don't root for his demise.
Okay.
Not quite.
And even the regular Disney Pinocchio
doesn't bother me as much as certainly
every single frame of the live action,
and then almost everything in which
like an adult has played Pinocchio.
Yeah.
In little shorts.
That's really where you get into trouble.
Even in fairy tale theater,
I think Paul Rubens did it.
I'm, you know, tempted to like
kind of anything Paul Rubens did,
but that, not so much.
I mean, I'm sure that's a very enjoyable piece,
but if I'm going to watch a fairy tale theater,
I'm going to watch Jeff Goldblum as the wolf.
Yeah.
If you've ever seen that one.
That's a strong piece.
Right, right.
Anyways, yeah.
Do you see, let me ask,
because I watched a few versions of each one.
Do you see Pocahontas during the Pocahontas sequence?
I think you do.
I think they both kind of climb the mountain
and then kind of look longingly at each other
from across the mountain.
By the way, John Smith's voice also
is somebody who is going to save Hollywood.
That's what I, yeah.
And made a Jesus couple,
well, it's going to be an occasion.
Yeah.
We should sign him up.
He should do the animated version too,
while he's at it.
May as well.
Who knows the beats?
I saw Passion of the Christ my freshman year
in college.
And I didn't know what Passion plays were.
And I went to like a comedy club rehearsal
right after that.
And a few of us just walked in like,
oh my God.
You thought it was going to be like a fun romp of a movie?
No, I didn't think it was going to be a fun romp.
I thought it was going to be a little more of a biopic.
Like the soap opera Passion.
So you just didn't know he gets the shit kicked out of him.
I didn't know he gets the shit kicked out of him.
There was like no English language.
And there was like hardly any dialogue.
I see.
No, that's the point of it,
is to get children to watch the bloodiest shit you've ever seen.
Right.
It actually, weirdly,
it's funny that Mickey was going to walk on water in this venue
because with The Big Rock,
it kind of does look like a high end version of a set
that could be used at like the Holy Land experience
for a daily Passion play.
That's true.
If Disney ever, you know,
if John Smith's voice and Maleficent's dad get their wish
and Disney's Hollywood studio is taken over,
is invaded, all the current smut is taken away.
And maybe this could, this would be, I think,
where the Passion play goes.
Yeah, I think that makes a lot of sense.
Yeah, I think we're going to see it.
Well, you'll be seeing it very strongly.
Nope, we're getting Percy Jackson
and the Mysterious Benedict Society.
And so, like all your favorite Disney Plus properties.
Are they talking about doing a lot of Percy?
No.
Percy Jackson has done, it is pretty popular, I believe.
Yeah, yeah.
So anyways, the biggest difference for sure is this,
and this is no longer the case.
What has this been replaced by?
Now it's more of a like, you know,
lots of characters get a chance to shine
instead of a mean governor.
It's a lot of quick hits of like, there is like,
there's a cool Mulan sequence with the song,
one of the songs, and Bo Staff fighting.
And then Pocahontas does a sequence.
There's a cool Moana running,
interacting with the water and stuff.
She's like making it, well, does she make it?
She's just sort of like, yeah.
She kind of like makes one go up.
I thought I had seen a version where she,
it looks like she's walking on water,
and then water is flying after her,
but then I couldn't find any video of that.
Oh, okay.
Maybe that's just a dream you had.
A dream or a-
A premonition?
Well, I was going to say,
I might have watched videos where it's in B mode
and not doing that.
Oh, maybe.
Because there are show B modes.
Oh, sure.
Yes.
Okay, well that makes sense.
I think that is a good change that has transpired
since the COVID reset.
One pretty neat plus up, I think,
about this whole thing is the addition of the Jafar snake.
I know, the snake is awesome.
That is cool as hell.
So it's similar to Ka.
There's a Ka in the Disneyland one
with the big spotlight eyes.
Right.
But it's a little more, I think this is scarier,
and I think it's, and just Jafar snake,
great sequence in the movie, great in the video game,
it's all great.
And the spotlight eyes are following Mickey
and chasing him around.
Right.
Is very cool.
It reminds me of like,
I'm trying to think if there's a,
I don't know if it's like,
there's like a snake game,
either like a board game or like old snake toys
that this snake reminds me of.
I don't know if I'm also kind of thinking
of Hungry Hungry Hippos.
It's like fragmented.
As well, like the Hungry Hungry Hippo neck.
Or the old cell phone game,
where you have to like-
Yeah, maybe that's what I'm thinking of.
You have to slice a snake up
and make him go into smaller and smaller pieces.
Yeah.
I believe we had the snakes and ladders.
Maybe that's what I'm thinking of.
It's just chutes and ladders,
just a different thing you go down.
But there's snakes involved.
You like segmented snakes.
Yeah, I do.
I like that they're all little like,
that it's, this feels like a school play
in a charming way,
where you see little people's legs,
like they don't hide from it.
It's theatrical, that's fine,
you know what's going on.
But it's, you know,
it's like,
like a Chinese dragon,
it's cool.
There's the jointed,
yeah, these like,
jointed snake toys.
Oh, the wooden ones
that you waggled around?
I don't know if you can see that,
yeah.
Yeah.
But those, yeah,
those are kind of what they seem,
it's like a big toy.
Like a giant toy.
It's cool, it's great.
Yeah.
You,
and then you get
just pure dragon finale in this,
which works very well.
This backdrop is really great for it.
Like everybody's got better vision on it
because of the amphora.
Yeah.
And I mean,
I watched a fireball hit
that was just like,
bonkers how good it was.
Like,
shot right out of the mouth
onto something else
that generated a bunch more flames.
Like,
like hit a spot
that caused a bigger explosion.
Yeah.
Just that,
that level of precision
is so crazy,
and the finale's
as good as it ever,
is Disneyland.
Yeah.
And then you get,
I think a,
I don't know,
like,
and then you get,
I think a,
it felt to me
like a longer montage
projected on a mist
of every villain dying.
Again,
a kind of crazy thing
that children watch every day
is just the screams of agony
of all the,
you know,
including recently referenced
on the show,
Claude Frollo.
Of course.
To see Frollo's anguish.
Children today
still watching Frollo's screams.
Watching Cardinal Suffer.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
But he's got,
but what they,
what you don't know
because it's a close-up
is that he's got a boner
while he's doing it.
It's every,
all anguish turned Frollo on.
Yeah, man.
Frollo and I are in the same
wave of life.
Even when you feel anguish,
you also get a boner.
Yeah.
It just gets mixed up in there
early on in your childhood,
and I don't know.
Just, you gotta,
you gotta figure it out.
I messed up in the head.
What can I say?
SMF and I were partying
at Coachella,
you know,
with Jelly Roll
and like fucking
Post Malone.
Then we got the next morning.
He's already gone
from the rental house.
Apparently the Pope died.
He's gotta go do
a conclave bullshit.
He didn't, he didn't.
Wait, did Jelly Roll
led to leave?
No, Claude Frollo.
Oh, Frollo.
Sorry, sorry.
I got confused.
Jelly Roll's got nothing to do
compared to Claude Frollo.
Jelly Roll.
Um.
You know what?
Frollo says,
YOLO.
In Winston-Ally,
that's how he rolls.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
You only live once,
so you know,
torture your cock and balls
as much as you want.
He's a Venmo me
as usual.
He forgot.
Bullshit.
That's how he is though.
I've come to accept that.
I know you got Nazi gold
in that cathedral
you piece of shit.
He got more than me though.
I don't think so.
This company was built
on Nazi gold.
That's right.
Lenny Ravenstahl
came to Burbank.
She would think
she came at the end.
She wanted that tour
and she was paying for it.
Nazis built Tomorrowland.
Come on.
We know.
There's gold under there.
Finale, Phantasmic,
you end up with,
you know,
they need to recreate
the Disneyland version,
which happens on the Mark Twain.
There's already been a ship
there for many, many years
and the Finale was built
with that in mind.
They can't just move
the whole ship
from Magic Kingdom
over to that,
you know,
over to that
and that's still in use.
It's different parks.
So they had to create
a new ship
from the ground up.
I have to admit
that I'd never put together
that the ship
is supposed to be
like Steamboat Willie's ship
and which is why
it's like a little bit cartoony
and like a little bulbous
because in my head
I would always,
and by any measure
I will say
this ship is like
an incredible set piece
for a theatrical presentation,
but compared to the Mark Twain,
it is a little bit like,
what's this dinky ship?
What's this dinky ship?
Is that insane?
It's like a PlayStation 1 polygon.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
Somebody posted a gif of like,
man,
I miss the simplicity
of the triangular,
the pointed seagulls.
Like it was just the seagulls
in video games.
Oh yeah.
It was just kind of like
a simple flapping thing
in the distance.
And that is what this boat wrote.
It's just very gray.
Yeah, yes.
It doesn't hold a candle
to the Mark Twain.
Mark Twain,
very beautiful,
but when fantastic's winning,
you can't do nighttime Mark Twain.
Oh, so you're happy
that by this being a different park,
it doesn't step on anyone's
riverboat enjoyment.
So you sign off on that.
That's true.
Well, and the other thing
I alluded to earlier in the show,
the funny,
the other funny fail in this
is that like,
as the riverboat rounds the bend
and everyone goes inside
to get away from fireworks and sparks.
The many, the dozens
of costume characters.
The many costume characters
all scurry away.
Scurry away,
but Ariel is sitting on a rock.
So Prince Eric throws
a flame retardant bag on her
and she kind of looks like
the hat man,
the nightmare that people have
if they took too much Benadryl
or the woman in the yard.
It's very woman in the yard-esque.
I'm wondering if there's any children
who like were looking around
at this show and then just saw
like pitch black Ariel
and we're like, huh, huh, huh.
Yeah, it's really,
and if you've like forgot
that that's where Ariel was,
then it just seems like why
is there suddenly a cloaked figure?
Yeah.
A lone cloaked figure
haunting the end of the show.
It's so sad.
Slumped off the edge of this boat
and like the,
with kind of like
Charlie Brown limp away posture.
It is so sad.
Poor Ariel,
who we want nothing more
than for Ariel's dreams to come true.
And then in this situation,
a black bag is thrown on her.
She gets half kidnapped
at the end of the show.
But then like,
but then it's like,
oh shit, the cops run.
And then they,
they like just leave her,
whatever,
leave the girl.
It's great.
She's got plausible deniability.
Yeah, it is very,
I mean, it's safe.
Like it,
it works,
but it is sort of like,
we could just put her in her dress
from the end of the movie.
Yes.
Yeah, really.
Yeah.
Why does she have to be in a fin?
That doesn't,
and what if it didn't?
What if you then one night
perfectly watched
just a green little sparkle
fly all the way from the sky
onto that bag
where it catches on fire
and you know that Ariel is in there
and you know that Ariel's hair
can't be made of anything
that goes well with fire.
No hair does,
but especially not wig hair.
It's grandfathered in asbestos.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes, the costume was built in a time
where this was approved.
Yeah.
Yeah, it would just be,
yeah,
praying for the safety
of any Ariel out there.
That is one of the funniest little,
I'm sure they've been doing that for decades.
That's where you got to think
like how much Disney fan culture
is out there
that like nobody,
like guess what I noticed?
Guess what I can make go viral?
Ariel's bag.
There's the Pruder film level details
from any angle on any of these shows
which is what made it the craziest thing
to catch on fire.
Something else that I clocked
in watching this video,
so I watched the performance
as late as you could go
before everything shut down
which was in January 2020
and I'm watching all these characters
run around the steamboat willy,
the SS willy or whatever at the end
and it's a lot of perennials obviously.
It's Geppetto and Pinocchio
and Prince Eric and the classics
and the seven dwarves and whatever.
And then in the group is Brer Bear
and just knowing the fate
that was coming to Brer Bear
not too long after that,
what I was picturing was the end of the show
and all the characters are like,
they're all like landing after
and he's talking to him like,
oh boy, another successful performance, eh?
Oh boy, boy gang, you know,
night after night,
you'd think it would get old
but it never does.
You know, you guys,
I just want to say you're my best friends
and I think this is going to be a great year
and I think that we're going to,
I think we're going to have
so many performances of Fantastic
and I'm going to be right there with all of you forever.
But then two months later,
he got really sick
and got put on a ventilator.
That's what you were getting at.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That and only that.
Yeah.
You know, come by Splash Mountain tonight.
If you want, come hang out with me.
You guys are welcome there anytime
from now, whether it's now
or 30 years from now.
You're always,
there's a spot with your name on it.
You know, when Splash opened,
we were worried this wasn't going to last
but now I'm sure.
I'm going to be here forever.
That's what I know.
Which is even like the honor of being with you,
with you guys that like,
to be here with Little Mermaid
and with Aladdin
lets me know that I'm one of the Disney greats.
So we're always,
just to be in this company.
I'm like nerding out right now.
Raise your champagne flutes.
That includes you, Jamestown gang.
We're never going to die.
All of us.
Yes, forever.
We're going to live forever.
Looking at you, Gene Schwartz.
We're in what I like to call the big 30,
the top 30 Disney characters.
It's a Mount Rushmore
that will never ever be questioned.
I'm 22.
Radcliffe, what is his name?
It's not Radigan.
I kept saying that.
Radigan's from Great Mouse Detective.
I wish Radigan was in here.
He's 23.
Radcliffe.
And you've got the Siamese cats are 21 and 22.
Did you ever see them in these?
I don't wonder why.
I heard the jumps to that song
but I haven't heard the cats in a while.
By the way, yes, this is how I talk.
This is my voice.
I think we can all agree on this.
It just gets better and better
and the more you hear it.
Well, here's to a happy 2020 for all of us,
especially me, and a happy eternity too.
And happy birthday, Roseanne Cowell
from home on the range.
You're going to live on streaming
for a long, long, long time.
I've been streaming for a long time.
Favorite Disney character, number 29
of the top 30.
Hopper, can't forget you, Hopper.
Number 30.
Hopper's 30.
The other thing I've a lot of alluded to
early in the thing, the biggest fail,
the worst thing that ever happened
to the point about this boat
while being technically very impressive
on most scales, but also
you got to throw a bag on her
and it kind of looks like Weird and Ricky.
And then one awful night, Dopey
is running around on the second level.
His foot slips.
I don't know, like stupid Dopey.
His foot just happened to go
in the massive chasm that any of the characters
with limited eyesight could have
on any night for 20 years
just easily kicked their way.
Just if you haven't seen the video,
Dopey slips and falls and lands
on top of Goofy.
It is, for an incident that apparently
did not terribly injure either of them,
thank God, it looks so bad.
It looks rough.
It looks so bad for both of them.
Really bad. They don't go in the water?
No, nobody lands in the water.
Thank God.
Landing on Goofy is not a good scenario,
but it does feel like Dopey is only
a foot away from landing in the water
and that can't be good either.
Now you have to rescue a character
in a head from water.
It's a miracle that doesn't happen
more often in these places.
And that was Orlando or Anaheim that happened?
That was Orlando.
Because this kind of shit wouldn't fly
in your beloved Mark Twain.
They thought about this, it was built to last,
it was built like proper railings
so that real children who go on that thing
don't go flying off,
built with care.
It's not a PlayStation 1 Spyro the Dragon boat.
Yes, plenty of polygons
on the Mark Twain from the get-go.
I wish they built,
I mean the different characters
wouldn't fit on the actual way
Steamboat Willie the boat looks.
But I wish it looked more like
Steamboat Willie somehow.
I know what they were going for.
I almost had not thought that,
it's like a kind of cartoon
cheapening out or something
that doesn't really...
The boat looks like shit
in Steamboat Willie.
But it doesn't, I don't know.
It could look more like that.
You would have been the highest caliber
of snob if you said that in 1928.
That's true.
Can you believe it? A cartoon talked.
What do you think, Michael?
Boat looks like shit.
Never mind, this thing is going to be a failure.
More harassment for the Fleischer fool.
I was a plant.
So, lots of funny
incidents, lots of funny strange
programming, I think a lot of
fun separate culture
of the Florida one.
Which I still
have to be honest, I will never take the
time to see this, it's not happening.
Either coast.
I've seen it in California.
But you'll never go to Orlando and see it.
I think I'm just not, I don't know.
But with kids?
That's the difference.
But in this current era, where I
have kids, but I keep going to Disney
World without them.
That's what I'm also in a situation.
I bring her too, but
often.
Getting in and out of this
amphitheater with kids.
That's just chaos.
Nightmare that not even
Mickey could conjure.
I like to see
my parents, so I would walk behind.
Other kids would run ahead.
If you're a parent, neither
is ideal.
I guess ahead you can see them.
But like, my parents
really, I feel like that
was a thing I'm remembering.
I was like, I'll walk behind you
so I can see. They're like, no, we
were fine. We need to see
you.
Because just following behind
your dad, or you think is your dad,
that's how Home Alone 2 happened.
That's right. Very good point.
Don't just trust the regular looking
guys backside.
Important point. You get home
alones, and then you have to go meet Trump in the
lobby.
Let's talk Tokyo for a minute here.
Did you see it in Tokyo?
I saw part of it in Tokyo.
We planned it and watched the whole
thing. The kind of leisurely thing that
yes, can happen when you have enough
days to do so.
I will admit this.
We didn't
plan on it.
I kind of loathe to see these things sometimes
because I don't want to take the time to pick out a spot.
But we were walking by and we were just like,
this is a good spot. We're fine. We got one.
This is great. Because that harbor,
we've obviously raved about Tokyo
Disney Sea a lot.
There's so much to rave about, you almost don't take the time
to say what you enter to.
It's unbelievable. And then you don't get tired of it.
Because you have to circle back that way
so many times throughout the day.
The Mediterranean harbor at the entrance
is so spectacular.
All of the lagoon shows they do
make incredible use of it.
And it looks, it's so
calming and gentle there
at night. There's such a feeling.
Like we were just outside
some random restaurant and I think at that time
not yet completed
Sorin Fantastic Flight.
And a really magical area
for it being just a restaurant and construction walls.
It was a great place to see the show.
I reminded myself the videos
I took of it where, oh my god,
it's the finale of Fantasmic.
But also, I go
that way and there's the volcano.
And lava's coming out as we speak. And then there's that
incredible Tower of Terror.
You can see the ship in the background.
Ugh, got that Tokyo.
Got that Tokyo Jones going again
as strong as always.
The fact that the backdrop for it
is Tokyo Disney Sea
really elevates it.
And it's massive.
I mean Tokyo Disney Sea is that lagoon
or whatever is massive. And it feels like
I mean there were people that were definitely
whenever we were there were crammed
against the whatever
railings to see it. But there's plenty
of places you can casually stand
and watch. It's not like
Disneyland. Yeah, I didn't feel like
constricted. I had plenty of breathing room.
We saw the Halloween show
during the daytime on the water as well.
With the different little barges
like Halloween barges which was fun.
There's such barge pros in Tokyo.
So it is
and we didn't watch. I forget why
we didn't watch all of it. I think maybe we
happened upon it leaving something
and then we watched five or ten minutes. I think I have
some video somewhere of it. But
just getting to sit by the
lagoon at night with lights.
That's really all you need. So anything above that
is gravy.
Content wise.
Pretty similar to the domestic phantasmics
would you say? It's sort of
not actually. It's not radically
different and it's the same structure.
But I mean it's
just so different to look at.
While you have the backdrop of
the volcano you can't put Mickey on there.
So he's on this kind of
like bedazzled
mountain that rolls out into the center.
He's on like a screen. He's on a big
screen cone.
It's a big screen cone. It's almost like a cake
of some kind in some ways.
Yes. It does kind of look delicious
despite it being a bunch of LEDs.
It's pretty jazzy.
It's pretty snazzy. It looks very cool.
They play clips off of there
and then sometimes it's just abstract when
he's fighting the dragon. The dragon
rises out of a big mirror
which
rolls out like the darkness.
It's incredible that they're able to do like the
seamless transitions in the dark.
Everything's right in front of you obviously.
But they keep it still very theatrical in its
lighting to where like whoa that's the
dragon float. And none of it's
out there. Right. As opposed to Phantasmac where they
got to shut or sorry in Disneyland
where they have to shut down Times
Island way early and get everything ready for show
mode. This seems like it just kind of
starts. It's what? Right.
It has to just be a lagoon during the day and they're probably
running some other show. It feels like
you're seeing Phantasmac
on Lake Michigan or something.
Yeah. Totally.
It feels so hidden.
I mean I'm sure if I went back because I
haven't spent as much time in DisneySea as I have in Disneyland
but you can definitely see even like all right they're getting
ready for Phantasmac. Here's all the different
stuff. Yeah. The stuff around the
like railings, lagoons, stuff
like lights and whatever. Yeah.
But like yeah it feels a lot of it feels
invisible. Yeah. Until
the show starts. Which is incredible that then it starts and then you end up
with like there is so much
fire on that lake. So much
fire. I think yeah there's
more fire in this than any of these shows.
Yeah I think it's. Fire is in all the shows.
I think there's at least fire in Disneyland
more in Orlando and then it feels like the most
is in Tokyo. Yeah. But I mean maybe
that's not true. Maybe that's my feeling.
We're getting a lot of the Midwest today
from Lake Michigan,
Gary, Indiana. Oh yeah I'm just bringing
it up you're saying. Not my accent. White Hamilton.
All the greatest
Midwest institutions.
Yeah. The greatest accomplishments
landmarks and exports. Right.
The best White Hamiltons
you ever seen.
So I mean like
I could talk about
parts of it but it mainly it's I mean
it's all going to as a lot of Tokyo things boil down
to it's just like you guys it's
so fucking cool. And then this
thing happens and it's so cool.
All this stuff is like like then there's like a
big Pumba balloon a big balloon
and it's so cool. And
I just like it made me I was so happy
I mean I was obviously happy all day
every day there. But
I watched a video I was like what are we doing right
after and we were walking out just all
it just crowds are dissipating and we seems
to go straight from there to our third
time of the day on Journey to the Center of the Earth.
Oh yeah. And we are
it's the it's the exit music
specifically if you look at it it's what I love as it's
classified on Spotify is the fantastic
exit music which is where it gets
like there's no more it's all instrumental and
it's just synthy at that point so I love it.
And we are it's
it's a track that means so much to Aaron and I both
from from childhood and have this
thing that like we remember from being nine years old
and now we're hearing it across the globe
in this new magical setting
that's far beyond what you thought
any Disney park could do.
We're just so we're just like giggling
weird like we have shit eating
grins we're so happy.
It like yeah
what can I say I
you know go go check it out next time
you're there. Oh wait you can't
yeah I don't know what happened I don't know why they got rid
of it. That's a good question I don't know either.
It's it's I thought it was like
triumphant I thought it was so great.
Have they are they doing any other show?
There has to be something planned right?
Because all of those shows are unbelievable
you saw Halloween one I saw the Easter one.
I've never stopped thinking about it.
Like so huge and grand.
Incredible costumes
for them. I didn't see a replacement.
The costumes that you see incredibly far away.
You know what's another we love our
Eisner stuff obviously you guys ever seen that footage
of like it's the opening ceremony of
Disney Sea and that it's him and Roy
and somebody else like be like be like
trotting out like being driven
out on a big barge. I don't think I have seen that.
It's pretty cool with Mickey
looking like Magellan or something.
Mickey is like it's like from the past
and future Mickey.
Wow. This is a
vibe yeah because it just
looks like he's speeding on a pontoon or something.
Just looks like yeah
Eisner swamp style.
Eisner going swamp
mode.
There's there has to be
more Eisner in Tokyo
footage like around
this time. Probably I don't associate
with I bet he didn't go terribly.
I guess that's probably and I don't associate Disney
Sea with him because around that time and the rest
of the parks he was building a bunch of cheap
shit. Right. But so it's like weird
that he's even parted like oh you did this.
Right. I guess technically you did
this. Technically stitch
is in this. You get some yeah
you get some like like a stupid
rock instrumental version of Hawaiian
coaster ride.
And
I don't know.
That's fun. It's as fun as Stitch being
glommed on to the Tiki Room which is what happens
there. A bunch of
big globes and orbs.
You know it's a good
dragon. So many but
I am not too
specific here. I'm just
putting I'm saying all these keywords and I'm putting
exclamation points behind them just like
the word phantasmic itself.
Mickey has like a light up
robe more like it's cooler.
Yes. Yes. Yeah. He's in a Technicolor
dream code. Yes. Very. Oh yeah.
You're right. He loved his
coat of many colors. That's right.
A lot of great
high school productions of that too. Yeah.
There's it's if there's not
one really good like one talented mom
at that school that writing to her
dream code is going to be
going to be a real bomb. That I feel like
that Jesus Christ superstar
Godspell. That was
in the 90s. That was the religion
you could have schools without
lawsuits. This was that's true.
Now in Trump's America those are the only shows that you
can do. Of course. Yeah. Although even
not so like I don't I don't care for any of that hippie
music though. Age of
Aquarius. We're getting rid of
it. The age of Americus.
We're not doing hair.
I have the best hair. That's the only
hair you need to concern yourself.
We don't need to learn about any other hair.
We don't need to do hair. I also
for some reason in this show they just
say the word imagination way more.
In any spare space in the song that
was just instrumental before now they say
imagination. And then in the end he doesn't say
some imagination huh. He says
imagination ha ha.
That's how he ends it.
They just I don't know it's as if they were like
this needs to cut through all
language. You have to you cannot
there's a minimum you must say imagination
a hundred and twenty times in the show.
We cannot green light it.
The smoldering volcano just
in the background adding
ambiance to
incredible.
I would like to see
Mickey pop out of it. Yes I
that is yes if they get over the dragon comes out
of it. Yes.
Something they could do there
but really they don't need to.
I mean it smolders it erupts normal
times as well. They should do like a
gag like Mickey goes in a barrel
and a barge and pops up the volcano.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Or just pops all over and then he's on top of the
tower of terror he's everywhere.
Volcano Bay's volcano also erupts.
We haven't really talked about enough fake
volcano eruptions I don't think on the show.
But I'm a big fan
of the volcano and
volcano bay. Yeah. Is this a path
to yet another episode about
Margaritaville. Well
it could be. I mean now that you say it.
I mean maybe you say is the
water park H2O. Is that around?
We should check in on it.
It can't be in good shape. It is
still around but it's not a water
theme park like volcano.
Yeah it's true. Well this
could be because I pitched
the notion of a final four
that is fake fire meets real fire. Yes that's true.
Lava could be part of
the equation. Oh and I think it has to be.
That might be a way to tribute all of the great fake
volcanoes out there. Sure.
So unless you disagree
that fake lava is not fake fire.
I agree. I think it could get along great.
Anything else to say about Phantasmagor
before we wind it down. I think these are all
remarkable in their own
ways except for the Disney World one which is
too cowardly to have Mickey walk on water.
Yes that's true.
I agree with that. It's just
I mean you know we talked about the music
ad nauseum I think on the first one. But
music obviously is still the biggest
thing because
everybody I think loves it.
So that really will
they could make a shittier
show and that music would still carry it through.
But there's a lot of different
there's a lot of different reasons
to like each Phantasmagor.
I think that
Disneyland
the location still maybe is
kind of cool that it's the most intimate.
I don't know why we have to pick
a favorite but. Well
that's fair to do. Yeah I think
I would still go towards original
but I think Tokyo is pretty remarkable.
Yeah I know. Disney World
kind of comes in third I think.
I think I go Disney little world Disneyland.
It just shows you how good a franchise it is.
Because I think by any measure the Disney World one
is an incredible show. Right of course.
But like you're getting the bigger
it's an arena or whatever it's a
stadium style.
I'd like to see a stadium in the round.
But the scope is better
in Tokyo Disney Sea as far as something oh my gosh
look at now it's like got so much room.
That uses the surroundings of the actual
park. Right. So I think Disney World is third.
You have the intimacy of Disneyland
of standing in the railing
right on the water. But you have the
extravagance of Disney World.
But there is the downside in
Disneyland that you could that intimacy
could cause you to get burnt to death.
Well that's true. That's the risk you take
at any theme park. Yeah
you go there knowing that if this is how you're going to
go out it'd be the most awesome way to go.
Metal very metal. Oh I have a very
weird thing that irks
me. But it's a bigger it's
from the movie. I really
like the movie Moana and I like
the song from that movie
that is in this.
Is it How Far I'll Go? Which one? Yeah it's
How Far I'll Go. Really like
that song.
The moment where she screams I am
Moana.
That always kind of
bumped for me. Like that always seems like
this doesn't
this doesn't quite make sense
in the song. Now maybe it's
there's a story element or something
I'm missing. But I
was like you know
I couldn't think of any other like
Disney animated movie where it's like
I'm just Belle you know.
I guess the
opening song in Beauty and the Beast they're kind
of saying that. Well I know
a character who would sing it in a song for sure.
Who? Groot.
Well you're certainly
right there. That's a good point.
If he's not busy rocking a roll in
and grooving you know.
You Jason on the podcast you should sometimes just
yell I am Jason.
Just to remind everyone.
Because sometimes people don't know
who or whatever I mean usually it's with
Scott and I is the problem with the voice
so I guess maybe Scott or I should be like I am
Michael and then I'll start
making my point. So if I'm missing
a story beat from Moana
let me know. Let him know.
Why would it make more sense?
Why would she yell her name?
It is already the title.
Sit and watch the film. Study the film.
You get to do it in a house without a child
who is scared of the lava monster.
We even tried that.
This is a wall I think that a lot of parents
face maybe they can attest is that
kids who like Moana until they don't.
We were playing the video game Astro
a Playstation.
The Astro is like a fun platformer Mario
style game with a little robot.
And we did my daughter really likes
the crazy volcano
that has eyes that shoots
fire at us and then you turn him like
good at the end and then it's just all water
flowing out of the mountain at the end.
So I'm wondering if that will prepare her for
a Moana. We'll see.
A live volcano. But maybe with music and maybe that
will be too much. Any other
thoughts on the giant crab for
Moana that I believe is Jermaine
Clement.
Doing sort of a Bowie. That's
fun. Yeah that's fun. I feel like
I would just be hooting and
hollering as a kid if I was like a giant
crab or hermit crab or something.
I'd like to see
I'd like to see that in a Parker
in a show where that'd be great in a phantasmac
type situation. Better than
Radcliffe. But I think
we have now fully covered
all of the phantasmics. Made sense
to split it. Lots to talk about.
You've survived podcast the ride
all phantasmics unless
a new one pops up. It won't.
Disney is too cheap to build a new one.
Thanks for subscribing to The Second Gate.
If you want to dig even deeper join us on our VAP
Patreon tier club three where you get one more
bonus episode every month and our regular episodes
ad free. I was starting to
mess around with just to combine a bunch
of things that we've been talking
about.
Do I do it as? No I don't think I could
sing like that. Mickey
Mouse Superstar
How come you don't
walk on water?
Mickey Christ
Who are you? Are you the king
of mice?
That'll get me wrong
That'll get me wrong now
I'm Mickey Mouse
I am Mickey Christ
So your Mickey
Mouse is the great Mickey
Look we all like you it's crazy
Bye